Speaker 1: Sorry about that. First day at the office. Guys, welcome in. Welcome in. Welcome in. We're glad to have the principal back presiding over the
Speaker 2: evening's festivities. Now we are relegated to after-party status. Sorry we're so late tonight. I do apologize. I know that makes it hard
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): on some people who prefer to go a little earlier. But I was not able to get ready any sooner than this. I think I predicted it, ladies and gentlemen. Did
anyone
Speaker 4: see the nails? Yes.
did
Speaker 4: anyone see the nails do
i need to
Speaker 4: pull up the nails i can do that if you guys don't believe me i can pull up the nails
they were as predicted
Speaker 5: yes that's right that's right uh actually hold on let me find them you guys don't believe me i should
have had
Speaker 5: this done before i started yes
Speaker 2: i'll just let you guys trust me they were maroon um always sending signals always
Speaker 6: sending
coded
Speaker 2: signals
Speaker 2: is the principle always sending coded signals um guys we've
Speaker 7: got a lot lined up for you tonight i hope you are buckled in um we're gonna go over some uh uh oh oh use this video for the nails we've
Speaker 8: got i've got backup for nail footage uh we're gonna
Speaker 9: go over some of the evidence rundown some of the cars that tyler seemed
Speaker 1: to be tracked by in a lot of those videos i know neither the prosecution nor the defense made a big deal out of it but who were those people
And
Speaker 1: why were they stopped for inordinate periods of time? And do we now have an answer why we were not able to see the original footage? You remember we kept asking, you know, you guys showed us the video
of the
Speaker 1: guy running off the roof. Why didn't you just back it up like five seconds so we could
see the, you
Speaker 1: know, what you guys allege is the gunshot? Well,
I think for
Speaker 1: two reasons. One reason is that they did not want us to notice there was no gunshot visible. I mean, I think it's plain and simple. But the second reason is
There
Speaker 1: was a car in the parking lot doing something very unusual, and it seemed to be timed with
Speaker 2: the figure on the roof. We will look at that in depth
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): today. Zach Costello pointed this out on his fine program today, or yesterday. When was it?
Speaker 10: Whenever he pointed it out. No, it was today. It was today. And I want to rip it right out of his program and show it to you. It was phenomenal. It
was
Speaker 2: great investigative work and something that had gotten past your humble host. This is why we crowdsource stuff. This is why we have a decentralized investigation.
Speaker 2: into who killed Charlie Kirk, how, and why. So we're going to take a look at that
a little
Speaker 2: bit. We're
Speaker 11: going to dive into the Lance Twig's testimony. Now that a few days have passed and we've
had an
Speaker 11: opportunity to really digest it, really dig into it, see some of the other things, make some
Speaker 12: connections, do a little research. Now we have some firepower to bring to the analysis of Lance Twig's video testimony.
Speaker 2: We will go through it in detail. Um...
Speaker 2: and I have a video. I'm
going to
Speaker 2: start here real quick. I know this is an unusual way to start the program, but this is a plea for help.
This is a
Speaker 2: plea for help. I don't know where Charlie Kirk is going in this video. It
Speaker 13: appears to me to be a staircase
that leads
Speaker 13: to the Hall of Flags. In all of the coverage of this, I had not heard
Speaker 14: that Charlie Kirk went into the Hall of Flags. You'll see Dan Flood slip on the stairs here.
Speaker 14: Right.
Down goes
Speaker 9: Dan. Down goes Flood. But they're walking up these stairs and they're walking into what appears to me to be the Hall of Flags.
I was not
Speaker 14: aware that Charlie Kirk had gone indoors during his...
during
Speaker 2: his trip to UVU. I
thought he
Speaker 2: stayed outside the whole time. If he went indoors, I want to know what they did in there. They just used the can, or did they meet with somebody? How long were they in there? If anybody can fill me in on that, by all means, please, realbaronpodcast.gmail.com. I think it could potentially become a relatively interesting development,
because if
Speaker 2: we're talking about something taking place underneath Charlie's shirt, was anything affixed to Charlie in that building? Because we know it couldn't have been done outside.
Did
Speaker 2: they say, hey, we're trying something new here, Charlie. We need you to wear this.
Hey, trade
Speaker 2: this out. We need
you to
Speaker 2: put this on instead. I'm just very curious what took place in there. I don't know how we would find out. I think unless you were in the room with him, you might not know. But if anybody has heard anything, anybody has any, not just speculation. I mean, if it's rooted
Speaker 15 (lower-pitched voice): in something, please let me know. If you're just guessing, I can sit
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): here and guess
Speaker 15 (lower-pitched voice): all day. You
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): know, my guess is as good as yours. Your guess is as good as mine. It's not very valuable.
Speaker 12: Yeah.
And so
Speaker 12: we'll get to we'll get to all that. We're going to get to all that and more. And yes, I know it's late. Yes, I know it's late, but I apologize. But because
Speaker 2: it's late, I will probably move a little swifter through the super chats towards the end of night because I don't want to be up till one or two in the
Speaker 17: morning.
God's
Speaker 18: time. I don't want to be up too late. So just understand if you send a super chat.
I
Speaker 18: will read it, but I may not put it up and react
Speaker 19 (lower-pitched voice): to it on the screen, depending on how long the show goes and how many come in and all that. So just bear with me. Be patient. We will do our best to get to as many as humanly
Speaker 20 (lower-pitched voice): possible, but understand that
Speaker 7: I'm going to have to call it quits at some point just for that. Now, your humble principle
has asked for
Speaker 14: our help, and we are here to answer the bell.
This
Speaker 14: is what happened on
Speaker 21: her program. I got to pull it up. This is what happened on her program this afternoon. And we will answer the bell here.
Speaker 22: First, I think you can see the maroon nails in this footage. It
is
Speaker 23: very important for us to establish. Look at them. They're maroon.
Speaker 24: I'll be
Speaker 25 (higher-pitched voice): honest. I was hoping for a whole maroon outfit, but I will take maroon nails. Those are maroon.
those
Speaker 25 (higher-pitched voice): are maroon okay
Speaker 26: back to the content i apologize madam principal
Speaker 27: it won't happen again because he is speaking about the canines and i think i can by the way i can back channel um because i talked about the canines on the show and i can go back to that source but if you have information related to when the canines were brought on to the scene please email us tips at canisowens.com that will allow us to get a time stamp in there because he says he's observing the canines going back and forth. And I...
This
Speaker 27: could be exculpatory evidence. The Panguitch. So
she wants
Speaker 28: to know
when the
Speaker 28: canines came onto the scene. Well, lucky for her, she
has
Speaker 29: access to a Daisy because
I have a Daisy
Speaker 29: and I'm going to give her the answer here in just a second because Daisy alerted
Speaker 30: me that she had this
in her
Speaker 30: notes. So I'm going to show when the canines
Speaker 31: arrived on the scene. This is the piece of footage here that she found. The timestamp is crazy.
I'm
Speaker 31: 1629 on this, but, uh, on the, Oh, okay. I don't need that. Um, this is 12 33
Speaker 32: PM mountain time. It's a very short piece of audio, just a
Speaker 33: few seconds of audio here. 12 33 PM mountain time.
One day one
Speaker 34: 29. I've got all the county canine ahead of that way. Where do you need it?
So at 12
Speaker 11: 33 mountain time.
Speaker 11: You had all canines headed
Speaker 32: to the scene. Where do you need us? We now have confirmation with somebody from the Utah County government of when the canines arrived. So I will show you this email here. This is an email from a little public request. I
will see if
Speaker 32: this handles your, this is Lance McDaniel. He's the dog guy. He loves being a dog guy, big into dogs.
I'll
Speaker 32: see if this helps answer your questions. By state mandate, all police service dogs in
Utah must
Speaker 32: be certified by post for each area they're trained in and must pass a recertification each year. Yada, yada, training, training, training.
Dogs are
Speaker 32: trained in specific odors. So we don't have a dog do both narcotics and explosives. And that makes sense, right? If your dog hits
Speaker 35: on me, you need to know, am I a drug user?
Speaker 35: Or am I a bomb guy? I mean, that's a clear thing you got to know if you're going to have it hit
Speaker 32: on me. Bomb dogs are trained on firearms and ammunition. Patrol dogs are trained to locate evidence. The difference is guns have residue for bomb dogs and there's human odor on guns and ammunition for evidence dogs. In other words, if you have a firearm, the gun dog can spell it.
They
Speaker 32: can also smell the ammunition. They're trained to smell the different powders and things like that. So that's in request of that. And now we
Speaker 31: have a video from 5 p.m.
There's a
Speaker 31: video from 5 p.m. Let me make this large so we can all benefit from being able to see it. But this is precisely at 5 p.m. And we
Speaker 7: have a view of dogs on campus.
i'll kill the
Speaker 36 (lower-pitched voice): volume just in case i don't know what it played here but these are the dogs looking around
Speaker 37: sniff sniff sniff sniff sniff over here fido oh
sniff sniff
Speaker 37: sniff sniff sniff sniff nothing here sergeant okay what about over here sniff sniff sniff
Speaker 37: sniff sniff those were your dogs on campus at
5 p.m and a
Speaker 38: tank just in
case we need a
Speaker 39: tank we got one
You
Speaker 39: never know. You never know if you're going to need a tank. So luckily, the Orem Police Department has a tank.
Speaker 7: I'm not sure how I feel about local police departments being so militarized, but that is what they have. So Utah County and Utah State dogs are pretty good dogs. They actually have not...
they've
Speaker 7: not gone without
Speaker 20 (lower-pitched voice): notice nationally. So I will show you some awards that have been won by these dogs.
Speaker 32: Oh, hold on. No, thanks. Don't need to subscribe to your dog newsletter. Here is an award ceremony
Speaker 7: from the
Speaker 7: canine games or whatever award winning show of laws and Paul enforcement. This is from 2024 32nd annual LV MPD canine trials. You'll
Speaker 40: notice right here, fourth place
Speaker 41: Lance McDaniel and canine Loki low key. That's low key. A good dog. My
kids would
Speaker 41: get that.
Speaker 7: You boomers may not understand, but that's low key. A good dog. And I'm not knocking on you boomers for not understanding. I frankly wish I didn't understand that joke.
Speaker 7: Um, overall, overall, we've got, um, dog placement here. So we've got talented dogs, right? These, these are not, these are
not garbage
Speaker 7: dogs.
Speaker 42: If there was a firearm in the area, you would think the dogs would
have found it because here
Speaker 42: are your rankings in the 33rd annual Las Vegas canine
Speaker 14: trials, uh, 2025, first place canine scout. Yeah.
And
Speaker 14: Officer Tona with the Provo Police
Speaker 31: Department. Utah County Sheriff's Office checking in at P3 with low-key. Low-key checking in at 3P. Utah County
Speaker 32: Sheriff's Office also picks up P4.
And the
Speaker 32: Provo Police Department with K9
Speaker 43: Eddie picking up fifth place. If you name your dog Eddie, you're probably not very polite
to your
Speaker 44: dog.
Speaker 45 (lower-pitched voice): But that's okay. That's okay. The
dog shouldn't
Speaker 45 (lower-pitched voice): have human names. The dog shouldn't be like named Fred. That's not a thing.
Speaker 35: I'll see you next time.
And so
Speaker 35: we actually have some more picks from that day. Here is one pick of a particularly terrifying looking animal walking around on campus led
Speaker 7: by a particularly terrifying looking individual, frankly, if we're being honest with ourselves. This is from that day, a canine
out
Speaker 46: there doing his work. And
if you need a yet more
Speaker 46: proof and actually we could
Speaker 43: keep going, I have helicopter
Speaker 19 (lower-pitched voice): footage of these dogs. I've got all kinds of stuff. I can
show you
Speaker 19 (lower-pitched voice): where they went.
um
Speaker 19 (lower-pitched voice): but here's another dog out there sniffling around this dog does not look like
Speaker 32: the big terrifying dog the other one was but he's he's out there man he's got his nose to the grindstone he's he's sniffing
Speaker 13: around he's sniffing around so those are your uh that's your evidence that in the afternoon hours beginning at 12 33
Speaker 47: lasting until after five o'clock there were police dogs all over
Speaker 2: the joint
Speaker 48: police dogs all over
Speaker 49: the now
I
Speaker 2: want to show you a little bit of what Zach Costello covered today
because it
Speaker 32: was interesting to me. I'm not going to show you his whole video here. I'm going to back up and show you this one in particular.
This part
Speaker 32: right here was so compelling to
me.
you
Speaker 50: guys remember the footage, the footage that they all came out and said was an excellent 4k high definition. You could see the boogers in his nose. You could see the strawberry seeds in his teeth. You could see the, the here's hair growing out of his ears. Like it was soup. You not only can see him pull the trigger, but you could see the trigger action move. And you knew it was a two stage trigger, but I
Speaker 12: mean, it was just crazy how detailed they said it was. And then we looked at it and Brandy and Billy were there. They're like, I don't
know if it's a
Speaker 12: cow. Is it a person going to be big foot, a space alien? We're not really sure. We saw a blob.
A
Speaker 2: very small blob at that, but when they initially showed us this
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): footage, they did not show us the part where the alleged shot was to have taken place. They actually started it a few seconds later, and I thought
that was a
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): little strange, a little interesting.
I couldn't figure
Speaker 52: out why, because if you have the footage
and you think
Speaker 52: it shows a guy taking a shot,
show me the
Speaker 52: footage.
Speaker 52: But what are you waiting on? And I'm not going to play the video. You've all seen it a thousand
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): times. It's him running across the roof, Spider-manning down the roof, and then running out into the grass. You guys have all seen it. We've all seen it.
And we
Speaker 54: noticed that they zoomed kind of suspectly and all this stuff. Well, we now have the unedited footage.
And when you see this
Speaker 54: unedited footage,
you're going to
Speaker 54: see, I think, why it is that they
kept us from
Speaker 55 (lower-pitched voice): looking at it. Here is the
Speaker 55 (lower-pitched voice): uh footage here i'll play it on mute just because it doesn't really matter what they're saying because that's not where
Speaker 32: we're watching that you see up here on the right hand side of this parking lot you've
got uh
Speaker 32: one two three four rows of cars starting at the top
ignore rows one and
Speaker 31: two up here for now look at rows three and four and then go all the way to the right between these two rows and you see this white suv pulling
in
you see
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): that white suv pulling it hold on why do i repeat myself it's annoying um when you have a successful podcast i will
Speaker 57: market myself after you i'll do exactly how you do it in the meantime settle down
Speaker 11: settle down um
So this
Speaker 11: white SUV is pulling in. I want you to watch as
Speaker 32: it drives down the lane here. I want you to watch and see what it does. This is interesting
Speaker 58: to me. Very interesting. And then we're going to look at what type of SUV it is. And then say,
do we
Speaker 58: see this SUV anywhere else? But watch this for a second.
Here comes the SUV
Speaker 58: turning in.
Now, he turned
Speaker 59: in. Let me back it up just a hair.
Speaker 59: This SUV, I want to look at the timestamp here. This is
Speaker 40: 12, 23, and 28 seconds. This
SUV turns
Speaker 40: into the parking lot at 12,
Speaker 37: 23, and 28 seconds. Does anybody know anything interesting about that timing?
Actually, 12, 23, and
Speaker 37: 23 seconds. This is almost
Speaker 60: to the second that the bang happened. Almost to the second that the bang happened.
I'm going
Speaker 60: to speculate here in
Speaker 43: a minute, but I think it's fair to say where my speculation is going. Might this car have been involved?
Speaker 13: Was it
part of the
Speaker 13: operation? Watch what the SUV does. So we're going to go here. 12,
Speaker 37: 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28. Bang. There's your bang. You've
got the guy now standing up and
Speaker 41: running away. Notice the car has stopped. Completely stopped.
if you look
Speaker 41: at the top of the roof here while the car is stopped, you see him making his way across the roof. Now he's
on this little
Speaker 41: white triangle on the corner of the roof. Car is still stopped. Right
here, the
Speaker 41: car is still stopped. He's now spider-manning off the roof. He's spider-manning off the roof. Car is now just barely going. Now that the guy has jumped off the roof, it's turning slowly around this corner right here. He's now running off and he's safe.
see
Speaker 41: how this car is going slow and then it nails the gas as soon as the car realizes this guy's walking off
Speaker 40: and going at a pretty brisk pace this guy nails the gas he turns here and he gets the heck out of
dodge i'm gonna play it again now that you know what
Speaker 61: you're looking for i'm pointing this out for a particular reason
I'm pointing
Speaker 62: this out for a particular reason. Let me go back to where he turns in the... Oh, that's going too far.
The
Speaker 59: timing is just too incredibly suspect. And now I'm going to speculate that
Speaker 52: this car was a pickup car in case he got injured coming
off the
Speaker 52: roof. I'm going to speculate that, and I'm going to support that in a minute. This is a pickup car, in my opinion.
In
Speaker 52: case that
Speaker 63: guy got hurt hurtling off the roof. He turns in
Speaker 40: almost to the second that the Big Bang happens.
Almost to the
Speaker 40: second, maybe five, eight seconds before.
And then he stops
Speaker 40: until the guy runs all the way to the roof, which means...
If I'm
Speaker 40: right,
Speaker 64: there had to be some kind of communication so this guy would have been told when he was dropping off
Speaker 41: the roof so he could start turning to go pick him up if he needed to.
Watch it
Speaker 41: again. This
blob up here that's
Speaker 41: supposedly up here in HD taking the shot is still lying down. The
car comes
Speaker 41: to a complete stop right here. I'll
tell you when the blob gets up
Speaker 65: and start running up there.
oh he's
Speaker 41: running across the roof now he's almost to the white triangle now he's entering the white triangle the car is still stopped the
guy's climbing down
Speaker 41: spider-maning off the roof this is a
Speaker 60: 15 18 foot roof it not out of the realm of possibility you might break an ankle sprain an ankle you know uh tear up a knee in
which case
Speaker 60: you would be dead
in
Speaker 41: the water if you didn't have a getaway car
now
Speaker 41: the guy is running across the grass this white truck can see he's safe and watch the
Speaker 29: acceleration he's getting out of there
in case
Speaker 29: he needs to pick him up
he has to
Speaker 66: get to the end down there to see if he needs to pick him up nope guy's going that way all right i'm out of here
i don't think i'm wrong
Speaker 67: about that
i don't think i'm
Speaker 67: wrong about that
I
Speaker 67: don't think I'm wrong about that
Speaker 68: at all. In fact, have we seen that car before, that exact white SUV? Have we had an opportunity
Speaker 52: to see that before? Well, now that we've had brilliant Zach Costello pointing this out on the Zach Costello show, I
want you
Speaker 69: to see this footage here. This is purportedly Tyler Robinson coming into campus.
Look at that car. That's the same car. The black
Speaker 9: wheels.
White four-door. It looks
Speaker 70: like the
same car
Speaker 70: to me. It's even got the little white thing poking off the back back here.
And Tyler turns around and
Speaker 71: looks back at it.
And then Tyler
Speaker 37: stands there, and
then the
Speaker 37: car disappears. Now, did they edit
this
Speaker 41: because they didn't want us to see
what that
Speaker 41: car did?
Speaker 41: Like, I thought maybe they edited it because they didn't want us to see him take a phone call.
But is it
Speaker 41: possible that car did something else? Maybe stopped for a minute and they chatted on it? I don't know.
But they
Speaker 37: edited the footage so that the vehicle just disappeared. Watch the car again. Watch only the car.
There it
Speaker 65: goes. It's just off the races there. Now you've got another
Speaker 42: car coming up behind him.
Tyler
Speaker 42: puts his phone back in his pocket Now watch, bends that knee That right knee is the knee that's supposed to be limpy He's got a gun down there
and he
Speaker 42: can't bend it, right? Watch this again He's not supposed to be able to use that knee The right knee is the one that's supposed to be limpy, watch He
forgets
Speaker 72: it's limpy Oh, I remember now I got a limp I
Speaker 73: thought that was pretty funny
Speaker 74: The Tylers all over campus was hilarious And I'm convinced there were at least two, maybe three
Speaker 74: I'm just going to refer to them as the Tylers
from
Speaker 75: now on. They were all over the place. Tylers all over the place. Now, there's another interaction with a car that I find particularly compelling.
And I want to
Speaker 75: ask a question. Have we seen this
Speaker 37: car again?
This is
Speaker 37: Tyler Robinson in the parking lot.
Speaker 37: Tyler Robinson in the parking
Speaker 32: lot.
uh zach
Speaker 32: costello points out two cars and then he stops and points out a third car zach i apologize that i'm not using your voice here i promise he provides excellent commentary everybody should go
watch him
Speaker 32: but i'm not i'm not
um i'm not doing it
Speaker 32: because i want to talk over it so so tyler that's supposed to be tyler robinson there that's what we're told is that is tyler robinson's great challenger
He
Speaker 32: pulls up to this parking lot for some unknown reason. We have no idea what he's doing. Notice the arrow to this white SUV here. That is not the same white SUV we saw in the last two clips. That is a different SUV. This is a Lexus. I
believe the
Speaker 32: other two were Toyotas.
Same ultimate car
Speaker 32: company, but different cars.
Speaker 37: So let's watch this now. You guys see this?
This guy, there's a guy
Speaker 37: sitting in this white car
Speaker 32: here.
he's
Speaker 32: about to get going. He does that little lean up. Everybody does right before they get ready to go. There he goes. He's leaning again, doing his little lean. Now he
Speaker 41: takes off. Now watch. Oh, he can't be with Tyler. He went the other way. He's
nowhere
Speaker 76 (higher-pitched voice): near Tyler. He's going, oh, there he is. And he
pulls up
Speaker 76 (higher-pitched voice): behind Tyler and they pull off together. Now,
right
Speaker 9: before the car pulled up, I want you to pay attention to this gray SUV. It's kind of blurry in the very, very top up here on
Speaker 13: the right-hand side.
This is
Speaker 13: a gray SUV, I believe, based on my expertise, that's some sort of GMC SUV. You
watch it pull up, and
Speaker 13: it kind of
Speaker 32: comes to almost, it does come to a stop, and then it drives off, and when it comes to a stop and drives off, these two cars leave. I'll
pull it
Speaker 32: one more
Speaker 37: time in real, this is actually in fast time. He's got the video sped up, but watch it. Up here on the top right, a gray SUV comes, stops. When it stops,
Speaker 41: these two cars leave.
Speaker 77: It's almost as if the white SUV, this Lexus that was up here in the front,
Speaker 77: Was waiting to be told, I'm almost there, I'm almost there, I'm almost there. Okay, go ahead and circle around and get behind them.
And then
Speaker 77: they all drove off together.
So the question is, have we
Speaker 59: seen that gray SUV anywhere?
Is that the
Speaker 59: first and only time we've seen the gray SUV? Have
we ever run
Speaker 59: into that gray SUV before? In other words, is this part of the
Speaker 78 (lower-pitched voice): story?
Well, let me
Speaker 78 (lower-pitched voice): show you one more clip here. Actually, I'm going to show you two more clips, I think. I think I've got the other one pulled
up.
I'm going
Speaker 5: to show you one more clip here of this, potentially the same gray SUV on campus, because I do believe that SUV that pulled up
Speaker 79: looks just like this one that's pulling off
the UVU
Speaker 79: surface after the Big Bang. Thank you, Adam Bartholomew, for making sure you capture every single piece of evidence. That's
what that gray SUV
Speaker 31: looked like that pulled up, and I recognized it because of the way the headlights sit, the way the grill was pictured on that blurry image.
and
Speaker 32: so that looks a lot to me like the same SUV and it's coming off of campus here you can walk
Speaker 79: by it you can walk by
it
Speaker 80: you would
Speaker 79: have turned and looked directly into the driver's
Speaker 7: window but he does not alas he does not um
oh
Speaker 33: gosh i put the wrong thing
in
Speaker 31: there uh daisy can you drop right here i i screwed up can you drop the um tyler limping down the street
video right there i i
Speaker 81: mislabeled that up oh no it's right here it's it's uh it's to be i got it okay don't worry
about that i just
Speaker 31: put it in the wrong i just put it in the wrong spot um let me show you if we see this gray suv again I'll
see you next time.
this is
Speaker 32: another podcaster. I'll let me give him credit. I don't know who it is. Crime
Speaker 82: scene to courtroom crime scene to courtroom. I don't know what that is, but
this
Speaker 19 (lower-pitched voice): is old man. I think he put this out like back in September. So you have Tyler here limping down the
Speaker 37: street. He's right here limping
down the
Speaker 37: street, almost to the corner. He gets to the corner and stops.
this
Speaker 37: guy's playing with the stuff let's see i don't know what all he's doing but he gets to the corner and stops pulls
Speaker 13: out his phone
while he's at the
Speaker 13: corner stopping and pulling up his phone notice our
gray suv is back this is now
Speaker 83: the third time we've seen
Speaker 9: i think that same car it pulls up it pulls over
out
Speaker 9: of the lane of travel so the way these streets are structured is there's two
Speaker 77: lanes of travel in the middle and then there's two parking line lanes on either side of it
Speaker 63: you can park on this main highway that's
the way
Speaker 63: for whatever reason that's how utah does it or at least orem utah does it you can drive down the two lanes they're opposite
Speaker 60: lanes you know double yellow lines down the middle
And
Speaker 60: then on the outside of those two lanes, there's a parking lane.
Speaker 37: Now, you'll see this guy pulls over into the parking lane. I'll back it up a
Speaker 32: little bit again so no one can accuse me of making it look like he stopped when he didn't. He doesn't completely stop, but he almost does. He slows way down to just a couple of miles
Speaker 84: an hour.
And you can see
Speaker 84: he has to turn left back into the travel lane.
See him
Speaker 84: turning back into the travel lane to get around this parked car over here. So, it's clear to me, in my opinion...
Speaker 84: That guy turned out
of the
Speaker 84: lane of
Speaker 83: traffic, slowed down to talk to one of the Tylers,
and then back out into
Speaker 83: the
Speaker 85: lane of travel and then kept going on.
I just don't see how you can see
Speaker 46: that any other way. Tyler's standing there at a dead
Speaker 40: stop. This guy pulls out of the lane of traffic near him, And I am 99.5% convinced that,
Speaker 40: That that is the same SUV that was in the parking lot.
You
Speaker 83: can see the front grill area here. The same SUV in the parking lot and the same SUV potentially on campus. In the parking lot, I'm pretty sure.
And so the question
Speaker 14: becomes, if you believe that Tyler Robinson planned and executed Charlie Kirk,
are you asking any of
Speaker 86: these questions? Like, who are these people?
who is in the
Speaker 63: white SUV that very obviously waited for him to jump off and make sure he was okay before speeding off? You
Speaker 1: know, the whole thing would have been ruined if that guy breaks his ankle and can't move and he doesn't
have a
Speaker 1: 30-06 in his hand. The
whole
Speaker 87: game is up. I think that guy was plan B. I
think plan A was dependent completely
Speaker 88 (higher-pitched voice): on Tyler Robinson alone. Plan B would be jump in this car, get out of town,
And
Speaker 52: we'll blame it on two people working together. And we'll pin it on them, Tyler Robinson and someone else.
And then they probably
Speaker 52: had a whole plan B set
Speaker 1: going. We don't know about it because we haven't seen it. We weren't looking for it. We haven't examined the evidence looking for it.
But when I saw
Speaker 14: Zach Costello talking about these car passes and seeing these cars over and over, I thought, wait a minute. These are the same cars. He
didn't, Zach
Speaker 14: didn't show the guy
Speaker 52: walking down
one of
Speaker 52: the Tylers limping down 800 north.
Speaker 52: 800 south but
when i saw
Speaker 52: that suv pull up in the parking lot and he identified it i thought that's
the
Speaker 58: same suv that pulled up next to him
on 800 south it
Speaker 58: looks like the same suv
and i think it presents a major
Speaker 55 (lower-pitched voice): credibility problem to the people opposing us in our investigation into who killed charlie
kirk how and why
Speaker 89: because if
The
Speaker 89: most compelling is the SUV that turns in the parking lot, stops at a dead stop, turns in the parking lot at the exact moment the alleged gunshot happens,
Speaker 90: stops, waits for the guy to jump off the roof, turns slowly to make sure he's okay, and then speeds out of the parking
lot,
Speaker 12: getting away from the scene.
That's, to me, the most
Speaker 12: compelling, that the Tylers weren't working alone. There's somebody else on the outside.
And
Speaker 12: then you have the
Speaker 52: SUV that pulls up beside him, slows down out of the lane of travel, and then goes back out. That to me is the second most compelling. The third most compelling is what happened in that parking
lot where
Speaker 52: Tyler Robinson or one of the Tylers pulls up, stops his
Speaker 63: car, waits for like two solid minutes.
And that white SUV
Speaker 63: does not get ready to turn, circle around, and get behind one of the Tylers until the gray SUV pulls up and stops. Then it's time to go.
that's a
Speaker 63: level of coordination you just
Speaker 87: can't approximate.
That's not
Speaker 87: like set your swatches and we'll be back here at 1 o'clock. That's like, hey, I'm 20 seconds out. I'm 10 seconds out. Go ahead and go.
That is very
Speaker 87: sophisticated operation.
It's a very
Speaker 28: sophisticated
Speaker 11: operation.
Think about
Speaker 11: the level of sophistication you would have to have to know precisely when the shot was going to take place, not
when it
Speaker 11: did take place, but when it was going to take place
Speaker 91: because you have to drive on campus.
and you have
Speaker 91: to turn into the parking lot and be
Speaker 90: prepared to be the getaway driver for plan b i'm
just insanely
Speaker 90: curious i wish they would have turned their cameras and we had better views inside those cars because i want to know are they wearing maroon shirts are
they all the tilers
Speaker 64: are these all the three or four different tilers and they're all also just driving cars but i get back to it
Speaker 88 (higher-pitched voice): i think plan b was to set up two people and they probably had a second fall guy there
and that
Speaker 88 (higher-pitched voice): second fall guy was supposedly going to be the pickup guy driving him off.
Because there's no way that if the
Speaker 88 (higher-pitched voice): guy jumps off the roof and twists his ankle, they go, well, we tried. We were going to pull
Speaker 92: off a frame job on a guy named Tyler Robinson, but sorry, Bill. I guess you're going to have to eat it.
That's not the way
Speaker 93: these operations work. They've got a backup plan and a backup to the backup plan.
The
Speaker 89: original plan, mind you, was for Tyler Robinson to be framed alone, and that's what happened. But
I think part of that
Speaker 94: plan was for Tyler Robinson to be taken out so that we're not doing any of this investigation 10 months and three days later. Now, speaking of 10 months and three days later,
I don't want to show the
Speaker 90: flight paths on the screen. I
thought about
Speaker 90: showing it on the screen. I don't want to show it on the screen because I accused of harassing people,
Speaker 95: and I don't want to do that.
But I want to
Speaker 31: describe something.
I want to
Speaker 31: describe something. This hearing started on
Speaker 37: September the
Speaker 32: 6th. Now, excuse me, July the 6th. Last Monday, July the 6th, this hearing date started. And
we were
Speaker 32: able to look at the different
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): planes that
are used
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): by these different TPSA people and get a determination of what time everybody arrived.
Speaker 13: Erica Kirk's plane, we believe, arrived around...
what
Speaker 13: time is that uh 25
Speaker 95: 50 minus 6 uh 19 57 50 p.m the night before september
Speaker 12: 6 so around 8 o'clock the night before erica kirk we believe flies in on a gulf stream
5 flew into
Speaker 12: ogden stayed in ogden didn't stay in salt lake didn't stay in provo but stayed stayed way far north of town a couple hour drive hour and a
half drive away and i
Speaker 12: get it i it's
the same
Speaker 12: reason i didn't have any fault with her going in a side door.
Speaker 12: um it's
safe
Speaker 35: stay way out away from town stay way far away it's why we never told anyone where she was it's why we never told anybody we knew
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): what time she arrived just wait till it's all over and then we'll recap that's what we've done we've waited till it's all over and she's safely
back home now
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): we can recap where
she's been no reason to
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): put anybody in any
jeopardy um
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): not that it would but no reason for them to claim that we're putting people in jeopardy it's
Speaker 94: nonsensical it's stupid but but i don't even want them to have the
claim
but she
Speaker 94: flies in 750 the night
before
Speaker 77: her plane does not stop it
Speaker 88 (higher-pitched voice): keeps going it goes to Kalispell Montana ladies and gentlemen I have to ask you what in the hell is going on in Kalispell
Speaker 76 (higher-pitched voice): Montana for
a little dinky town that
Speaker 76 (higher-pitched voice): almost nobody had heard of before this case started
Speaker 60: it gets so many private plane flights from TPSA affiliated people it's uncanny how often they're in Kalispell
Speaker 14: Montana
Speaker 14: I mean, it's absolutely uncanny. I'll show you why it's weird to me.
Because if you look
Speaker 14: at Kalispell,
Speaker 40: it's basically a map dot. It's one
Speaker 32: little
tiny map dot. Hold
Speaker 32: on, I'm trying to find the main street here. Where's the main street of Kalispell? There it is. So I'm on main street here in Kalispell, Montana.
I'm
Speaker 98 (lower-pitched voice): going to give the game away if I show my screen right.
There it is. So
Speaker 99: let me show you real quickly what I'm talking about.
This is
Speaker 46: Kalispell. We're talking about, I'm not kidding, a legitimate map dot. Oh, I lost it.
I don't know.
I
Speaker 31: apologize. I'm an amateur. All right, let me back up here. I got to do this just right or it won't have the right effect. All right, this is
Speaker 41: Kalispell, Montana.
Why are so many
Speaker 41: TPUSA people flying into Kalispell? You'll notice it's just like any other city in America. They've just got some stuff, you know, old-timey-looking
Speaker 40: town. We're just looking around. It just looks like any small-town America. You know, these kinds of buildings here, all this stuff, nothing to it.
Speaker 40: And you just turn around in every direction and you think, why would
Speaker 100: anybody be flying nonstop constantly to Kalispell?
What is that? What is that brand
Speaker 101 (higher-pitched voice): new looking building? Oh, that's the FBI headquarters. They got a bank in there too, but that's the FBI headquarters
Speaker 46: for Kalispell, Montana. If you look, it says it's right there, the Federal Bureau of Investigation right there.
I
Speaker 102: don't know if that's what they're doing in Kalispell or not, but it's
enough to
Speaker 102: make you wonder as often as they're going up there. It
makes it feel like this is
Speaker 102: kind of an FBI operation. So we noticed that. We just were taking notes. We're listening. We're watching. We're seeing different people go different places. We
watch
Speaker 57: a plane drop, presumably drop off Erica, because that never goes back, drop off Erica, and immediately continue on to Kalispell.
Okay, fair
Speaker 2: enough.
And
Speaker 2: it goes from Kalispell, and it doesn't really matter what it does the rest of the week because
Speaker 42: Erica Kirk's at the trial.
And so at the end
Speaker 42: of the week, you figure, where did Erica
go by
Speaker 42: the end of the week? The trial was over on
the 10th, and then we were able to
Speaker 42: figure it out. She was picked up
Speaker 46: in Ogden, Utah.
The
Speaker 46: plane leaves Ogden, Utah at, what's that, 2036 minus 6, 1430, 2.36 p.m. It was a morning ending,
Speaker 47: drive up, grab your bags, get on the plane, off you go. And you're leaving Ogden. And
you would figure
Speaker 9: after five days away from home, you would rush home to see your kids.
You couldn't wait
Speaker 9: to get home and see your kids. Well, not exactly.
Speaker 71: Not exactly where they went. In fact,
Speaker 71: They flew into
Speaker 42: Manassas, Virginia.
Flew into Manassas, Virginia. And if you know
Speaker 42: anything about Manassas, Virginia, I'm
going to
Speaker 103 (lower-pitched voice): take a screen cap and show you. That way we hide the flight information. If
you know
Speaker 42: anything about Manassas, Virginia, you will instantly recognize what I'm about
Speaker 13: to show you. It was the strangest place you would ever think someone might go to
Speaker 13: immediately following being
in a
Speaker 104: trial for a week
what's in
Speaker 104: manassas virginia
the marine base quantico
Speaker 101 (higher-pitched voice): what's it marine base quantico the fbi testing office now manassas
Speaker 60: virginia you say well that's kind of suburban washington dc yeah but there are six closer airports to Washington, D.C. than Manassas, Virginia. In fact,
Speaker 60: When the FBI director flies to Marine Base
Speaker 87: Quantico, he flies into Manassas.
We know what
Speaker 87: planes he flies as well. I
thought that was an
Speaker 42: interesting choice. You know, you just finished up your whole week. You're dying
to get
Speaker 42: home and see your kids. It's Friday night. You've had a
Speaker 47: very stressful week, cried many times. You've had to get up and leave court a few times because the testimony was particularly stressful on you.
Um...
You don't
Speaker 105: rush home. You
don't rush
Speaker 105: home. You run to Manassas, Virginia. You
run to Manassas,
Speaker 106: Virginia. And then we saw she finally leaves the Washington, D.C. area on today, right?
Which plane was
Speaker 106: she on? Let me look at the
other.
She
Speaker 106: finally leaves Washington, D.C. on, yeah, yesterday.
Speaker 85: Yesterday. But they don't go home.
She gives her big speech. Everybody's
Speaker 9: sharing clips of it. They leave Washington, D.C., but they don't go back to Scottsdale. That
was yesterday,
Speaker 77: Red.
They
Speaker 77: don't go back to Scottsdale. Instead, they go to Dillon, Montana.
Little bitty
Speaker 77: Dillon, Montana. Tiny, tiny little
Speaker 87: map dot. Only there about 30 minutes, and then they fly to the next city over called Bozeman. Just about a 10-minute flight away.
And I couldn't figure out what the
Speaker 87: connection was between Dillon and Bozeman. Like, if you're going to fly into Bozeman, just fly into Bozeman. Why would you fly to Dillon and then to Bozeman? Do
you know who
Speaker 87: owns a tremendous amount of property in Dillon, Montana?
Speaker 87: Rupert Murdoch owns
a
Speaker 94: disgusting amount of property in Dillon, Montana. The
top of his property to
Speaker 94: the bottom of his property is 50
Speaker 63: miles, 50 miles. Think
of what
Speaker 63: interstate exit
you
Speaker 60: live near. Think of an interstate exit 50 miles away. That's how much property is in this one piece of property, the big piece of property.
They
Speaker 87: bought it from the Koch brothers. Dillon, Montana. They fly into Dillon, Montana, then they fly over to Bozeman. I don't know.
Maybe you
Speaker 87: pick up someone in Dillon and you
Speaker 46: go to Bozeman and then you have your meetings. They're there
overnight and
Speaker 46: then leave today.
Leave Bozeman back
Speaker 46: to Dillon for
Speaker 94: just a short period of time and a parent drop off. And then finally back home.
Finally back
Speaker 94: home. And then the plane, for whatever reason, continues
Speaker 12: on to Las Vegas. I don't know if someone
It
Speaker 12: was also on the plane needed to continue on to Las Vegas or whether that was, you know, the pilots like, man, a lot of traveling this week, I'm going to go gamble. I don't
Speaker 90: know.
But it's just
Speaker 88 (higher-pitched voice): a weird set of events. Like if I had just been through one of the most stressful weeks of my life,
I would want
Speaker 88 (higher-pitched voice): to go home. I would
want to
Speaker 88 (higher-pitched voice): go home. And if I'm not speaking until Sunday, maybe I go home on Friday and fly to Washington DC on
Speaker 83: Sunday. I don't fly to Marine base Quantico where the FBI testing headquarters is.
and
Speaker 60: then wait a couple of days in the D.C. area and then, I guess, drive up to Washington, D.C., give my speech,
Speaker 88 (higher-pitched voice): and then fly, but not fly home. Fly to Dillon, Montana, and then to Bozeman, Montana, and then home. I
say all
Speaker 88 (higher-pitched voice): this to say, guys,
unless she's paying for
Speaker 14: this privately, I'm
assuming all this
Speaker 14: is being paid for by TPUSA. I don't know that. I mean, truthfully, I don't audit their books, But
I think it's going to be a little bit of a little bit more.
Speaker 50: Yeah.
this is not
Speaker 50: an exaggeration. People like to bang on Candace. Oh, Candace
makes so
Speaker 50: much money on an episode or bang on this creator or that creator. Oh, they make too much money.
Those
Speaker 107: flights, those flights alone, I did a little math to Ogden, to Kalispell,
Speaker 47: Ogden, Quantico, DC, to Dylan, to Bozeman, to Dylan, and back to Scottsdale.
My
Speaker 47: back-of-the-envelope math
Speaker 12: was almost $300,000. I don't
know what percentage
Speaker 12: of our audience makes $300,000 a year. That was burnt in airline mileage in
a couple of days. That's a lot. And it's fair game
Speaker 83: because they're a nonprofit entity, which means to the extent that they call that a business expense, they don't pay taxes on it. No, it doesn't get charged to anybody.
Now,
Speaker 109 (lower-pitched voice): it's possible, like I say, she could be paying it out of her pocket.
Speaker 110: Maybe she said, hey, this is a personal flight. Here's $150,000 or whatever, and I'll just
Speaker 111 (lower-pitched voice): cover the cost. Don't worry about
it. It's possible
Speaker 111 (lower-pitched voice): they're charging it to one of the
Speaker 12: for-profit entities they have. Charlie was a wealthy man and involved in a lot of business. Maybe he had private flight credits with a bunch of his
Speaker 87: business. I don't know. I really honestly don't know.
But I am
Speaker 87: mystified. I am totally mystified.
why at
Speaker 77: the end of that week that stressful week you didn't fly straight home his parents flew straight home i saw
their plane his
Speaker 77: parents left about the same time
she did they
Speaker 112: didn't fly to marine base quantico they didn't go to washington dc they didn't go to dylan montana they didn't go to bozeman they didn't go back to dylan they didn't
Speaker 113: go back to scottsdale they went home
they flew
Speaker 113: to chicago
it's been a
Speaker 113: long week a very stressful week they lost their
son
There
Speaker 113: was a preliminary hearing with the guy accused of taking their son's life. She was very taxing on them. He went
Speaker 114: home.
He went
Speaker 114: home. I
think she should have gone
Speaker 115 (lower-pitched voice): home. I'm being honest. I
think she
Speaker 115 (lower-pitched voice): should have gone home, but that's up to her. I mean, it's her life. She can live whatever life she wants. I do want to know where the kids
Speaker 116: were this whole time.
I am
Speaker 116: curious about where the kids were. All
Speaker 36 (lower-pitched voice): right, I'm going to switch
Speaker 31: gears. I got to show you the Lance Twiggs testimony. We have a few timestamps here set out for you. I want to clarify as I go through this, I'm going to clarify one piece of confusion that has reigned supreme all week. It will
come up
Speaker 31: early, so you'll know the moment I clarify it. But let me play this testimony.
not in
Speaker 117 (lower-pitched voice): its entirety. We're going to skip around a little bit. It's 20 minutes long. I don't want to spend the whole 20 minutes. All
Speaker 118: right. We're going to open here. How well did Lance Twigs know
Speaker 11: Tyler?
How well did
Speaker 11: Lance Twigs know Tyler? Should be easy, right? This is the furry boyfriend. And
do you
Speaker 119: know Tyler Robinson? Yes,
Speaker 120: I do. Yeah, I do.
Speaker 71: do you or don't you
do you know
Speaker 71: Tyler I mean that's
you know if
Speaker 71: somebody came up to me they're
like do you
Speaker 71: know Bill Smith and Bill Smith lived in my
Speaker 68: house until September 10th I'd
be like
Speaker 68: yes I know Bill Smith he lived in my house I wouldn't have to stop pause look up at this guy think
Speaker 121: about
and do
Speaker 119: you know Tyler Robinson yes
Speaker 120: I do yeah I do
Speaker 122: yeah I do
yeah I know
Speaker 20 (lower-pitched voice): Tyler I know Tyler the
other.
Speaker 20 (lower-pitched voice): um what does tyler robinson do
for
Speaker 117 (lower-pitched voice): a living actually hold on i want i had one more thing i wanted to share here there's
not any
Speaker 117 (lower-pitched voice): notes oh
and i think i
Speaker 123: closed them out
let me let me uh real
Speaker 98 (lower-pitched voice): quickly let me go to the uh transcript
okay
Speaker 32: yeah um
So
Speaker 32: I'm going to go to where he talks about when did he meet Tyler Robinson.
So here
Speaker 32: we are
Speaker 124: back.
When did you
Speaker 124: meet Tyler Robinson?
All
Speaker 125 (lower-pitched voice): right. Okay. Sorry about that interruption. All right. So you said when you first met Matt, you were roommates.
There's been a lot
Speaker 60: of confusion that he said met Matt as
if the
Speaker 60: guy's name was Matthew and he's nicknaming it down to Matt.
Speaker 94: When you met Matt, you were roommates. Yeah.
Speaker 94: that's not at all what he's saying here um i'm gonna back it up a little bit
and then put it
Speaker 94: in context it makes a lot more sense so
Speaker 126: i think this
Speaker 127: one's mic is
Speaker 126: on okay sorry okay
you know that's
Speaker 128 (lower-pitched voice): fine okay so we should be good all right
i don't think i backed it
Speaker 129: up enough
no i
Speaker 129: didn't just
make a
Speaker 130: record i'm gonna do it again
Speaker 131 (lower-pitched voice): and will you describe your relationship with with tyler uh when you first met him anyway
um when i first
Speaker 132: met him i didn't know him super well he was just a new roommate so that's
what
Speaker 22: he's referencing when you first met him he's
like well
Speaker 112: when i first met him i didn't know him very well he was just a roommate and then he goes on to say he actually met him before that not in person
Speaker 133: uh
I knew
Speaker 133: he knew my friend group and I knew he
Speaker 134: liked playing games, but that's, that's about it. When we first, uh, like when he first moved up. Okay.
Speaker 94: Um, before we go on. And now he changes. Now let's go back. That's the context for this next question where he talks about,
Speaker 22: okay, so when you first met, met him, meaning you were aware of him, you guys may have played games. He was part of your friend group, but when you met, met him, meaning when he moved in. - Yes.
Speaker 125 (lower-pitched voice): -
Speaker 135: Okay, great.
All
Speaker 125 (lower-pitched voice): right. Okay. Sorry about that interruption. All right. So you said when you first met, met you were roommates.
Speaker 136: Yeah.
Speaker 128 (lower-pitched voice): Okay. And then at some point, your relationship progressed to something more than roommates that ran.
Speaker 137: When was
Speaker 138: that? Did that seem very confident? I don't think they were lovers. I
see no
Speaker 41: evidence of it. I don't
think they
Speaker 41: were boyfriend. I think that is a totally made up thing of this. I just don't believe it.
They
Speaker 139: don't, this guy doesn't act like it at all. I
Speaker 140: think we started
Speaker 141: dating two or three months after he moved in.
Okay. And where did
Speaker 141: you live at that time?
And he says they
Speaker 142: lived at the,
Speaker 103 (lower-pitched voice): um, at the apartment where they eventually was. Okay. Now let's skip
Speaker 31: forward to, do you even know what Tyler does?
Speaker 41: Okay. We're told this is a guy who,
that
Speaker 41: Tyler Robinson literally took a life for. He was so in love. He was so
Speaker 63: taken by him.
New
Speaker 143: construction. Okay. How
about
Speaker 144 (lower-pitched voice): Tyler? I think he was both working. I think he was working for an electrician company
Speaker 145 (lower-pitched voice): then, and he was also in a trade school for being a,
I don't know,
Speaker 145 (lower-pitched voice): higher, like, ranking electrician. I'm not sure how the trade system works for that. Okay.
But I
Speaker 145 (lower-pitched voice): think he was
both.
What was
Speaker 146: his typical workday like?
He didn't
Speaker 99: even know, like, did he go to school? What days? What time did he get? He didn't know any of that.
It's almost like
Speaker 99: he was just sort of a passive roommate, a guy
Speaker 147: who was part of the friend group, and he moved in.
I
Speaker 148 (lower-pitched voice): think he'd leave around 7, generally, and get back around 3 to 4, depending on, like, where the job was and how long it was for the day.
I want you to
Speaker 14: listen to his voice for a second.
We
Speaker 14: already said that there's
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): no way that someone would kill Charlie Kirk over the L, the G, or the B in LGBT if they know anything about Charlie Kirk. If they follow him closely enough to be willing to take his life, it
can't be over the L, G, or B if
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): they know anything about Charlie Kirk and anything about TPUSA. The place is literally crawling with Ls, Gs, and Bs. I mean, it's eaten up with the place.
So it
Speaker 29: has to be the T. Is
there anything
Speaker 29: in this guy's affect, anything in his voice, anything in his appearance that makes you think he's a T? And
then on
Speaker 149: certain days of the week during
Speaker 145 (lower-pitched voice): school, like, semesters, he would then later in the day, I think around five or six, go to school. So, yeah.
Speaker 128 (lower-pitched voice): Okay. Let's jump to September 10th.
Speaker 128 (lower-pitched voice): Did he spend the night in the apartment the night of September 9th into September 10th?
Speaker 150: Yeah, he did.
Speaker 151: Yes.
Speaker 152: Do you know?
Someone's
Speaker 153: coaching him, too.
Someone's like,
Speaker 153: yes, you have to give a clear
Speaker 99: yes.
Because he's
Speaker 99: like, yeah, he did. Yes. Yes.
Someone's
Speaker 99: coaching this guy. There are a lot of people in the
Speaker 32: room. There's only one guy on camera. There's this Sarah Varner. She's a victim's rights advocate. David Sturgill, I think. I don't know what that guy does. But there are other people in the room. It's
not
Speaker 55 (lower-pitched voice): just the two of them because there was a woman who came up, and she's not one of them, and she was fiddling with the microphone. And you can see him looking at other people.
The
Speaker 154 (lower-pitched voice): apartment on September 10th. I don't know an exact time. I just know he left early.
I
Speaker 154 (lower-pitched voice): heard him leaving, and he just said he had a long drive to work that day,
Speaker 128 (lower-pitched voice): so he was leaving early. So early, any guess as to when that was? I
Speaker 155 (lower-pitched voice): don't know. I would have thought it was 5 a.m. because that's
when
Speaker 148 (lower-pitched voice): an early work day was for him,
Speaker 140: but it was probably more like 4 a.m.
You
Speaker 156: would have thought five, but then I'm going to look at somebody and
Speaker 55 (lower-pitched voice): now I'm going to say four.
Did you see that? Like you
Speaker 55 (lower-pitched voice): don't, you don't change your estimation in the middle of a sentence.
I would have thought
Speaker 55 (lower-pitched voice): maybe like 5am.
Oh, I
Speaker 157: think four. When that
Speaker 155 (lower-pitched voice): was, uh, I don't know. I would have thought it was 5am because that's when like, that's
Speaker 158: him looking
up at
Speaker 158: somebody.
so
Speaker 158: he's looking over he's looking past there he's looking up at some
Speaker 140: early work day was for him but it was probably more like four okay
just
Speaker 158: to make
Speaker 159: sure that i can do that you're right in front of your laptop oh here you go
all right let's jump
Speaker 160: forward ever so slightly
what was
Speaker 161: lance doing on the biggest news day in utah history what time did you get up on
Speaker 162: september
10th probably like
Speaker 162: 12 to 1 p.m
Speaker 149: yeah probably
Speaker 107: around uh after it was over so i definitely wasn't there
i was just
Speaker 107: asleep that's my alibi i'm sticking to it i was snoozing officer i promise you
didn't have to
Speaker 163: work that day uh no
Speaker 57: didn't
have to
Speaker 57: work that day a wednesday
He does
Speaker 57: blue-collar remodeling and construction.
Tyler had to take the
Speaker 164: day off of work because he also does blue-collar construction-type work. Just a couple of blue-collar construction
gay
Speaker 165: guys. You
know, the
Speaker 165: blue-collar construction feels just eating
up with
Speaker 165: trans and furries.
he just
Speaker 165: mysteriously didn't have to work on a Wednesday and he just
Speaker 43: slept until after it happened I was just sleeping notice he never again asked him what he did the rest of the day
and
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): did you hear from Tyler did he call or text you before then uh no
Speaker 144 (lower-pitched voice): he sent that message in the group chat I mentioned but he didn't message me directly at all and
we talked about this
Speaker 31: but I want to show it because I think it's relatively critical
to
Speaker 31: whether or not
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): Lance Twiggs is an honest human being. I think the answer to that question is pretty obvious. No, he's not.
But he
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): says he didn't hear from Tyler that
Speaker 43: day.
He sent a
Speaker 43: message in the group chat, meaning probably the Discord chat if I had to guess.
Speaker 43: message in the group chat,
but I
Speaker 43: didn't hear from him
Speaker 64: directly, except the phone text you show says you did hear from him at 4.33 p.m. on Wednesday. Okay.
while tyler
Speaker 167: robinson is out scrambling to get his gun allegedly while
Speaker 63: tyler robinson is trapped in orem for a little longer yet because they they're police dogs and police cars and he can't get
back there's a text
Speaker 76 (higher-pitched voice): message from tyler
Speaker 63: robinson at 4 33 p.m that he says he didn't get the problem is he responded to it allegedly
Speaker 87: in my opinion that's what this
Speaker 87: evidence seems to suggest i don't know how many of these are fake i don't believe all of them are real
but i don't believe
Speaker 87: lance twigs is a
Speaker 54: credible
guy has anybody double
Speaker 54: checked to see whether
lance
Speaker 168: twigs was supposed to work that
Speaker 164: day
or was wednesday
Speaker 63: his day to sleep till 12 or 1 and then be unaccountable for the rest of the day and have no alibi Okay.
Speaker 63: nobody
Speaker 42: identify where he is. Nobody to tell you that they saw him, even though his DNA is all over the crime scene.
We're just not going to worry
Speaker 169: about it. We're going to take his word for it. Oh, you were sleeping? Good. Good night. Hope it was good.
It's a little
Speaker 170: suspicious to me. He's a dishonest human being. According to his texts, he's dishonest.
I mean, what about
He
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): asks you here, remember how I was engraving bullets. Which
is,
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): by the way, one of the most insane things in the history of the world. No one would ever say, remember how I was engraving bullets. Even if you
were
Speaker 76 (higher-pitched voice): engraving bullets, you wouldn't say, remember how I was engraving bullets. That wouldn't come out of your mouth. Was
he engraving bullets
Speaker 174: before this? Yeah,
Speaker 145 (lower-pitched voice): I don't remember exactly when, but he had said he was planning to go hunting with his family. Yeah.
Speaker 145 (lower-pitched voice): Um, and he asked me for a, if we had a, like a Dremel to, cause he said he wanted to create
Speaker 148 (lower-pitched voice): messages on bullets. Um,
and I just
Speaker 148 (lower-pitched voice): told him where Dremel was and I told
him to
Speaker 148 (lower-pitched voice): make sure he doesn't like set off a
Speaker 145 (lower-pitched voice): bullet on accident in the house.
Speaker 175: Yeah. Be careful out there playing with bullets. It's dangerous work. Just, just be careful. Would you, honey? My love,
Speaker 11: my sweet. Um,
do they
Speaker 11: sound, does that interaction, does this guy's affect sound like somebody
Speaker 176 (lower-pitched voice): Okay.
Speaker 176 (lower-pitched voice): Who's texting, my love this, and I did it all for you, my love, and my love this. Does
his interaction sound
Speaker 40: anything like someone who talks like that? Does he talk like that, like this 16th century Shakespearean
Speaker 11: prose?
Or does he sound like a
Speaker 11: brain-dead zombie mentally ill 22-year-old? Because that's
Speaker 177 (lower-pitched voice): kind of how he appears. That's
sort of
Speaker 177 (lower-pitched voice): his mental history that's been released publicly.
But I
Speaker 178: didn't really think about it until then.
How
Speaker 179: long before
Speaker 163: September 10th was this that he asked about the Dremel? I
don't
Speaker 145 (lower-pitched voice): remember because he'd been talking about the hunting slash camping trip for a couple months.
This is a kid, Tyler
Speaker 181: Robinson, who
has
Speaker 87: for months I'll
Speaker 182: see you
Speaker 43: next week.
I've
Speaker 87: been talking about this family trip he's going to take.
It's hunting and camping
Speaker 182: trip. Not something he sounds like he's, I got to get roped into this. No, he's looking forward to it. He's talking about it for months.
He doesn't present in
Speaker 43: that retelling as the type of kid who's like, to hell with my old man. He's too MAGA. I'm taking lives.
he sounds
Speaker 87: like a decent kid who like likes to hunt with his dad fish and did some boy scout activities growing
up and the reason i bring that
Speaker 89: up is not to say oh i'm super pro tyler robinson i'm just saying it doesn't sound like it's consistent
Speaker 183: with the evidence that we've been presented about
him it
Speaker 183: sounds like someone
who for a couple of
Speaker 164: months was looking
Speaker 184: forward to taking a family trip with his old
man.
His
Speaker 184: ultra-maga old man.
But
Speaker 145 (lower-pitched voice): I don't remember when he was specifically asking to engrave the bullets. So are
Speaker 185: we talking like a year before? Oh, no, not that
Speaker 186: long. It would have been, I'd say, at most a month before this. Got
a problem now,
Speaker 181: though, guys. At
most a month
Speaker 181: before this.
Speaker 164: Okay, so for a month, he's engraving bullets
Speaker 187 (lower-pitched voice): for an event to kill Charlie Kirk that Charlie Kirk doesn't announce until a week or a week and a half before?
that timeline
Speaker 188: doesn't add up.
That's a
Speaker 188: problem. Or
was he just
Speaker 188: engraving
Speaker 12: bullets on the off chance a high-profile political figure was going to make his way to Orem, Utah at some point, or St. George? It
doesn't sound like the
Speaker 181: story we've been told. Sounds
like a
Speaker 181: different event.
This
Speaker 189: guy, maybe a month before, is out there
Speaker 190: engraving. Remember how I was engraving bullets? Oh, yeah, I was engraving bullets. It
wasn't announced a
Speaker 190: month before. It
wasn't announced that
Speaker 190: early.
Speaker 11: All right, let me fast forward a little bit to the next little slice here. What
happened to
Speaker 11: the note? You got
Speaker 191: a note, right? This is the critical piece of evidence, the handwritten note.
Speaker 128 (lower-pitched voice): Okay, the notes have been titled 16.3 with a note,
and this is
Speaker 128 (lower-pitched voice): base number
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): 58. Do you recognize that on the screen
Speaker 127: there? Yeah. Yeah. What do you
Speaker 145 (lower-pitched voice): recognize it as? That was the note under his keyboard that he was referring to in the first text of that chain. Okay. So where did you find this?
Speaker 186: On his desk underneath his computer keyboard.
On the desk underneath his computer keyboard, meaning
Speaker 192 (lower-pitched voice): he has access to his computer, physical access.
If he's a roommate and
Speaker 115 (lower-pitched voice): they play the same games, maybe he has access to the login credentials, the
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): password to access the computer. If you have my password to my computer, you can send text out in my name.
I
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): would say a good chunk of the texts I send during
Speaker 91: the day are done on my computer and not on my phone, but
they do
Speaker 91: appear on my phone.
They do appear
Speaker 91: on my phone,
but they're
Speaker 91: actually sent from this keyboard right here.
That's a weird thing
Speaker 91: about the
Speaker 63: way Apple works. So what happened to the note? You found the note. It's a critical piece of evidence. We were told the note was burned. And...
i
Speaker 163: what i assume
Speaker 194: you read it yeah and
Speaker 154 (lower-pitched voice): then what did you do with it after you read it
um i
Speaker 154 (lower-pitched voice): believe i just put it back down on the desk after i took a picture of it
i believe i
Speaker 195: just put it back on the desk after i took a picture of
it i
Speaker 195: think i did
never saw
Speaker 195: it again
Well, if
Speaker 196: you don't believe me, I'll play it. He goes on
to say
Speaker 196: he never saw it again.
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): Okay. And again, the time you read it was probably around 11 o'clock or so on the 10th. Yes. The night of September 10th.
Speaker 197: Mm-hmm.
All
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): right. And did you ever see that again after you placed it back on his desk? No,
Speaker 185: I don't think I did. I
don't
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): think I saw it again. I placed it back down. I took a picture of it. I had to preserve this critical piece of evidence. But I don't think I ever saw it again.
Speaker 48: how do you not know if you saw it again? Like, do you observe anything
Speaker 77: and remember it? Like, are you the kind of, it's a pretty big deal. Your roommate confessed allegedly
Speaker 63: to murder in this note. You thought enough of it to take a picture of it. Then you set it on the desk and you can't remember if you ever saw it again.
And do you recognize that,
this
Speaker 199: series of messages here.
Speaker 145 (lower-pitched voice): Yeah, that
Speaker 131 (lower-pitched voice): was the server of his friend that I was mentioning. Okay, and this is your phone again? Yeah.
Again, I would recognize
Speaker 200 (lower-pitched voice): my phone, particularly if it was all beat up in that condition. I wouldn't be like,
Speaker 32: yeah, I guess.
I
Speaker 32: guess I do. We think we know what messages
Speaker 158: these are. We're not 100%
sure we
Speaker 158: know what messages we are, but we think we know what messages these are. We think these are these messages here. He said, do you recognize these? And he said, yeah, I think that's the server that his friends group was on.
Speaker 158: And this is these series of messages, and it has this fatal. Now, keep in mind, this timestamp is an
Speaker 95: hour ahead because of where it was captured in the central time zone, not the mountain time zone where it was allegedly drafted. So
the Zealous Monkey
Speaker 95: 55095, this purports to be Tyler Robinson down here.
But these up here,
Speaker 95: allegedly, are
Speaker 31: his friends. These are
his friend group up
Speaker 201: here.
again i i
Speaker 201: don't i don't know if if i've seen no evidence from anyone
Speaker 112: to say who actually crafted any of those messages
or those friends at all
Speaker 112: i do know that
discord makes
Speaker 32: me really nervous i don't i don't love discord i also know that
i would
Speaker 32: recognize my phone if you put my phone up and it was in that particularly that condition with the holes all over
it and the screen all cracked
I
Speaker 201: would recognize it immediately, immediately.
Now,
Speaker 117 (lower-pitched voice): here is an interesting discussion about the messages
that took place on
Speaker 117 (lower-pitched voice): September 11th.
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): Yeah, it looks like the last text from Tyler, it looks like it's 8 p.m. And
do you know what
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): day this would have been, 8 p.m. on the 10th or the 11th?
I would
Speaker 202: think that
Speaker 145 (lower-pitched voice): would be the 11th.
Speaker 145 (lower-pitched voice): because uh on at least i think so because i don't think on the 10th that he messaged anyone before me at like
Speaker 203: 11. and he turned
Speaker 163: himself in on the 11th right
i
Speaker 203: thought so yeah i just i
just feel like the boyfriend
Speaker 115 (lower-pitched voice): would know that the date he turned himself in like
none
Speaker 115 (lower-pitched voice): of us here would struggle. I
Speaker 14: think he turned himself in on the left. Like this is, and we're just like passive people. And
he supposedly
Speaker 14: was interviewed that same day
at one o'clock in
Speaker 204: the morning. Like
this should
Speaker 204: be seared in his mind. How often do you get interviewed by the FBI?
It may
Speaker 204: be,
Speaker 205 (lower-pitched voice): Maybe some more than others, but ideally not very often, not very often.
Again,
Speaker 206: those messages covered
Speaker 128 (lower-pitched voice): from September 10th to the evening of September 11th. Now, September 11th,
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): what time did or did you see,
however, on
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): September
Speaker 207: 11th? Yes. When did you first see
him on
Speaker 207: September 11th? So this is the day after. Yeah, I
Speaker 148 (lower-pitched voice): saw him when I woke up.
Speaker 148 (lower-pitched voice): Um, like I said, he was, uh, up and around doing a lot of stuff around the house.
Now, this is a
Speaker 208: little bit of an inconsistency. It's
a little bit of
Speaker 208: an inconsistency here
because
Speaker 87: not the text messages they showed in the preliminary hearing, but the text messages we have in our records that were on the probable cause affidavit, the research warrants. You remember we built out a whole timeline of different
text messages
Speaker 87: and the,
Speaker 87: Lance Twig supposedly was at his mom's house. And remember, he needed to find some excuse to get out of the house. And he had to, oh, I'll tell my mom I'm going to do laundry. I'll see you in a little bit. Now, this would have all been like 7, 8, 9 in the morning.
But now he's seeing Tyler
Speaker 87: Robinson when he wakes up.
That's not
Speaker 87: consistent with what
Speaker 164: we were told.
That is a total
Speaker 164: difference of what we were told.
You
Speaker 164: can't say, oh, I saw him when
Speaker 165: I woke up
and also say
Speaker 165: we had this whole long exchange where I was at my mother's house celebrating her birthday
Speaker 112: at 9 a.m. and looking for an excuse to get out of the house. And
those were text
Speaker 1: messages they gave us, the public. Well, they put them in court filings that eventually became made public, and that's what we looked at.
and
Speaker 1: so how do you square that
Speaker 63: circle there's just a lot of things in here that are not consistent with what was represented
Speaker 11: to us as an airtight lock tight perfect case open and shut case we
were told it was an
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): open and shut case let me uh keep rolling here i don't
have too many more cuts off of this
Speaker 185: um
Speaker 185: And then I think I
Speaker 145 (lower-pitched voice): saw him after that message where I said, I'll come home and say I'm doing laundry because I didn't want him going
to my
Speaker 145 (lower-pitched voice): parents' house right then when
Speaker 148 (lower-pitched voice): he said there was probably cops outside. So I went back home and it was just him there. So
now
Speaker 165: he's backing off of the story. He says, I saw you when I woke up. And it's almost as if somebody in the room is like, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
Speaker 60: whoa.
What are you
Speaker 60: doing?
You're
Speaker 60: not supposed to see him in the house. You're not supposed to see him when you wake up. You're supposed to be at your mom's house. Oh, so I think I saw him after, you know, we had this series. So did you see him when you woke up or not?
Like, that's the
Speaker 64: answer. That's the question. You've given two different scenarios here in 20 seconds. Did you see him when you woke up or did you see him? Oh, I didn't want him
Speaker 165: coming to my parents' house,
so I
Speaker 165: went over there.
Or are you saying I
Speaker 165: woke up at my parents' house? In which case, why were you asleep at your parents' house?
You have your
Speaker 165: own place.
And I
Speaker 145 (lower-pitched voice): said bye to him, and then he drove off. So I just went back to my parents' house.
And I just went back to my
Speaker 209: parents' house.
Speaker 210: Theoretically, was he
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): pacing? Was he just sitting down, relaxing? No, he was walking around a lot. And
Speaker 211: that's within the home? Mm-hmm.
Speaker 212: And...
Did
Speaker 212: you see his lips move at all when he said that? That he was walking around a lot? Go
back and
Speaker 212: watch this again. Just watch his face here. Did his lips move at all when he says this?
Speaker 210: Erratically. Was he pacing?
Was he just
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): sitting down, relaxing? No, he was walking around a lot.
He's a
Speaker 213: ventriloquist. He's throwing his voice. He was walking
Speaker 14: around a lot.
He's a talented ventriloquist. But I didn't see
Speaker 14: his voice
Speaker 52: moved.
But we
Speaker 52: can't just have the text messages because people can say, well, anybody can send the text messages.
Speaker 60: We've got to put his confession in his own mouth. And that's what they're seeking to establish here. Not only did he confess by text, not only did he confess by letter,
Speaker 214: he also confesses with his own mouth.
Speaker 211: That's within the home. And did he talk about what he had done? Yeah.
Speaker 211: Didn't go
Speaker 144 (lower-pitched voice): into detail. He just, I just asked him in person if what he said was true the night before, and he said it was. I started crying a little bit and said
Speaker 148 (lower-pitched voice): he wishes he hadn't done it, and then
kept going
Speaker 148 (lower-pitched voice): around and
just doing stuff, I
Speaker 215 (lower-pitched voice): think, to keep himself busy or distracted or something.
Through
Speaker 216: this whole exchange, his lips don't
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): move right.
I
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): mean, granted, there are technical glitches and computer glitches, and it's not the highest quality footage. But
I'm very
Speaker 87: concerned, if I'm being honest,
that there
Speaker 87: might have been dubbing over things. I
Speaker 47: really don't know. Like, they went back and cleaned it up because he didn't say the right thing the first time because
Speaker 13: he's shaking his head like he's like, no, he didn't say anything. Go back and I'm going to play just a few more seconds of this. I want you to watch his lips, watch his head,
Speaker 29: and then compare it to what you hear coming out of his mouth.
Speaker 144 (lower-pitched voice): It just...
Speaker 144 (lower-pitched voice): i just asked him in person if what he said was true the night before and he said it was i started crying a little bit and said
Speaker 148 (lower-pitched voice): he wishes he hadn't done it uh and then kept going around and just
doing stuff i
Speaker 215 (lower-pitched voice): think to keep himself busy or distracted or something am i
the only one
Speaker 218: on earth that sees that his lips don't match what he's saying
and that
Speaker 60: his head movements are not consistent with what he's saying? Like, you wouldn't shake your head no during that? Yeah,
he just was
Speaker 165: telling me all about what he did. Oh, sorry, hold on.
Speaker 219: Yeah, he told me all about what he did. He's confessing to the whole thing. He just says he wished he didn't do it. Uh-huh, yeah, that's exactly what he said. It's
not
Speaker 220: consistent. It doesn't look right. And if
Speaker 9: we're going to accept this as probable cause evidence,
Speaker 64: Thank you.
you at
Speaker 9: least need to record it in a way that I can see his mouth move.
Speaker 64: There are court reporting services that specialize in video depositions. They don't do it on Zoom when they're sitting across the table from each other. Now, you might have to use Zoom if one guy's in New York and the other guy's in L.A. But
you don't do it
Speaker 221 (higher-pitched voice): this
Speaker 88 (higher-pitched voice): way.
Speaker 88 (higher-pitched voice): on zoom when you're across the table from each other in my opinion unless you intend to manipulate the evidence get
a court
Speaker 88 (higher-pitched voice): reporting service in there and record his face we
were doing
Speaker 88 (higher-pitched voice): this in like 2005 six seven you would go to a video deposition and there would be a professional
Speaker 64: videographer there and they would have their lights out and their really big cameras cameras were bigger back then 20 years ago guys
They'd
Speaker 64: have these giant
Speaker 77: cameras, and they'd have these big lights, and they would test it. All right, say, count to eight, one, two, three, four. Okay, we're good. We're good.
Because with his mouth
Speaker 88 (higher-pitched voice): moving that way, you could go back and edit anything in on top
of what
Speaker 88 (higher-pitched voice): he just said.
And no one
Speaker 88 (higher-pitched voice): would know.
Now, maybe there is a court
Speaker 1: reporter there who's transcribing it. We haven't seen the transcription. We just got the video.
Okay.
but this is the
Speaker 1: type of
Speaker 12: stuff you do. This is why I'm saying Tyler Robinson is in grave danger. This is the type of stuff you do. If you don't plan on Tyler Robinson going to trial, if you don't plan on Tyler Robinson breathing oxygen and
Speaker 107: Lance twigs, sitting on a
courtroom doc giving
Speaker 107: testimony,
because i think it's
Speaker 102: ludicrous the lawyer's voice the lawyer's mouth always moves his
head's bob
Speaker 102: consistently with what he's saying okay
did he talk about what he was
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): going to do next and
then we
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): got to
turn the screen off because even
Speaker 222: our edits look too bad
Speaker 222: and
Speaker 149: then eventually said that he would talk to his parents or turn himself over
Speaker 211: and when you left was that
how you went
Speaker 211: you left understanding that he's going to turn himself in or go to his parents
house
Speaker 145 (lower-pitched voice): yeah and i didn't really want to be at our apartment while any of that was happening regardless of what went down
okay
i i'm just i'm telling you
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): right now i don't believe this i don't believe that in the year 2026 even if everything's
true
Speaker 60: even if every word out
of his
Speaker 60: mouth is the exact word he uttered that day i cannot believe in 2026 we're going to make a probable cause determination
Speaker 63: based on this not
have a witness in
Speaker 63: the courtroom not have it in writing where he signed it
but
Speaker 47: just have him giving a videotape where his lips don't move, his head bobs inconsistently, it glitches out all over the place, and
that's what
Speaker 113: we're going to submit to your honor, Judge Tony Graff.
Speaker 210: Okay,
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): before he came home, had you seen the press
Speaker 128 (lower-pitched voice): releases, any of the media on this? I'd seen one...
Speaker 185: Instagram
Speaker 148 (lower-pitched voice): like link a friend of mine had sent in our group chat. But I hadn't really looked into it at all. You
guys want
Speaker 52: to guess what that Instagram link was? I know what it was. I'll tell you right now what it had to be. It
had to be about
Speaker 52: somebody getting
Speaker 29: detained.
Because if
Speaker 29: that's the only thing he saw. If that's absolutely the only thing he saw.
Then
Speaker 11: it had to be that. Because.
from his
Speaker 11: text messages right
off
Speaker 41: the bat he says drop what you're doing looking at the keyboard what you're joking right blank i tried to delete that i'm
still
Speaker 63: stuck in oram shouldn't be longer you weren't the one who did it right i am i thought they caught the person so
if the only thing he knew
Speaker 63: about the charlie kirk
Speaker 223: case
was
was that they
Speaker 85: caught the person. I just closed
the wrong
Speaker 85: screen. If the only thing he knew about the case was that he caught the person, then
that had
Speaker 1: to be what the link was about. Because otherwise, once again, we have an inconsistency with his 1102 deposition. Because
that's what the
Speaker 112: text said. He said he was aware they caught
somebody.
And the
Speaker 112: only thing he saw was a single Instagram link. It's
Speaker 223: weird to me that that's the only thing that he saw on Instagram. He's on Instagram, and that's all he comes across? The only thing he sees?
What's my timestamp
Speaker 224: here? I had to open it back. All
right, let's go to
Speaker 43: the FBI pics. This is the fun part for me.
And we talked
Speaker 43: about this the other day, but even better in light of the fact that they have multiple Tylers running around.
Even
Speaker 43: better now.
Let me pull it
Speaker 225: up. Apologize for the technical delays, my friends.
Hey, I'm on the
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): FBI's website. You can see the URL there at the top. This
is a
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): press release about this
Speaker 226: event. And here on the screen, you see these, there's, looks like there's two...
Now, I
Speaker 40: want you to know he has shown him all six pictures already. So
if he
Speaker 40: recognized him in any of these
Speaker 63: pictures, it
should jump
Speaker 63: off the screen at him.
And he should have
Speaker 63: no question it's him. He
has looked
Speaker 63: now at all six pictures. He rolled through the first three, then he rolled through the second three
Speaker 169: before he even asks the question.
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): Do you recognize the person in these images?
And
Speaker 227: when he says, do you recognize the person? He rolls back up so you can see the face in all six
Speaker 76 (higher-pitched voice): images. I
wouldn't say with
Speaker 155 (lower-pitched voice): 100% certainty. All right,
Speaker 76 (higher-pitched voice): we're going home, guys. That's reasonable doubt. The money line
in any
Speaker 76 (higher-pitched voice): trial
Speaker 228: is, that's him right there. That's him. That's the guy who did it. I'm 100% certain he's sitting right there at the defense counsel's table.
Let
Speaker 229: the record reflect that the witness has pointed to the defendant, Mr. Bill Smithers.
And he cannot state it, and he just looked at
Speaker 230: all six pictures.
Just
Speaker 144 (lower-pitched voice): because of camera quality, but that looks like him in terms of the shoes he's wearing, the sunglasses. I don't think I'd specifically
Speaker 231 (lower-pitched voice): seen him wearing that hat, but he was usually wearing a hat, and then jeans, so...
And
Speaker 231 (lower-pitched voice): definitely, especially the bottom, the last two
Speaker 232: definitely do look like him. And
again, we
Speaker 233: can't really see
Speaker 43: what his face and that little bitty camera thing up there. We can't see who he's looking at. We can't tell where his eyes are. This is not a professionally done deposition. This is a Zoom call taking place across the table from each other.
But
Speaker 43: try to look at his face. I can imagine, because he's saying he can't
Speaker 60: definitively identify him, and then all of a sudden he decides, no, in fact, I can. That definitely looks like him.
Speaker 231 (lower-pitched voice): He was usually wearing a hat and then jeans. So it definitely, especially the bottom, the last two. It
Speaker 25 (higher-pitched voice): almost sounds like the cut in the Charlie Kirk thing. Something ever happens to me. We've got a good board. They'll figure it out. I
Speaker 234: appoint Erica.
She'll do a
Speaker 100: great job.
but but
Speaker 100: guys that that sounds like it was a jump cut listen again for the jump cut
Speaker 231 (lower-pitched voice): he was usually wearing a hat um and then jeans so it definitely especially the bottom the last two
Speaker 232: definitely do look like him
sounds
Speaker 93: like a jump cut and
you can't see
Speaker 93: with his little bitty face up there what his mouth is doing
Speaker 88 (higher-pitched voice): what his eyes are doing you can't tell
but it
Speaker 88 (higher-pitched voice): sounds like it was cut in. No one talks like that normally. I have to struggle to do it. I'll try to do it one more time and listen to the
Speaker 77: effort, the painstaking effort. Tens
of
Speaker 107: thousands of hours of broadcast training in order to pull this off. This is not an easy feat, guys, but I'll do it. Ready? I can't
state with
Speaker 40: 100% certainty. I mean, it does kind of look like him. He's got shoes on. Tyler always wore shoes.
um i've
Speaker 100: never seen that hat in particular but he was a big hat guy loved hats so he so he's wearing a hat that's
oh and
Speaker 100: sunglasses he liked sunglasses
Speaker 77: and shirts he had a shirt on it definitely looks like him a hundred
percent i'll play it one more time i
Speaker 235: think this is damning
a
Speaker 231 (lower-pitched voice): hat um and then jeans so it definitely
Speaker 232: especially the bottom the last
two
Speaker 232: definitely do look like him.
And then the
Speaker 236: emphasis on do.
It
Speaker 237: definitely, the bottom two, it definitely, the bottom two, do look like him.
Just like a
Speaker 112: second ago, you'd looked at all six pictures and you couldn't stay with 100% certainty and all you could say is he had on jeans. He liked jeans. He's a big jean guy. Big into denim.
Blue jeans, black jeans. Supposedly
Speaker 239: gay, maybe wore white jeans. We don't know. We don't know.
but
Speaker 239: it sounded like a jump
Speaker 240: cut.
Are you saying
Speaker 240: that they
Speaker 221 (higher-pitched voice): might have fiddled with this? Yes, yes, I am saying that. The guy's lips don't move at critical junctures of the testimony. He's
Speaker 9: sitting there
with a
Speaker 9: blank expression on his face and words are coming out of his mouth. And then the most critical part of the testimony, The I.D.?
where
Speaker 9: we're
Speaker 64: supposed to believe that the Tylers are all the same Tyler?
And he's
Speaker 64: like, I don't know,
man. I can't really
Speaker 241: tell. I do
think
Speaker 242: it looks like him, though, especially those bottom two. I do, I do, I do, do.
Now, you must
Speaker 107: believe, ladies and gentlemen, if a man is willing to take on a political assassination, he must have been huge.
into
Speaker 107: politics it must have been all he talked about it
Speaker 243: must have been on his mind constantly right and
group on
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): to play and he was someone that my friends invited okay
um did
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): you and he ever talk about
Speaker 144 (lower-pitched voice): politics um he did more than me uh i i didn't really still don't really keep up with politics very
much i
Speaker 144 (lower-pitched voice): usually talk about stuff he heard on the radio on his drive to work and like their work car since it sounds like a their whole crew went
went in
Speaker 144 (lower-pitched voice): the same
car
Most
Speaker 144 (lower-pitched voice): of the time, but I wouldn't say super consistently
Speaker 145 (lower-pitched voice): because it wasn't a topic I really contributed much on.
Hey, Daisy, do you
Speaker 244: have the Jordan Peterson link you can drop in there? Just put
it under
Speaker 244: 3S2, if you
Speaker 246: can. This does not sound, or in the Andrew Tate
Speaker 223: one, this doesn't sound to
me...
Speaker 223: Like a particularly convincing
Speaker 111 (lower-pitched voice): support for the fact that Tyler Robinson planned and executed Charlie Kirk over politics. Some
hate can't be
Speaker 175: negotiated out. It was on my mind constantly. I
even engraved
Speaker 175: bullets for the special occasion
Speaker 247: sometime in the last month or so.
What about
Speaker 226: Charlie Kirk?
Speaker 154 (lower-pitched voice): Did he ever talk about Charlie Kirk?
Speaker 154 (lower-pitched voice): I personally had never heard him talk about Charlie Kirk before, specifically.
Oh,
Speaker 92: man. I
don't want to spoil the
Speaker 92: surprise if you're new to the show, but Charlie
Kirk's the
Speaker 92: guy he
Speaker 107: shot, allegedly, in the state's opinion.
He never talked
Speaker 107: about him, never dawned on him to
never
Speaker 43: dawned on him
Speaker 35: to bring him up even though he's planning to take his life away and he's so much hate you couldn't negotiate out of him and
he did
Speaker 35: it all for Lance but he never bothered
Speaker 235: to bring him up never actually spent any time talking about it okay
Speaker 172 (lower-pitched voice): how about
political
Speaker 248 (lower-pitched voice): issues so did you ever talk about gender identity issues and LGBTQ rights Thank you
very much.
Speaker 249: uh no not not really no
not not
Speaker 250: lgb2q stuff either nope
Speaker 107: didn't talk about that
not charlie
Speaker 107: not really talked about much political say every now and then he'd mention something that the boys
had
Speaker 112: talked about on their blue collar job when they crammed themselves
into the
Speaker 112: car as blue collar people tend to
do just a couple of blue
Speaker 112: collar gays living
Speaker 107: together in utah it
was like
Speaker 107: 98 republican
Speaker 165: but we never talked politics never talked politics never talked gay stuff i mean
we talked a little
Speaker 251: gay stuff but not
Speaker 165: that gay politics
Speaker 252: um uh
usually if he
Speaker 148 (lower-pitched voice): did talk about politics stuff it was uh relating to trump or current like
Speaker 215 (lower-pitched voice): policies being uh again
i it feels
Speaker 254: like a cue happened
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): there i'm
gonna go
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): back and and let it just run in real
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): time without the pause Thank you.
he
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): doesn't talk about charlie kirk he doesn't talk about lgbtq stuff he doesn't talk about politics and then there's
like a there's a
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): sudden decision to change your mind all of a sudden he does talk about
Speaker 248 (lower-pitched voice): trump issues so did you ever talk about gender identity issues and lgbtq rights uh
Speaker 155 (lower-pitched voice): no not not really um
Speaker 148 (lower-pitched voice): Usually if he did talk about politics stuff, it was relating to Trump or current like
Speaker 215 (lower-pitched voice): policies being like issued or voted, voted on, I
Speaker 148 (lower-pitched voice): think. I
Speaker 256: think. We
were sold a different
Speaker 257: story. We
were sold a completely
Speaker 63: different story.
we
Speaker 63: were told this was a political assassination
and it
Speaker 63: was motivated by
the amount
Speaker 29: of hate Charlie Kirk had. And
he was so
Speaker 29: motivated by it, he actually never talked about it.
He was so
Speaker 29: motivated
Speaker 63: by it, it never came up. And the hate was about trans rights or gay rights or something.
but
Speaker 63: doggone it.
Speaker 64: He never really talked about that either. I mean, occasionally he would talk about a particular policy that's being voted on. I don't
even talk
Speaker 107: about particular policies being voted on it. Much to your guys' annoyance. Sometimes you, you text me on certain things that are being voted on. I'm like, yeah, we're not really talking about that tonight.
Speaker 258: Oh, that's fine days. Don't
worry about it. But
Speaker 258: it's, it's, it's a, it is
not the
Speaker 258: story we're
Speaker 83: told. For example,
Speaker 87: Thank
Speaker 13: you.
We were told he
Speaker 87: confessed to his parents and they turned him in. It was a key critical part of the narrative of Tyler Robinson did it.
We're told he's
Speaker 87: motivated
Speaker 113: by hate. We
didn't get any
Speaker 113: evidence of that. We didn't
get any
Speaker 113: evidence his parents turned him in.
We were told
Speaker 113: he
Speaker 13: was motivated by this left-wing ideology, you know, this gay trans stuff.
I
Speaker 99: have some,
Daisy's
Speaker 100: good. She tracked him down on Reddit, of all places.
And this was Lance on
Speaker 77: Reddit. He's on a Jordan Peterson Reddit. This is subreddit Jordan Peterson.
Lancelot three here
Speaker 169: talking.
people
Speaker 37: need to stop putting themselves in boxes because political parties don't care about any of their people. They just want money. That
was five
Speaker 59: years ago. I mean, does it sound, again, like a particularly political person?
Speaker 35: And if so, he's more on the Jordan Peterson side. Maybe we'll, in the coming
Speaker 89: days, maybe we'll show you some more of his Reddit posts. There are a lot of them. He was very active
Speaker 91: on Reddit.
Speaker 91: talking about, I mean, appeared, at least in my opinion, to be a fan of Andrew
Speaker 238: Tate, Jordan Peterson. Like, these are not rabid left-wingers. These
are people
Speaker 238: that the rabid left-wingers
Speaker 260: hate, even mainstream Republicans hate.
So is this consistent
Speaker 14: with what we were sold?
This
Speaker 14: is the open and shut case. No, it's not.
We got
Speaker 261: a kid who can't even identify him until his lips stop moving. And
then
Speaker 262: they're like, oh yeah, that's definitely him. That's definitely him. I swear. I'm 100% him. Look,
Speaker 223: we may get to the end of this and maybe it'll be so obvious Tyler Robinson did it.
Maybe
Speaker 223: it'll be one
Speaker 263: of those things where you just can't avoid that reality and nobody would ever question that Tyler Robinson did this. And
if we get to that point, then your
Speaker 91: humble host will be the first one to get up here and be like, that is an open
Speaker 12: and shut case.
But anyone right now who's
Speaker 12: telling you it is an open and shut case is not being honest with you.
Speaker 12: Anyone telling you right now this is one of the
Speaker 89: clearest-cut cases they've ever
Speaker 30: seen in criminal law is not being honest with you. I saw someone today who's like, you know, it doesn't have to be on camera in order to be a crime. Well, no, but you've got to have some evidence.
All the evidence
Speaker 30: can't come through the roommate whose DNA is all over the crime scene.
Speaker 39: That's called reasonable doubt. The roommate, by the way, who doesn't have an alibi, his alibi is I was asleep.
Speaker 102: Okay.
what else were
Speaker 102: you doing? Why weren't you working on a Wednesday, dude? And why is your roommate, I
Speaker 107: mean, I'm sorry, I don't believe he was, I'll state it right now, I don't believe they were in a gay relationship. I just don't. I
think we were
Speaker 39: sold that as a motivating factor. I don't
believe, I see
Speaker 39: no evidence
Speaker 264: of it. He doesn't look like it.
and when i say
Speaker 265: look like it i don't mean that you like tell by looking to somebody but he doesn't act like it he doesn't he
doesn't it
Speaker 265: doesn't support
Speaker 266: the narrative they stayed in separate bedrooms they started out just as roommates they he doesn't know where he works he doesn't know what time he normally
Speaker 267: leaves or what he you know i think he might be in school or something i don't know
i think the kid was going like excited to go
Speaker 268: hunting with his dad he'd been talking about it for months.
Speaker 269: that's just not what we were sold and i think had tyler died we would have all believed
it i know i
Speaker 269: think i would have
i think we would have just all
Speaker 269: believed it
Speaker 204: there might have been a few people that
Speaker 270: around there like you
take you back to 9-11 i've come a long
Speaker 270: way on that
but
Speaker 270: I remember for the first few years
Speaker 271: at several years on 9-11, I would see someone say, you know, jet fuel can't melt steel beams. And I'd be like, oh God, here we go.
Speaker 272: Controlled demolition. Wasn't terrorist. Dancing
Speaker 273: Israelis. Oh,
Speaker 274: come on guys.
Speaker 273: This is so stupid. You
Speaker 275: know, but after a while you kind of look at it and you're like,
why were they
Speaker 275: dancing? And
what happened to
Speaker 276: that company they owned? Why was it a fraud? Where'd they all go? Why
were they
Speaker 242: holding lighters up in front of the World Trade Center and taking pictures of themselves? That's a little weird. The whole thing's a little weird. And
now that I think
Speaker 277: about it, why did Building 7 fall anyway? Like,
Speaker 63: it took me like 10 years before I knew Building 7 fell. I think
it was
Speaker 63: in the 20-teens and someone said something about Building 7. I was like, what are you talking about? What's Building 7? That
was a red
Speaker 63: pill moment for me.
Went back
Speaker 89: and watched the footage. I was like, oh, wait a minute. They said on the news that the building had fallen and it hadn't fallen yet. And
then it
Speaker 68: fell and it felt like that. It just fell in on itself.
Why didn't
Speaker 68: anyone tell me it fell? We talked about the Pentagon,
that
Speaker 278: conveniently there's no pictures of anything striking. We talked about the World Trade Center, one and two. We talked about Shanksville, Pennsylvania, where they didn't find much of a plane. Why
is no one
Speaker 278: mentioned building seven? Why?
Speaker 278: Now, it took me
Speaker 47: years to figure this out
or to
Speaker 47: come around on the issue. I don't know that I figured it out, but I've at least evolved on the issue or devolved, depending on your perspective.
And maybe years from now, I
Speaker 165: would look back and be like,
that doesn't
Speaker 165: really look like a 30-06 to the neck, if I'm being honest.
But when Tyler Robinson
Speaker 235: turned himself in and the whole case started, in my opinion, falling apart.
and they
Speaker 52: kept telling us oh his parents turned himself in his parents turned himself in his parents turned himself in and i know people who personally had spoken to the family they're like they're lying we did not turn
Speaker 68: him in like
we might
Speaker 68: have driven him there but we didn't tell him he did it because he didn't tell
us he did it and i thought wait a minute
Speaker 165: why are they telling us that he confessed to you if he didn't confess to you
why why are
Speaker 165: we being
Speaker 279: told this
And so
Speaker 280: maybe we would have started to come around.
Speaker 281: Maybe. But
I don't
Speaker 282: know. I
don't know that we
Speaker 282: would have. And
I think that was the
Speaker 84: plan. I think we saw plan B today. Plan
B was if
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): the guy jumping off the roof hurt himself on his way down, he would be picked up by the white SUV.
And then
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): they have to frame two patsies.
That was
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): plan B. I'm pretty confident on that now. There's no reason that car stopped,
entered exactly
Speaker 12: as the shot took place, shot,
came to a
Speaker 12: dead stop until the guy jumps off the roof and then turns
Speaker 77: and accelerates as soon as he sees he's fine.
There's no reason
Speaker 77: for that. And it happens to look awfully
Speaker 89: lot
like the
Speaker 89: exact same car that had just pulled up to Tyler Robinson.
One of the
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): Tylers.
as
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): he was coming onto campus maybe
Speaker 52: minutes earlier.
Looked like the same
Speaker 52: car to me.
Why is this
Speaker 52: car hanging around this guy so much? It's
almost like he knew something
Speaker 52: was going to happen.
And what's up
Speaker 77: with this gray GMC car?
Speaker 77: This SUV that's following everywhere that seems to be in the parking lot coming to a complete stop right as Tyler's pulling out right as an SUV pulls around behind him. And why did that SUV seem to wait until the the white SUV? Why did it seem to wait until the gray SUV was in the parking lot before it circled around
Speaker 87: behind him so they could all leave together?
And why is that same gray SUV
Speaker 87: seem to
Speaker 223: be pulling up beside him out of the lane of traffic? It seems to be the same
Speaker 183: car to me. It looks identical.
How many
Speaker 183: of them could there be? It's not a late model car. It's a couple of models
Speaker 89: ago. But why does it look like it turns out of the lane of traffic when one of the Tylers is stopped there on the intersection waiting and it pulls
up and it
Speaker 89: slows down to almost a stop and then pulls back out into the lane of traffic and drives off? Were they talking
Speaker 278: to each other? Did they communicate in some way? Did they make a hand signal, an eye signal?
Did they make
Speaker 278: eye contact? We don't know.
and
Speaker 83: it was that the same gray suv turning off of campus
Speaker 87: i you know that's the one that probably if i had to say any of those weren't the same car i would say it's that one because
that one would have
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): been stuck in traffic i think trying to
Speaker 109 (lower-pitched voice): get off of campus as that was happening i don't think it could have gotten off of campus into that shopping center in the right time but maybe i don't know i don't know exactly what time
that was
Speaker 109 (lower-pitched voice): actually i could go back and figure out exactly.
Speaker 283: it
Speaker 284: was 17 no it was 27 minutes after the shot said
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): it'd be 1250 no it can't be the same SUV can't be in two places at once
so were
Speaker 285 (lower-pitched voice): there multiple Tylers
walking
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): around town were there multiple SUVs that were actually the same SUV that were pulling up next to the multiple Tylers
were
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): there multiple
Speaker 286 (lower-pitched voice): Dodge challengers? Why didn't they tell us the license plates? Why are they giving us the descriptions?
There's enough
Speaker 35: going on that
you have
Speaker 35: to step back and evaluate the full
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): court press being put on this case by people who are trying to convince you it was Tyler Robinson alone. Why
not just let the
Speaker 287: court case
play out?
Why not
Speaker 287: ask the questions we're asking? What I think are pretty obvious questions.
If he's motivated by
Speaker 288: politics, why did they never talk about politics? If he wanted to kill Charlie Kirk, why did they never talk about Charlie Kirk? If
he says he didn't contact until
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): 11, why is there a text message from him at 433? Why
wasn't he at
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): work that day? I mean,
I think
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): these are
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): legitimate questions. I don't
think these are
Speaker 115 (lower-pitched voice): crazy questions to start asking.
Speaker 115 (lower-pitched voice): um all
Speaker 43: right let me do this uh i'm
gonna run
Speaker 43: through some questions i'm gonna get to as so many comments i'm gonna get to as many as i can i don't want to scare you off um but um it is already
almost
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): nine o'clock here and uh i've got two meetings tomorrow i will not be on the air tomorrow won't do a member show till friday but i've got two meetings tomorrow and will not be able to be on the air at all tomorrow so
um so i'm gonna
Speaker 290 (lower-pitched voice): run through as many of these as i can i should be able to get to most all of them but i
have to
Speaker 290 (lower-pitched voice): start skipping around at the end uh,
don't
Speaker 290 (lower-pitched voice): get mad at me you can i don't care
and i
Speaker 57: do but i don't uh
if you
Speaker 57: like the show click the like button it always helps i i hate
Speaker 12: to remind you but i have to be reminded i watch a lot of podcasts and until they say hit the like button
i
Speaker 291: usually don't um i'm actually watching candace right here and realized i didn't even click the like
button on
Speaker 291: that one um
so
Speaker 50: yeah
Speaker 12: click the like button oh the clips channel it's people are loving the clips channel baron coleman clips just search baron coleman clips on youtube you'll find it it's amazing if you want to join the program if you'd like to make a monthly contribution to the production of this program uh get access to exclusive member content we do a
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): member show every week i think one week out of like seven months we've skipped and that was because i was out of town
But if
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): you'd like access to the members' content and it's just an easy way to support the
Speaker 292 (lower-pitched voice): program, when you go to subscribe, right next to that's a button that says join. You can click the join button and it'll take you to the members' page. If you want to join and
Speaker 12: save $3, don't sign up on your YouTube app. Go
to a
Speaker 12: browser, log in that way and join from there.
Speaker 12: um that'll save you the three dollar apple fee i don't get anything out of that three dollar apple fee that all goes to them they got plenty of money don't don't pay them anymore
they got enough i
Speaker 12: promise john don't
be rude
Speaker 12: but baron was giving us time to watch candace which is also important to him love you be uh yeah i didn't
Speaker 90: want you guys to feel like you had to make a choice there at the end so i apologize
Thoughts from
Speaker 90: last night's episode. What if they tried to take out TR before the trial? What will we do? Charlie's still gone. No justice.
Speaker 31: Still lies. What happens next, regardless of proving who did it? Yeah, if
they try
Speaker 31: to take him out or successfully take him out at this point, I think it would be supremely problematic
Speaker 32: because they will have to explain I don't know.
Speaker 32: Why it is that on a case
that appears
Speaker 32: on its face to be falling apart, that that's when their guy decided to take himself out. That doesn't usually work that way. I think that's why
Speaker 50: they're trying so
hard to convince you the case is bulletproof. They want that
Speaker 50: message out there in case
he does
Speaker 115 (lower-pitched voice): get removed.
They want the
Speaker 115 (lower-pitched voice): message that this case was so bulletproof
when
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): the reality is it is not.
It is not.
not uh one
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): handwriting samples can be used with specific ai programs to reproduce a letter would clearly be printer ink not
pen so
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): it would have to
burn to
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): hide that um yeah except there were a couple of letters i think that survived the burn so maybe they can be tested if not that's very suspicious
what's up my beat
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): can't wait to see how this week goes now that the principal is back my birthday was this last saturday had a great
Speaker 47: one happy birthday less all I don't know.
I
Speaker 47: hope it was as great as you thought it was. My prediction,
Speaker 195: Candace has the battle bun on all week long.
She was
Speaker 195: battle bunned up tonight. There's no doubt about that. She was bringing thunder.
Speaker 87: Thundare. Reminder, the grieving widow claims she had CK's phone for days and never read through the messages he'd sent the day before. Imagine that.
Wouldn't most
Speaker 187 (lower-pitched voice): wise pour through every word ever typed. Um...
Speaker 293: maybe, I mean, again, I'm giving her the complete benefit of the doubt when I say this,
you
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): know, I think it's only
fair to do
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): if she was particularly destroyed by this as most widows, I could
see her
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): not wanting to dig through
it in
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): like the first five days.
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): Now, months later, I think she should have gone through it. I mean, those are the last words your husband's
ever
Speaker 294: spoken or written. Yeah.
Speaker 294: congratulations top 25 on spotify our humble host has arrived all glory to god congratulations
Speaker 91: to daisy too and the whole outfit christ is king indeed it is a team
effort here
Speaker 91: uh takes all
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): three of us and more we get a lot of tips from other podcasters and members of the jury who
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): who write in tips so it's it's a it's a team effort it's an absolute team effort
but yeah
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): we uh
Speaker 89: someone sent that
to me
Speaker 89: yesterday they're like you know you're in the top 25 on spotify and i was like no they're I'm like, go look,
we were
Speaker 89: 24.
We're
Speaker 89: 24. I don't
know
Speaker 295: if we still are. How did they change it every day? I'll pull it up if we still are. If we've dropped out of the top 25, I'm going to hide it.
But
Speaker 32: I'll look. I'll look.
Let's see how it
Speaker 296: works here.
Are
Speaker 36 (lower-pitched voice): we still
Speaker 297: there? Humble host, humble host. Oh, yeah. 24. There it is right there. Right
Speaker 75: there. 24. Take that, Knowles.
Suck it
Speaker 75: daily. Why? Oh, sorry.
Sorry.
Speaker 98 (lower-pitched voice): Uh, uh, congratulations, Michael podcast is doing
swimmingly. It's
Speaker 98 (lower-pitched voice): not as swimmingly,
Speaker 297: uh, Pierce Pierce
Speaker 298: Morgan. Um, yeah, I was, I was excited about that. So thank you. So if any of you guys who watch on Spotify regularly, um,
Speaker 20 (lower-pitched voice): we appreciate it. Spotify has been a great partner
Speaker 91: to us. They've been nothing but helpful when we've had questions.
And
Speaker 91: I'm very thankful for them. Counselor B,
Speaker 52: FYC, the
real reason for all
Speaker 52: the TPSA and company mishaps was, is to annihilate pre-September
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): 10th TPSA. So they aren't incompetent or stupid. They're doing the job they were hired to do.
I tend to agree
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): with that
Speaker 299 (lower-pitched voice): wholeheartedly. I endorse that. And thank you. That's very kind. The one I feed.
Speaker 299 (lower-pitched voice): This one goes out to the one you feed. Might be as you
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): grow and get massive amounts of followers, please stay humble and keep reading all our super chats.
Christ is
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): king indeed. I'll address that because last
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): night I did have to blow through a lot. I cannot
commit to
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): reading them all on air. I just promise you I can't.
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): There are days that it will not happen. I get through as many as I can. This is my favorite part of the show because it's a chance to interact with people that I don't interact with on a regular basis. I
Speaker 292 (lower-pitched voice): can't answer every email
It
Speaker 292 (lower-pitched voice): would take, frankly, days to get through one day's worth of email and read them and respond and do all that. I can't read everything someone says, hey, check this out. I can't watch everything someone
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): says, check this out.
I'm not
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): aware of another podcast host who spends
as much
Speaker 12: time or as much effort reading Super Chats.
Speaker 12: and I do try to read every member
Speaker 292 (lower-pitched voice): chat because
those are
Speaker 292 (lower-pitched voice): people who pay for the privilege of joining the members page, and that's one of the privileges I try to offer is reading every member's chat, pull it up on the screen and react to it.
But I
Speaker 95: can't commit to reading every single super chat. Some nights there's just too many. Some nights there's not, and we can get through them all, and some nights there's too many.
When I
Speaker 95: started this show, I
would get
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): maybe 10 or 20.
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): super chats and so at the end of the show i would spend 20 minutes and read through
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): them all
some nights
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): were on bordering on two and a half hours and that's with me even being a little selective at times that's not to say don't send them i do read them like afterwards i spend the time and and while everything's editing and processing i go through and
i scroll through all
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): the super chats and see the ones i missed and read them and sometimes they make me chuckle and sometimes i
you know but
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): i i just i cannot commit to reading them all on the air that's not being
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): Uh, what'd you say? Stay humble. It's not being not humble. That's just, it's just a reality. I'm not going to do a seven hour show every day. I can't, I can't, um, it's not fair
Speaker 300 (lower-pitched voice): to, uh, not fair to everybody to do that.
So thank
Speaker 300 (lower-pitched voice): you. I appreciate that.
Uh, Baron, I
Speaker 301: messaged
Speaker 302: a few shows back about God answering your prayers, but not necessarily how you'd think maybe a
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): month ago. I'd asked for prayers of the weekend. He kept delivering. He's probably always done. And I'm just finally noticing Christ is King. Indeed.
Uh,
Speaker 292 (lower-pitched voice): chop rock
Speaker 95: guitars.
That's
Speaker 95: wonderful news. That's wonderful news. We're promised God hears every
prayer. And
Speaker 95: some prayers, well, Garth Brooks had a song. Some of God's greatest gifts are unanswered prayers. He
talks about
Speaker 292 (lower-pitched voice): running into his high school sweetheart and how he just begged God to marry this girl. And they
Speaker 50: didn't get married. And he ends up with this beautiful wife and kids and like the greatest life he could have ever imagined. And then when he
Speaker 292 (lower-pitched voice): runs back into the girl, he realizes...
And
Speaker 292 (lower-pitched voice): that's God's greatest gift was that that prayer was not answered. So
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): sometimes God has a better plan than what we're begging for. But I appreciate you following up on that. Principal has
Speaker 303: returned. It looks like some problem kids on Twitter X haven't done their homework and are spreading
Speaker 90: disinformation to make the principal look bad while she was on away. Shame.
Yeah, I
Speaker 90: mean, I don't pay attention
to the
Speaker 90: haters.
Speaker 95: I really don't.
uh i
Speaker 95: know some people do and they get all bent out of shape about it but it does it doesn't bother me
Speaker 292 (lower-pitched voice): much like i'm doing battle with
some i saw
Speaker 292 (lower-pitched voice): somebody sent me something and i clicked on his account and i'm not making fun of smaller creators but he had like 2400 subscriptions and i'm like
Speaker 304: he's
like i'm
Speaker 304: gonna air baron out i'm like okay
go for it have fun let
Speaker 225: me know how it
Speaker 304: turns out
uh baron
Speaker 303: canton defense subpoena tyler or Seltow
Speaker 89: Records or Google Timeline, if enabled.
Speaker 89: Close bank records to corroborate the steakhouse alibi and test the prosecution's timeline. Or
have
Speaker 305: they already? Maybe they have. Maybe that's why they did not show any concern
Speaker 50: towards the steakhouse. I don't know. I don't know.
Wasn't there a guy who
Speaker 50: said he was paid to say he did it? Paid by whom? Has anyone asked?
Yeah, that
Speaker 50: was George
Speaker 90: Zen, allegedly. That was someone at the hospital allegedly
Speaker 306: said that
Speaker 306: George Zinn told the hospital worker that he was paid to do it or paid to jump up and all that stuff.
Just a thought
Speaker 153: via security. A call could have been linked to CarBT. What if updates came via CarSpeaker auto-connected
Speaker 307: to phone and all in car? I
mean,
Speaker 308: yeah,
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): we don't know. My best guess is it was Frank Turg's phone. He
claims he
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): was on FaceTime the whole time.
If Ben
Speaker 192 (lower-pitched voice): Shapiro is being accurate, and I don't know why he'd lie about that,
it
Speaker 192 (lower-pitched voice): makes a lot of sense that it would have come through Frank Turek's phone. I don't know. Frank
says he
Speaker 192 (lower-pitched voice): was talking to his son and shoved it
in his
Speaker 192 (lower-pitched voice): pocket or something. He's
told a
Speaker 192 (lower-pitched voice): lot of things I don't know about, though.
I've been
Speaker 57: listening to screw tape letters today. Couldn't get image of George Farmer narrating out of my head.
George
Speaker 309: Farmer? Mr. George Farmer?
The betrothed of
Speaker 310: Candace Owens Farmer?
Speaker 310: narrating screw tape letters i
do want to
Speaker 310: interview him
i hope
Speaker 311: he'll let me christ is king
indeed who's here for the
Speaker 311: after party good
Speaker 183: morning from sydney australia sending you lots of love and
prayers of
Speaker 183: protection to you and your family i get really excited when i see my family and friends share your content
christ
Speaker 177 (lower-pitched voice): is king indeed um
well thank
Speaker 177 (lower-pitched voice): you that's interesting to know all the way over in australia people sharing stuff that's
Nails looked
Speaker 312: orange to me. Oh, man, I was going for maroon. I was really rooting for maroon. Were they orange? I
was watching on a
Speaker 313: computer, on a phone and a computer, so maybe I didn't see it right. It
Speaker 314: looked kind of
Speaker 315: maroonish, but I'll give you orange if they were orange.
Easter eggs
Speaker 315: are the best. Candace is a professional. That
Speaker 43: man thought they were maroon.
Speaker 165: Ha,
ha, ha, ha.
or
Speaker 165: woman excuse me that woman thought they're maroon congratulations on top 25 grok had your back on x good grok uh love from
Speaker 316: yankee town florida population 289 but i'm the only
Speaker 91: one generation off the mountain and a fellow iu grad thank you um well
go
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): hoosiers thanks for checking in i know you're a brilliant individual if you graduated from iu
First
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): super chat, third shifter. So love this time slot. Number one fan, Flant, Michigan.
Doing
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): amazing work. Love my
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): tank and tea. Keep doing what you do, Baron.
Third
Speaker 317 (lower-pitched voice): shifter. I
don't know how
Speaker 317 (lower-pitched voice): people do that. I
know a
Speaker 317 (lower-pitched voice): lot of people do. I mean, it's a huge percentage
of
Speaker 318 (lower-pitched voice): the population works third shift,
but I like to
Speaker 318 (lower-pitched voice): sleep at night. I
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): don't sleep well during the day. BK, increasingly grumpy when speaking. It's unbecoming. That is all. Love you, B and Daisy.
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): I watched that whole speech she gave over the weekend. Not the
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): tone I would have struck. Not the tone I would have recommended
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): she strike.
But with a
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): PR person as lousy as Andrew Colvett, I understand why she does that. They probably told her, oh, you, yeah, you're going to kill. Walk around, pace all around
and
Speaker 63: get a weird look
on your
Speaker 63: face and, like, say stuff that doesn't make sense.
I want
Speaker 319: the country to look like this room, not the courtroom.
Even though I was
Speaker 320: in the courtroom.
and so
Speaker 320: was my mother-in-law and my sister and
all my
Speaker 320: friends.
Speaker 321: Maybe
not
Speaker 322: the best time to say that.
Speaker 77: I love our podcast family. Christ is king indeed. Thank you, dear Jen. Regarding the spelling caliber when they released the text, but I'm stuck in Orem for a little while longer yet, but
I got to
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): grab my rifle still. Americans would omit the yet and say, I've still got to
grab
Speaker 323 (lower-pitched voice): my rifle.
Speaker 323 (lower-pitched voice): Yeah, they wouldn't omit it. They would just move it. Oh, omit the yet. Still got to grab my rifle still. Stuck
in Oram a
Speaker 324: little while longer. Yeah. I don't
think they
Speaker 325: were written by an American. I don't think they were written by Tyler
Speaker 45 (lower-pitched voice): Robinson. I'll tell you that.
Took me a
Speaker 45 (lower-pitched voice): while, but that opening song now makes me dance when it comes on. Feels good after being sick. Wash
Speaker 177 (lower-pitched voice): hands, guys. Nasty norovirus going around. Ooh, is that
the
Speaker 115 (lower-pitched voice): one that
makes you go
Speaker 115 (lower-pitched voice): number two a lot?
Is
Speaker 115 (lower-pitched voice): that norovirus?
I think it
Speaker 115 (lower-pitched voice): is.
Speaker 326: Yeah. Vomiting and watery diarrhea.
Sorry about
Speaker 327: that, Ken.
Wash your hands. Take
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): your vitamin D. Baron had a thought about B. Sneff.
Says he doesn't know
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): the TP employee that TR spoke to. But if he did, he knows they had nothing to do with it.
What if
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): that's because
he knows
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): everyone involved?
Crossed my mind. Definitely crossed
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): my mind.
And
Speaker 328 (lower-pitched voice): you're familiar with the UCMJ. Would you consider DJT, DJT Jr. and JDV saying TR is guilty, undue command
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): influence and the military commanders are supposed to remain neutral?
JD being a
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): Marine knows this. No, I wouldn't.
I
Speaker 323 (lower-pitched voice): wouldn't. They're not particularly junior. I mean,
he's not in
Speaker 323 (lower-pitched voice): the military, nor is Vance.
Nor is Vance
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): right now. Donald Trump
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): is the commander-in-chief but he's the he's the president he can say whatever
it's not right i don't think
Speaker 290 (lower-pitched voice): the president should be commenting on pending criminal litigation but he's the president
gardening in a
Speaker 35: light rain wearing my love you
my b
Speaker 35: racerback tank love it you have been with me in my garden since ian mentioned you in google trends i fell in love it welcome in and jesus loves you christ
is
Speaker 13: king indeed blessed bless you and this group man that was awfully positive you are happy it's
Speaker 52: right there in your name
it
Speaker 52: was so great to see your name all over the comments in julian dory's recent episode it seems we all agree you're the antidote to the slop is
he a slop
Speaker 52: pusher is
Speaker 329: he a fed slopper who's julian dory let me look him
up julian dory
Speaker 65: internet personality uh
investigative
Speaker 158: journalist julian Dory podcast, massive following.
I don't
Speaker 158: know, is he pushing the Fed Slop or did he just host someone who was pushing Fed Slop? But
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): thank you. Thank you.
I was
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): reminded today as I was driving down the interstate that I'm always searching for unmarked state troopers in Dodge Chargers. Anyone else noticed
Speaker 90: unmarked top cars are after Chargers? Yeah, except Tyler was
in a
Speaker 95: Challenger, not a Charger. Challenger is the two-door version. Charger is the four-door version.
But
Speaker 95: yeah, good
Speaker 209: call. Nails were definitely not maroon, Barron. Check your eyes. Definitely shade of
them.
Speaker 330: Okay. Okay. I'll allow it.
I'll allow
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): it. Listening to BJ.
BJ, talk about EK
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): losing it and Charlie's mom comforting her. Benny Johnson. Benny Johnson. Makes me sad and
sus
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): of Charlie's parents now. Charlie Kirk's dad goes way back
with Trump.
I
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): don't think they killed their kid, if that's what you're suggesting. I agree
they go
Speaker 90: back. Harpole in one of the interviews said they went to the bathroom before the event. Well, that must have been the trip up the stairs.
Speaker 45 (lower-pitched voice): Thank you. That's good advice. Good catch there, Cassia. You're not the Cassia, are you? The Daily Freddo? Freddo? I can't talk like she
Speaker 300 (lower-pitched voice): does. Daily Freddo? She was great on the member show. If you're a member, you should go back and watch it.
She
Speaker 300 (lower-pitched voice): was great. Okay, so they went up and went to the bathroom.
Could have put
Speaker 316: anything on.
Testing, is this
Speaker 316: thing on? Last night and two previous episodes, my super chats were ignored. Something I
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): said. No, Adriana, not at all. Those were two particularly busy episodes,
and I
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): had to be a little selective. So this thing is on. It is
Speaker 332: very much on.
uh
Speaker 333 (lower-pitched voice): they all lied about tr taking shot in 4k
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): because they plan on unaliving tr soon so they can close this case with the world thinking it was
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): definitely
him so that
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): no one else can be investigated i tend to agree
i tend to
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): agree and it
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): terrifies
me afraid
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): tyler's defense is aware that tyler won't be around for long therefore they're not working hard for evidence love you b i hope that's not
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): true think
ben will tell
Speaker 286 (lower-pitched voice): her the info and collect the 10k since he likes her money so much.
Speaker 286 (lower-pitched voice): Oh, no, no.
How nervous
Speaker 107: did Candace
Speaker 19 (lower-pitched voice): look when Sean Ryan pulled out the firearm during the interview? I
was nervous for a
Speaker 19 (lower-pitched voice): second until I realized it was a gift. You must not watch a lot of Sean Ryan because he gives
a lot
Speaker 19 (lower-pitched voice): of firearms away.
Daisy rocks. Christ
Speaker 335: is king indeed. I agree, dear
Speaker 43: Jen.
And the video of
Speaker 43: Tyler on the roof. Where does it show him stop and assemble the rifle? That had to be before, I guess. I don't know. That's a good question.
Speaker 43: We were told he assembled
Speaker 91: it up there, but
I don't know either. What time did
Speaker 336: we?
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): We picked up about a full minute of him sort of making his way, I guess, before that. It
would have been
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): nice for them to back it
up and
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): show the assembly, since that's a key part of the story.
Baron, two points. The
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): ATF agent testified TRDNA was most degraded, plus they said there was dust in the barrel.
and
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): a freshly fired rifle. So Max, Christ is king indeed.
The dust
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): in the
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): barrel, I've thought about. It was stuffed in the bushes. I don't know if dust gets in a barrel in bushes. I don't know.
But yeah,
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): I've thought about that.
The most degraded,
Speaker 337 (lower-pitched voice): I'm not a DNA expert. I
heard Candace
Speaker 338 (lower-pitched voice): talking about that. I did not talk about that after I watched that evidence because I'm
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): not a DNA expert. I
don't want
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): to say something stupid.
Not
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): that she said something stupid. She may have experts she's
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): consulting with. By Baron, what would happen if TR disclosed he's a patsy
to his attorney?
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): Unfamiliar with the term until now?
Thank you
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): for your insight and hard work. They would build
a defense
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): around that.
It was someone else. I was set
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): up. That's a common defense.
lt in
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): videos
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): said tr was up early on the 11th where did he sleep the night of the 10th no discussions another timeline
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): issue keep going max
well we know he was getting
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): gas in cedar city at
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): 7 or 7
Speaker 285 (lower-pitched voice): 15 so he obviously didn't sleep at
home probably
Speaker 285 (lower-pitched voice): you know i think the story is he slept in the car on the way on the way back or pulled over and got a hotel room i don't
know but
Speaker 339: not at his house not his house
Bible in
Speaker 55 (lower-pitched voice): a Year readings today. Isaiah 520, woe to those who call evil good and good evil, who acquit the guilty for a bribe and deprive the innocent of his right.
Well, that's not Erica's
Speaker 91: Bible in a Year.
Because if
Speaker 91: so, she needs to read it. I
thought I
Speaker 91: had the answer to Ben's breakfast question,
Speaker 340 (lower-pitched voice): but it was Jay Boring having breakfast with his team. Not him. Missed $10,000. Love you both.
I
Speaker 12: thought I had the answer, too, and
I saw an
Speaker 12: interesting flight on the night of the 9th that I'm checking out
that would put him
Speaker 12: in position to
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): have a breakfast meeting that morning. So stay tuned. So thankful for you, Candace, Ian, and the others. The only way now to get the truth anywhere. Legacy Media is
Speaker 89: done. Compromised podcaster. Lying liars will lie. Thank you, Crisis King, indeed.
Speaker 285 (lower-pitched voice): Um, there are several of us out here trying to get to the truth wherever it is,
but
Speaker 318 (lower-pitched voice): yeah, I agree with you. Those, you know, thank you for putting me
in their
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): company. I still
weird to see it
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): there, uh, from YouTube for the
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): YouTube video, electrical safety and jewelry that proves necklace swings up during electrocution. I sent you an email, July 11th, subject line, electro man shows times for key moments, reduces view
time to
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): eight
Speaker 45 (lower-pitched voice): and a half minutes. Thank you for your interest.
Speaker 45 (lower-pitched voice): Uh, I am going to watch that. I have it bookmarked in my list of things to do. Um, but I don't work on Saturday, so I didn't watch it Saturday, had the prep for the show Sunday, uh, and was watching the trial prep all last week and prepping for that.
Speaker 318 (lower-pitched voice): So while Dynamo, I appreciate it. I'm not ignoring you. I do have it bookmarked. I am going
to watch it.
Speaker 318 (lower-pitched voice): Um, but it's
just a
Speaker 318 (lower-pitched voice): time priority issue,
but telling me it's
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): bookmarked and shortened is helpful.
They will
Speaker 35: have to throw a lower participant under the bus because the big dogs at the top aren't going to be caught. Lance Twiggs might be low. I
think you would struggle to
Speaker 341: convict Tyler without Lance's testimony. So
I'm not sure you can
Speaker 342: throw him
under
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): the bus.
Just
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): saying English SBI inspector and proper English spelling caliber and dialect used in text messages.
Speaker 115 (lower-pitched voice): Anyone else know that? Yes, yes, we all now know that
in a good
Speaker 115 (lower-pitched voice): way, in a good way.
Thank you.
Speaker 100: Did Sergeant McDee mention daffodil sniffing KDs? He didn't, he didn't,
but there
Speaker 35: were no daffodils to befuddle the dogs at the time. Love Daisy and her dog with
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): glasses icon, Christ is king indeed.
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): Yeah, the first time I saw that, I was like, what's that all about?
Why do you
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): have that?
And you
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): could take a
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): day a week to solely answer super chats instead of staying up late every night so everyone can still feel like they can truly connect with you. Thank you for all you guys do. That wouldn't
feel right to
Speaker 323 (lower-pitched voice): just open a show, do no content, just
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): read chats. I mean, most
of the chats I
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): respond to are things I said during the show. The early ones are not, but the later ones are almost all.
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): Uh, Loki is a demon is also a demon outside of Marvel. Oh, Loki, Loki,
Speaker 343: see father Riberger, Sean Ryan interview for one example, Loki possessing
someone love doggos,
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): but just saying,
I did not know that I
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): watched that interview, but I didn't catch the name back to Fiji water. I see Sunday show. Here's a little something
to get some more
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): mountain Valley spring. I had to go get more.
Yeah.
uh
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): thank you thank you uh keep on bringing your keen observations and intellectually honest interpretations in your philosophically consistent manner crisis gig indeed annie were you the one that bought the last box of fiji water i
had i mean of
Speaker 344 (lower-pitched voice): a mountain valley i had no idea how much it was by the box
until i went to buy a box
Speaker 340 (lower-pitched voice): and i was like whoa i'm glad somebody paid for it
uh
Speaker 345: now the Tyler's yes the Tyler's there's more than one Tyler you're adorable sometimes Bubba Baron I saw the maroon
Speaker 35: nails I predicted maroon nails as well Christ is the almighty
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): king see orange people they looked maroon
to me
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): maybe she also has seeing eye issues
AUS what is
Speaker 115 (lower-pitched voice): that
A
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): U.S. article from 12 September 2025 reported alleged gunmen heard on ring camera discussing the shooting.
Also the help
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): of an accomplice not spoken by
Speaker 158: MediaSense. You
raise a
Speaker 158: really interesting point. Daisy, we're going to have to go back and find that video. It's been buried. There
were some boys
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): that reenacted the trip out.
And one
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): of the women that was with him was
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): like, oh, is that the woman that was helping him change clothes? Yeah.
And
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): then it was like that no one ever mentioned anything else about it again. Hi, Baron. Thank you for all you do. Keep wondering why their text combo began with, did you do it? And not something more like, did you hear what happened? Love and light to you. I think it's an
Speaker 55 (lower-pitched voice): easy answer. The text conversation actually started with stop what
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): you're doing. Look under your keyboard.
Under the
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): keyboard was a purportedly a handwritten confession.
And so
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): it's not what happened to him.
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): It's he'd
already said what happened. That's that's why
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): that's that's the reason why Daisy will get the 10k on
Speaker 298: the Candace bounty. I hope so. I hope so. I hope so. I'll match it if she does. I
want to
Speaker 298: know who he was
eating breakfast
Speaker 298: with.
So if
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): the only true eyewitness to TR even being on campus that day was a TPUSA person at the tent, why wasn't that person called in as
Speaker 57: a witness? Thanks for all you do, Baron. That's a great point, Christ is King indeed. Rose, that's a phenomenal chat.
Why didn't they call that
Speaker 52: person and say, I'm the one who talked with him? It was definitely him.
You don't
Speaker 52: have to focus on grainy potato
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): quality video footage.
I saw him
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): with my own two peepers up close. Here's what he said. Great call.
Hear me
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): out on
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): BS as much as I dislike him. He's too smart to spill about CK's security communication with his own security.
Could
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): this be a distraction back to sandbox and away from the guilt of TPSA or other? What's motive? I
honestly think he has
Speaker 40: either been alerted or is
Speaker 45 (lower-pitched voice): concerned.
That
Speaker 45 (lower-pitched voice): that text message will be, I mean, that conversation will be exposed in discovery.
And it may be that
Speaker 45 (lower-pitched voice): the
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): defense has subpoenaed records and they were like, dude, that call, they've
got it. And so he just
Speaker 340 (lower-pitched voice): got out ahead of it.
Take the sting out
Speaker 340 (lower-pitched voice): of it when it's dropped.
And I see
Speaker 216: the haters in the chat. You
must be
Speaker 216: on target. Go
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): max. Also asking for prayers. My grandson, he is having surgery in the morning. God bless this community.
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): Um,
I'll pray
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): for your grandson. I
hope the
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): surgery goes well. Gosh, I hope he's not a young little feller.
Speaker 95: Actually, you texted about him the other night. Or you chatted about him the other night.
The haters in the
Speaker 95: chat. I noticed that
the
Speaker 323 (lower-pitched voice): more success the show has, the more haters show up, the more...
Speaker 346 (lower-pitched voice): We dig into certain things they don't want to face as reality. They start to attack me or the show instead of the content.
They'll pick and
Speaker 346 (lower-pitched voice): choose one little thing. Maybe one time we said it sounded a little off to them, and that's their whole day's content. It's
Speaker 347 (lower-pitched voice): very clear that there are talking points that go out to these communities, to these different creators, to these different commenters. It's like,
Speaker 348: we're fighting Candace today. Here's the talking point. She's evil. We're fighting Candace today. We're fighting Baron today. He's evil.
it's
Speaker 30: very clear um
i'll give
Speaker 30: them some material if they call me i'll tell them some things to attack
Speaker 1: me on i know more about me than
you do
Speaker 1: fort h group call soar night stalkers use maroon drone experts 917 one week after
Speaker 349: copta crash took for them
tons
Speaker 343: more info but can't
Speaker 350: send big s seeds um helicopter
crash
Speaker 351: fort huachuca
What did you
Speaker 352: say? Soar?
Speaker 297: Yeah. Oh, that was two weeks before. That was August 27th.
Oh, that was a
Speaker 297: long time ago.
I'll have to
Speaker 297: look for
Speaker 344 (lower-pitched voice): that. I'm not seeing it immediately. I'll
look into
Speaker 303: that. That's interesting. Thank you.
bear the
Speaker 303: taillights on the challenger in the garage and tyler's challenger are totally different it's not even the same model in the exhaust
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): front spoiler and taillights um i don't know that i've looked at the taillights i did look at the exhaust i did look at the front fender
uh the
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): giveaway for me was that the one in the garage did not appear at least from the terrible quality video footage we got to have a license plate holder and tyler's did front license plate holder
that was
Speaker 353: the giveaway for me
why
Speaker 341: did ek and family friends rush out of the court on day one dramatically not to view the video but then had her attorney demand they have an opportunity to view the enhanced
Speaker 354: video on the last day that's
a great
Speaker 354: question well put
Speaker 355: excellent point and the video they showed wasn't even
bad
Speaker 205 (lower-pitched voice): uh could have trained canine pick up after the human scent from a screwdriver and then trace the person's movements
if yes
Speaker 205 (lower-pitched voice): why didn't they do that i don't
Speaker 356: know i'm not a dog expert
Speaker 357: that seems
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): maybe hey
broski is someone who really
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): appreciated charlie's perspective for years it would be amazing to see
him on
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): the wall in place of disgraced trump just temporarily we sure miss him thanks for seeking
truth
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): thank you i appreciate that
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): Um, back to the screwdriver, why didn't they just,
if you
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): know, he laid down on the gravel, why not run the dog to the gravel and then chase it to the side of the building and then go back to the building and pick it up? That'd be a great question.
There's a lot,
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): there's a lot they didn't do with the dogs. They never went under the tent that I can tell.
Was it
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): there a white SUV pulled over that flashed an FBI badge that day? And a lot
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): of white SUVs were ended by officials that day. That's the rumor. I've not seen the evidence of that. I've heard about it, but I didn't see a link to it.
Yes to
Speaker 90: Candace. The writing sounds like someone whose English is second language. Vehicle, outfit, unseen. Yes, not an FBI agent. Someone
Speaker 19 (lower-pitched voice): else who doesn't speak English well. Or
who
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): speaks colonial English, meaning one of the
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): colonial countries New Zealand Australia South Africa
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): or England itself I'm sure when George Farmer read it he's
Speaker 359: like what's the problem they sound
great it
Speaker 359: sounds exactly right it sounds exactly like what he should
say aka
Speaker 360: insisting to show the evidence was
Speaker 299 (lower-pitched voice): the setup for the net slappers to perform their stories aka calling the ball more bad PR congrats be Jesus Christ is king indeed um
it
Speaker 5: seemed coordinated i'll give you that
um love the
Speaker 5: bear knight sharing their human dog names once fostered a dog at the
Speaker 361 (lower-pitched voice): shelter called david schwimmer that's unacceptable you
Speaker 362: can't name your dog after ross
uh look
Speaker 299 (lower-pitched voice): up gerard getting's photo dogs that look like their owners it's wild no pun intended oh it's
wild um you
Speaker 299 (lower-pitched voice): can't name a dog
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): david schwimmer
Remember the
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): white SUV pulled up the shopping center, waits, and then Tyler's car pulls out behind it and they leave together? Could that be the same car? I hope
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): that –
I think you
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): probably wrote that before I did. I did that segment, so I'm not going to address it because I already did that. But, yes, I think it could be.
Makes me
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): wonder if
Speaker 187 (lower-pitched voice): video behind CK was streamed to whoever was leading the op so they
could communicate to
Speaker 187 (lower-pitched voice): all the players. Maybe.
But
Speaker 187 (lower-pitched voice): Barron won't these details that you're showing come out at
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): trial. Some people think the defense was lame, but
it was just a
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): preliminary. I hope so.
I hope
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): so. If
not, they can
Speaker 363: brush up before trial and watch some episodes. Was
there a
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): white car like that in the ring camera before the bang when he was walking by the Congress Senator House in the neighborhood? Rental car.
Speaker 303: Uh...
Speaker 303: Congress, Senator House? I don't even know what house you're talking about.
I think I know
Speaker 303: what you're
Speaker 364: talking about. Oh, oh, oh, oh, you're talking about Phil Lyman. I
don't
Speaker 365: remember if there was a white white
car
Speaker 366: in the
Speaker 366: if there's
Speaker 367: a white car parked across the street or not. I don't remember. It's been so long since I've seen that video. If
so, good
Speaker 367: catch. I'll
try to find
Speaker 368: it. I'm not finding it when I'm
Speaker 369: looking real quickly. Now
all Tyler Robinson
Speaker 370 (lower-pitched voice): videos are from the trial. You can't find any. Before, if you look for Tyler Robinson walking, it was always that video. Now
it
Speaker 371: doesn't come up.
a
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): good catch they're the people who publicly claim there was clear footage in court not feel any shame no
they have
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): no shame these are these aren't
the type
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): of people who feel shame not them
looking for my little fan
Speaker 372: remote i don't see
it
Speaker 35: uh misleading people would eat me alive watching all the way from australia bless
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): you and candace and everyone involved in bringing
the truth out
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): thank you um no shame
and thank you
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): for that the
two from the
Speaker 187 (lower-pitched voice): first two clips were 2025 toyota rav4 which were also on candace's list of sketchy Rental cars.
It would be
Speaker 164: great if the car that stops and waits for the white car had car video cam and we could get the plate. Wish
Speaker 373: they watched your show. Oh,
I don't even know they
Speaker 373: still have it. That was 10 months ago.
Candace did some
Speaker 200 (lower-pitched voice): commentary about a white SUV early on in the Sir Harley Kirk investigation. If you looked at that, Christ is King indeed. I have many, many times.
More times
Speaker 297: than I can shake a stick at.
Let me pull
Speaker 297: something up here. I
have
Speaker 374 (lower-pitched voice): another question.
Speaker 374 (lower-pitched voice): place I think there was a white SUV but I can't remember
I don't want to
Speaker 375: say it out loud and then be wrong let me look
here give me just one
Speaker 376: second I'm right
here where you
Speaker 377: at little white car where you at where are you little white car here
Speaker 378: white car Oh my god, oh my god.
All
Speaker 379: right, let me look here. September 10.
There we go.
Speaker 379: No, that's
not a white
Speaker 379: car. Oh, that's September 24th.
September 10. There we go. No, that
Speaker 380: doesn't look like the same car. I don't think.
Yeah, no, that's a different
Speaker 370 (lower-pitched voice): car.
But I
Speaker 370 (lower-pitched voice): think those are the Camrys.
Speaker 168: I'll show you what I'm looking at. This is footage from the Provo Airport that week.
This is the Provo
Speaker 20 (lower-pitched voice): Airport. Remember she said there were some Toyota Camrys that had been rented? And
there was a
Speaker 381 (lower-pitched voice): Toyota 4Runner? And
then you switch to a
Speaker 381 (lower-pitched voice): different angle.
Speaker 381 (lower-pitched voice): and the Camrys are
Speaker 383: there still. Two of the Camrys are there, but not the other one. You can't see
Speaker 374 (lower-pitched voice): it from that angle. I do think those were the cars she said were rented, and they
Speaker 384: were at the airport
at Duncan
Speaker 374 (lower-pitched voice): Aviation. If
you remember her
Speaker 385: talking about that months ago.
The
Speaker 187 (lower-pitched voice): Great Car Chase seems like a screening of Bullet starring Steve McQueen. The cars in that movie were used throughout its eight-minute car chase. I don't
know what you're
Speaker 386: talking about. God bless you and yours. I appreciate that.
Christ is
Speaker 386: king indeed. I know what that means.
Are there any cars
Speaker 338 (lower-pitched voice): the same as we saw stop to talk to Tyler when
he was
Speaker 338 (lower-pitched voice): walking around town in the morning? I
can't tell if you wrote that
Speaker 68: before I did my segment because that's
what I was trying
Speaker 344 (lower-pitched voice): to show.
Oh,
Speaker 344 (lower-pitched voice): you're saying when he, the other stuff, I don't know. I have to go back and look. I didn't have that ready.
Google claims
Speaker 95: the Google trends we discussed were artificial data fluctuations. Of course they did. No, they were not.
Also looks like trend
Speaker 95: data was
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): scrubbed. Is this just more slop? Do the trends still hold water? They do if you can use the old Google trends tool. But yeah, they no doubt changed it. That's why
Speaker 387 (lower-pitched voice): we're going to go back in time. Okay.
And
Speaker 387 (lower-pitched voice): we'll do a Google Trends recap at some point, but we can't do it right now.
Speaker 78 (lower-pitched voice): Video, when the alleged Tyler turns and looks at the white car, he has a different shoes than the great covers. Oh, really?
Is that so? Let me
Speaker 388: see. Oh, that's tomorrow. You
already have
Speaker 388: tomorrow's run open?
Daisy's on
Speaker 36 (lower-pitched voice): the ball.
Speaker 389: Wow.
Speaker 36 (lower-pitched voice): Uh, let me
Speaker 390 (lower-pitched voice): go back and look at the, which one did you say video when he led turns and looks at the, I don't know which one you're talking about turns to the white car.
Oh, I think that's just
Speaker 391: artificial. I think it's just the lighting. I don't think, I don't
think you can tell
Speaker 370 (lower-pitched voice): those are different shoes. Uh,
but I'll look
Speaker 370 (lower-pitched voice): more into that when I
Speaker 170: have time. Thank you.
when
Speaker 170: the canine dogs pick up the scent of the alleged explosives on campus that day, if they were near the explosives, that's
Speaker 90: the thing is every image we have, every video we have of the dogs, they were so far away from the tent that
Speaker 47: you don't know. It would have ruled it out, right? It
would have
Speaker 47: been a great thing to just run them through the tent and rule it out.
So do we
Speaker 47: know if it was an advanced evidence dog or a bomb dog that took out that day? If
it was an
Speaker 47: evidence, no, they, they, they used every dog. If you,
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): if that's why I played that first radio thing, we have all dogs coming to your location. Every
dog in
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): the counties on the way.
Don't forget about the
Speaker 43: white SUV speeding off. It got pulled over driver flashes badge. It was let go of a passenger in the front seat. Yeah. I just addressed that a second
Speaker 21: ago. I, I don't, I've never
seen a
Speaker 21: link to that. I just heard about it. I don't even remember where I heard it.
Did you
Speaker 43: really just low-key throw shade at us baby boomers? I am more hip than you think might be. Oh, I no doubt you are, Kay the
Speaker 13: Patriot. I
would never
Speaker 30: say that about you.
I was talking
Speaker 30: about the other ones.
Not
Speaker 21: you. No. Are those same cars? The airport transponders. White one, maybe. That's what I just looked at. I hope you're still looking. I just showed that. When Cam Race was taught. Cam Race? Oh, Candace. Talking about
her
Speaker 392: dreams early on.
Speaker 392: Taking her kids out of school in B's. How many B's? Two B's? A B and a B? B-B? Christ is king, dude.
Speaker 345: I don't know. I don't know.
Why would he
Speaker 345: drop the gun off if it was in his car as he drove off in?
The same
Speaker 345: car that got impounded.
I don't know what that
Speaker 345: means.
Speaker 370 (lower-pitched voice): I think the story is that he jumps off the roof. He stashes the gun with the intent to come back later because he has a little walk back to his car. And then we'll walk through town with a gun in his hand.
Speaker 370 (lower-pitched voice): that's my understanding but i don't know
nice trim
Speaker 393: shorter hair ultra focus edge i did
Speaker 15 (lower-pitched voice): not get a haircut
what you see is what
Speaker 15 (lower-pitched voice): you saw yesterday i
did take an earlier
Speaker 394: shower today usually i'm like jumping out of the shower to run in
here and i took a
Speaker 395: shower a couple
hours early today
Speaker 395: so maybe that's what you see is just drier
uh
Speaker 343: just a suggestion i think we
Speaker 361 (lower-pitched voice): should refer to the guy in the stairwell parking garage and the pixel figure on the roof is
tyler but
Speaker 361 (lower-pitched voice): that's why i said tyler's he's been hasn't been he's not been positively identified as tyler congrats on the top 25 thank you miss ang i um i try to i tried to to solve that by saying the tyler's it's any one of the tyler's what
were the vehicles
Speaker 361 (lower-pitched voice): we saw at quick
Speaker 396: quack i swear there was a white suv but could be incorrect i shouldn't have closed the map down
Speaker 396: I'll look again. I'll look again. If
I
Speaker 397: can find it.
Quick
Speaker 399: quack. Coming right up. Quick quack Orem, Utah. Except
I think
Speaker 400: there are two and I don't remember which one it is. It's
not
Speaker 401: that one. I
think it's that
Speaker 401: one. Let
me
Speaker 402: look at the other one.
Quick
Speaker 403: quack.
Speaker 388: Oh, man, there's a bunch of
Speaker 404: them. Oh, no, there's just two. No,
it was
Speaker 404: that one. No, which one was it?
I'm all
Speaker 405: confused now.
Hold on. No, it was the first
Speaker 62: one.
Speaker 406: Hold, please. Hold, please. Here
Speaker 62: we go.
Speaker 407: Yeah, it was this one. I
think it
Speaker 408: was this one.
Speaker 388: Oh, that's 24th. I was like, I don't
see a
Speaker 388: white SUV. Oh, there's
Speaker 409: a white... Is that the same kind of car?
Let me...
Speaker 116: Oh, there's a couple here. Let me share with you. That's a good call. Good catch. You
guys are
Speaker 116: smart tonight. Not
that
Speaker 36 (lower-pitched voice): you're not usually. Not the point. So we have a white SUV here. I
Speaker 297: can't see enough of it.
We've
Speaker 297: got one here. That looks like a Tesla, actually. But
we also have
Speaker 367: one over here.
It looks a
Speaker 367: lot like it.
Even has the
Speaker 367: black wheels.
That was
Speaker 410: before. This, keep in mind, this was taken before. This isn't after. So
I don't know that
Speaker 317 (lower-pitched voice): it's of much value.
unless they
Speaker 291: were like partying at the quick quackle.
That's not that same GMC
Speaker 411: truck, is it? GMC, is that it? No. Does
that look like
Speaker 411: it?
Speaker 412: It
looks like it to
Speaker 412: me.
i'll have to double check
Speaker 5: i'm leaving that pulled up sure for sure uh thank you that was a nice
Speaker 413: little jaunt um i'll check that out
dogs couldn't
Speaker 414: smell anything over the mountain of bull butter being pushed around uh dogs are
Speaker 187 (lower-pitched voice): pretty talented
Speaker 187 (lower-pitched voice): There's another missing minute of UVU surveillance
Speaker 19 (lower-pitched voice): footage that I don't think you've covered. It's from 1215.58 to 1217.03. And the other parking lot roof bid, I bet they cut out video of red, of car
Speaker 52: circling. Potentially, I don't know.
Did I
Speaker 52: not catch that one? I'll go back and look. Thank you.
And you guys all
Speaker 52: on the payroll.
Feeding me
Speaker 52: all day.
And I'm confused. You
Speaker 187 (lower-pitched voice): previously covered all these cars. You also saw a car stopped in an empty lot near doorbell.
Cam
Speaker 187 (lower-pitched voice): footage where Tyler walked down
Speaker 43: the street you thought was suspicious. I didn't previously cover the white SUV stopping, waiting for the timing, and then driving off suspiciously at speed. No, I didn't cover that car because we didn't have that footage.
In fact, it was
Speaker 90: selectively
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): cut, I believe, so that we wouldn't see that car doing that because we would have 10 months to sit around and say, why'd that car stop?
Because that's
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): suspicious as
Speaker 361 (lower-pitched voice): hell.
I mean,
Speaker 89: that is really bad.
Yeah.
Also
Speaker 89: possible the white car from Zach Costello's analysis dropped off that plainclothes guy that met Officer Bagley. You're right.
He could
Speaker 415: have. I
hadn't thought of that
Speaker 302: either. Tyler's phone's still in evidence. His lawyer needs to go get the timestamps off the text. Swipe left. Lawyer, swipe left.
Get them all. Nice
Speaker 187 (lower-pitched voice): work, BC. Nice work, you.
Baron, like I
Speaker 187 (lower-pitched voice): said months ago, I believe the SUV pulled up to TR to remind him to limp.
While
Speaker 89: walking down the street, he wasn't limping before the SUV pulled up beside him.
Yeah, he
Speaker 89: wasn't, but I always attributed that to him going downhill a little bit, but, you know,
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): maybe. Also, the high-def influencer lies were so egregious, I honestly thought it was satire or AI. They have no shame. So morally bankrupt and deeply
Speaker 95: dishonest. Agreed,
Speaker 47: agreed, agreed.
On all
Speaker 47: counts. Agreed.
So if
Speaker 47: you look at the SUV, he stopped because a golf cart that was coming around and you immediately see the golf cart after he ends
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): up taking off again,
coming down
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): the sidewalk on that same side he was driving from.
Pull it up one more time and look
Speaker 416 (lower-pitched voice): yet again, because I don't
know that I
Speaker 416 (lower-pitched voice): agree with you yet, but we will watch
Speaker 417: together, shall we, folks? Ladies and gentlemen,
I'm
Speaker 418: being challenged.
Here we
Speaker 390 (lower-pitched voice): have the car turning in. Let me turn the volume off again. Here we have the car turning in. Where is the golf cart?
Where's the golf
Speaker 419: cart? He
stopped in the middle of
Speaker 419: the road. I see no golf cart.
Still
Speaker 420: waiting.
For a
Speaker 124: golf cart. No golf cart visible.
I see
Speaker 124: no golf carting.
Ixnay on
Speaker 421: the off-cart gay.
Where's the golf cart? I was
Speaker 70: promised there would be a golf cart.
Am I looking at
Speaker 422: a different video?
it must
Speaker 298: be a different video. I apologize. That's the one that is the most suspicious to me.
I'll
Speaker 45 (lower-pitched voice): have to go back and check the others. Seems there are multiple red herrings that are set up to mask the actual crime. The Fed
Speaker 89: picks the one that they thought people would buy. That's
Speaker 423: what I was saying.
They
Speaker 89: had a plan A, a plan B, maybe a plan C. They had lots of different things going on depending on which plan they needed to execute. And Tyler got whatever
Speaker 341: plan he got.
Both the
Speaker 341: white SUV and that small black
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): hatchback were in the lot when Tyler jumped and when he was getting waiting by the stairs, not just the white SUV. Black
Speaker 424: hatchback SUV. I
Speaker 407: don't see it.
I don't see it. Thank
Speaker 299 (lower-pitched voice): you.
Speaker 299 (lower-pitched voice): Barron, I love you, but I would say Candace's nails are coral.
In case you haven't
Speaker 187 (lower-pitched voice): confirmed, as your previously self-titled Australian correspondent, I'm 99% certain Hull is an Aussie in your humble
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): opinion. Keep going, Max, love you. Love you more, and I am willing to accept that. He
sounds
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): Aussie-ish. I
didn't hear him
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): say mate, so I don't know.
i didn't
Speaker 204: hear him say i don't know knife this is a knife and then i would have really known why
are you relying on granny
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): footage if the driver of the white suv had a clear view of the tyler climbing down the building where's that witness it's
a good question good
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): question lindsey
Speaker 39: graham is looking up at us right now oh me
probably right but
Speaker 39: let's not talk ill
Speaker 43: of the dead
We
Speaker 43: should go back to the map, satellite footage, before the event. Look for the SUV. Oh, that's
what I
Speaker 43: just did. That's what I
Speaker 425: just did.
Could
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): those SUVs possibly be related to the one Candace mentioned
a while back related to the
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): Egyptian
Speaker 187 (lower-pitched voice): planes? They certainly could be. They look like Toyota RAV4s.
Same black-gray car
Speaker 187 (lower-pitched voice): that is following behind the white
Speaker 363: car in the second video also appears to be in the first video, passing by the white car, going the opposite way when the blob is running across the roof.
Speaker 426: okay
Speaker 427: same one going past the second or i
Speaker 103 (lower-pitched voice): don't i i'm very confused i don't remember which ones i played in what order oh
there's the
Speaker 417: black suv i see
Speaker 78 (lower-pitched voice): that
Is
Speaker 428: that also a RAV4? Here, you tell me. I don't know. Oh, I didn't mean to hit that.
Ah. Sorry,
Speaker 429: guys. Hit
a
Speaker 245: button and it screwed everything up.
I'd pull
Speaker 245: it back
up.
I
Speaker 430: don't... Let me pull this up
because I
Speaker 430: want you guys to see and see if this is also a RAV4.
There it goes. Is this
Speaker 432: also a RAV4? Try
not to hit
Speaker 431: the wrong button this time. I
can't
Speaker 433: tell if that is or not.
It
Speaker 433: doesn't look like one necessarily. Is
that
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): the SUV you're talking about? Black gray SUV car falling behind the white car in
the second
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): video. Also appears to be in the first video,
Speaker 344 (lower-pitched voice): passing by
the white
Speaker 344 (lower-pitched voice): car, going the opposite way when the blob is running across the roof.
Okay, so
Speaker 344 (lower-pitched voice): now we've got to go to
Speaker 416 (lower-pitched voice): blob running.
Okay, here's the car
Speaker 416 (lower-pitched voice): coming in.
And you're saying it's going to turn
Speaker 381 (lower-pitched voice): in behind it, I guess?
let's
Speaker 381 (lower-pitched voice): speed it ahead so
it starts moving
Speaker 78 (lower-pitched voice): because you said it's passing this car oh there it
Speaker 391: is no it's got different wheels I think I think it does
maybe maybe they had two
Speaker 434: pickups planned
that really does
Speaker 390 (lower-pitched voice): look like it now that you mention it hold on let's see if let's watch it turn all the
way through it'll be closer over
Speaker 390 (lower-pitched voice): on this side
Speaker 417: We'll
be
Speaker 435: right
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): back.
Speaker 416 (lower-pitched voice): assuming we see it turn through.
That's
Speaker 417: speeding up down the parking lot's a dead giveaway. That's not... Oh, no, that car's red.
That car's red. That wasn't black at all. Yeah, we tried. We
Speaker 436: tried. We try so hard here.
Curious
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): about the side-by-side that came from the sidewalk while the blur leaped. Looked intentional.
We had
Speaker 158: authorization to operate these side-by-side that day. Yeah, I saw that as well, and it did. It was in that
Speaker 382: video we just
Speaker 158: played. I
don't know. Were the 12
Speaker 187 (lower-pitched voice): to 13 SUVs that were rented from the airport per the FBI or who? Was there anything else discovered about the rentals and the Israeli phones? I didn't think
it was
Speaker 187 (lower-pitched voice): 12 or 13. I thought it was six total
Speaker 374 (lower-pitched voice): vehicles, maybe. Five or six. I don't know who rented them. And I don't know about the Israeli phones.
Plan
Speaker 374 (lower-pitched voice): B would explain why some men in the crowd kept repeating two shots
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): to the students running away. Maybe they didn't know which plan to go with. Oh, good call.
Hey, Barron, what
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): are the chances Tyler or someone that looked like him shot a
Speaker 361 (lower-pitched voice): blank from the roof? This would explain the gunshot sound.
I mean,
Speaker 361 (lower-pitched voice): it's possible. I don't know. I
don't know the
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): answer to that.
It
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): wasn't Candace trying to find a white SUV that looked very similar to the one Candace was looking for linked to the plane.
I think
Speaker 78 (lower-pitched voice): she was. Maybe that'll be it. 30-06 is used to hunt buffalo,
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): too. They're huge, that poor guy. I
have no
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): idea what's up with Kalispell.
Speaker 361 (lower-pitched voice): Flathead Lake is popular, like Lake Tahoe. I don't know. Yeah, maybe they're just vacationers. They like to vacation a lot.
A, B,
Speaker 95: please check the 12, 15, 30 mark in the security footage from campus. There's a white SUV passing by when the person rolls over
Speaker 370 (lower-pitched voice): the wall. I'd
have to
Speaker 370 (lower-pitched voice): go find that. I can't find that on the fly because I
Speaker 437: don't have that with me.
But I
Speaker 438: will
Speaker 437: look. Now that you've mentioned it, I'll go back and find it and look.
If the gun was in
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): Tyler Robinson's pant leg, would
it be
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): covered with his DNA rather than a little bit on the trigger? That's a good call.
That's a good,
Speaker 89: again.
Speaker 89: I don't know what
they tested
Speaker 89: video on the IG nine 10 recorded by Erica
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): of her and Charlie
was removed
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): same day. They stayed together at the
Speaker 270: dorm
the night
Speaker 270: before. Can't find it anywhere. Ideas they'd together in a dorm night before nine 10.
I've never heard of that. Congrats on making
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): the top 25. I said it to you privately.
so why
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): pay to say it again so that
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): i can say it publicly that the only reason you beat me by so much is because you're so handsome and how's the guy supposed to compete congrats
Speaker 90: stud well earned that's jesse on fire the real
jesse on
Speaker 90: fire thank you i appreciate that i genuinely appreciate that um
i saw
Speaker 90: jesse's stuff
Speaker 361 (lower-pitched voice): on spotify too good platform good platform they've been good partners so
go check jesse
Speaker 361 (lower-pitched voice): out as well he told me he
Speaker 439: was going to stream tonight if so you guys should jump over there when you're done.
Speaker 439: um i'll
look and see if
Speaker 439: he puts up a
Speaker 370 (lower-pitched voice): time um a
while ago i
Speaker 187 (lower-pitched voice): recall someone mentioning a white rav suv pulled over by local pdf to the bang fbi badge something commented on yeah
i just don't remember um
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): where it came from i do remember the discussion but i can't remember is it somebody said they talked to somebody or was there a
story about it
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): i i need some kind
of
Speaker 19 (lower-pitched voice): link to pull up to look at it again because i don't remember
where
Speaker 19 (lower-pitched voice): it came from baron do you think that charlie played both sides and told canis one thing and aka something else
she said he
Speaker 187 (lower-pitched voice): was a maestro remember how he was careful criticizing oga but told tc to go max
love
Speaker 440: you my b um well
and i know candace said
Speaker 440: she caught
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): him lying to her once
But to
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): believe what you just said, you'd have to believe it was an ongoing, continual, years-long liescapade. I made up a new word there. And
I just don't
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): believe he's like a continual two-faced liar. I just don't.
Please pray
Speaker 19 (lower-pitched voice): for Parkersburg. Our community spent a
Speaker 111 (lower-pitched voice): week under the smoke of a massive chemical fire, breathing toxic air. While
many of us
Speaker 111 (lower-pitched voice): felt information was limited and questions went unanswered. Parkersburg?
What's going on
Speaker 111 (lower-pitched voice): in Parkersburg?
Where is
Speaker 441: Parker? A
warehouse
Speaker 442: fire, I see.
Speaker 443: Interesting.
Fire reported
Speaker 444: again this morning. Oh, that was two days. Well,
I hope you're doing better
Speaker 444: now. I
hope you're doing better
Speaker 444: now. I hope they got that thing. Oh,
Speaker 45 (lower-pitched voice): that looks nasty. I just saw some pictures of it. Big, thick cloud.
uh
Speaker 45 (lower-pitched voice): 25 looks good on you sir
Speaker 89: explains the haircut got a show for the cameras correct why do you guys think i have a haircut oh it's edge again edge i did not get a haircut
i might need one but i did not
Speaker 89: get one but thank you
for the
Speaker 89: compliment found out yesterday my daughter's god sister gets 1200 a month from turning point to keep the chapter going at her
school she opened
Speaker 242: it after the big bang 1200 a month what i'm taking a picture
of
Speaker 445: I, that is impossible for me to, $1,200 a month. No.
Speaker 396: TR also
interacts
Speaker 147: with white car after limping through parking tunnel, walks the stairs, car pulls up acknowledgement,
goes
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): upstairs, taps earbud car leaves.
i have to go
Speaker 89: back and look at that i didn't catch that
uh her
Speaker 89: flights must might be paid by the government she was appointed to that air force position to replace charlie no no
the
Speaker 285 (lower-pitched voice): board of visitors is like an honorary position i don't think they're
Speaker 446: certainly not flying around on the taxpayer dime doesn't that wind dude
live in
Speaker 446: las vegas maybe the plane was taking him home i
mean he
Speaker 447: does Yes.
Miriam Adelson lives
Speaker 447: in Las Vegas. That means she does. Hi, Barron, if only we knew someone from the FBI who would
need to
Speaker 447: fly
Speaker 90: to Vegas after the flights from D.C. and Montana. Oh, wait, it's cash money. I think he's prohibited from flying
on other private
Speaker 90: planes except his FBI plane. I think is the rule. I'm not sure how that works.
why tr go
Speaker 90: out of his way to pick go back into the garage when returning on foot with the rifle bottle up the stairs in front of students and cameras just get back on the
Speaker 100: sidewalk only
reason i can
Speaker 100: think of is for photo shoot that's a really good point because it's hard
Speaker 305: to climb stairs on a rifle with
a rifle why
Speaker 305: don't you just walk around that's a great question let me look at the map of uvu real quick
i tell you what this is why
Speaker 448: they don't like this show
this is
Speaker 448: why they don't like this show. We've
Speaker 32: gotten more good tips tonight than they've gotten
Speaker 297: in 10 months. All
Speaker 449: right, let's look here.
Speaker 450: Yeah, just walk
on the
Speaker 450: sidewalk. Why would you go back up the side?
Wait a
Speaker 439: minute. Am I missing something here? Oh,
let me get
Speaker 439: on the street view.
okay
Speaker 439: walk through there got it got it
yeah why do
Speaker 439: you walk back to the parking garage
Speaker 451: hold on look with
me here this is a
Speaker 297: great point so tyler comes out here-ish uh
Speaker 37: no i'm sorry he comes out up here
he walks up these
Speaker 37: stairs right here oh this is a tunnel so he walks through this tunnel here
and
Speaker 37: then he comes out oh oh that's
Speaker 344 (lower-pitched voice): why because he came out into the garage because he used the tunnel he'd
have had
Speaker 344 (lower-pitched voice): to walk around and
and oh sorry you
Speaker 344 (lower-pitched voice): zipped all over
the place i think
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): he had to if he used that tunnel i think he has to go
back up up
Speaker 452: through the
garage maybe it's not
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): as cut and
dry as
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): we thought um
but
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): good good point made us look uh
shy king
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): baron
How can
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): you not put two and two together? She had to stop by the FBI spots to
Speaker 361 (lower-pitched voice): recalibre, download her empathic, sad personality. I
don't know why I
Speaker 361 (lower-pitched voice): didn't think of that. I forgot. She had to recharge her batteries. My
boss and
Speaker 361 (lower-pitched voice): I love what you all are doing for
Speaker 453 (lower-pitched voice): Charlie. We watch daily. What is the time difference between when the three cars were in the parking lot and when the guy was jumping off the roof?
Three cars were in
Speaker 317 (lower-pitched voice): the parking lot
and the
Speaker 317 (lower-pitched voice): time guy was jumping. I don't know what you're asking.
I
Speaker 317 (lower-pitched voice): would love to answer that, but I don't know if you're asking. Three cars were in the parking lot, the guy
jumping off
Speaker 317 (lower-pitched voice): the roof.
I don't know what you're
Speaker 317 (lower-pitched voice): asking. I played the video, so however long that took, that's the time difference. If it's that video, I mean,
Speaker 338 (lower-pitched voice): just run it back and watch it and count,
if that's what
Speaker 338 (lower-pitched voice): you're talking about.
I
Speaker 454: don't know what three cars you're talking about.
Speaker 338 (lower-pitched voice): Ogden is a small regional airport, but it's only a few miles outside of Hill Air Force Base, a very
Speaker 43: large base. My dad and husband worked there. Ogden is a small, cool, boho town. I've been to Ogden,
believe it
Speaker 43: or not.
I met a guy
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): that was potentially going to be a client. He never ended up being a client. Well, actually, he did
Speaker 19 (lower-pitched voice): sort of end up being a client.
Not for what he was
Speaker 19 (lower-pitched voice): asking me about then, but later, I think he hired me for a couple of days.
and
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): so i flew to ogden actually i flew to salt lake stayed there and then drove up to ogden the next day and met him
there in a
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): little
Speaker 455: diner it
was nice i don't
Speaker 456: even remember
what
Speaker 455: year it
Speaker 91: was
2020 oh it was
Speaker 91: covid yeah it was a covid year 2020 uh erica's cls speech recent
i can play
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): take a plane to to be here after all i've been through hell this week it's not easy again one more speech your way.
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): Yeah, I thought that was a kind of a bad line because her plane costs more than those kids are going to make their first five years out of college. I
was there on
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): 910 at UVU and I had a voicemail save from the FBI agent asking me for any video or imaging that could
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): help. Contacted me by my license plate. So the cameras are good enough to get mine, just not Tyler's go max. Wow.
Speaker 47: Duly noted. That's
a good
Speaker 47: tip there. Thank you.
This was
Speaker 47: the worst op
Speaker 35: ever.
They couldn't
Speaker 35: pull it off. Exposed them all. Crisis King, go max. Don't slow down. Keep draining the swamp. They can't see how fake and gay they all come across to us. Normies. I
think they're getting desperate
Speaker 457: too. They
had a
Speaker 298: bad week. Twig sounds like Noam Chomsky.
Okay.
Speaker 458: Like 70 years younger.
Baron YouTube randomly suggested a video
Speaker 459: titled Getting Help from Uncle Sam. Baron Coleman News and Views. It was amazing.
That
Speaker 459: was young, fat, alcoholic
Speaker 460: baron. Don't watch that guy. I
don't even know what year
Speaker 461: that was.
That had to be 10 or 12
Speaker 320: years ago or more.
That's okay,
Speaker 462 (lower-pitched voice): though. That
wasn't the
Speaker 462 (lower-pitched voice): healthiest baron you've ever seen. I have no idea
why it
Speaker 462 (lower-pitched voice): does that. Every now and
then it
Speaker 462 (lower-pitched voice): pushes that video out.
I think
Speaker 462 (lower-pitched voice): someone finds it, sends it
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): around to a few people, so it gets a few hits, and YouTube goes, oh, people want
to see
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): this, and they start sending it to everybody's feed.
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): Would TRs, lawyers, be working other cases at the same time? Do you think they have enough resources to find all of this? Can't envision them
Speaker 192 (lower-pitched voice): digging this hard. I
almost
Speaker 285 (lower-pitched voice): assuredly believe they have
Speaker 387 (lower-pitched voice): other cases going at the same time. You
can take an
Speaker 387 (lower-pitched voice): antifungal for that. I'll
laugh for five
Speaker 463: minutes. Be right back late watching Candida. I
Speaker 464: mean,
you can. Lance
Speaker 298: Twig said he didn't hear from TR because he didn't.
Speaker 298: Because it was the feds who
Speaker 2: texted him. Oh, maybe he's intuitive. In
New Zealand
Speaker 2: or Australia, when someone
Speaker 345: throws a kiss via chat, they type moi, moi. I've never seen an American type that. The cop has a weird British accent. I've
never seen an American type
Speaker 83: that either. In fact, I didn't know what it was. I
had to like
Speaker 83: think about
Speaker 87: it. Mua, mua? I had no idea what they were talking about at first. And
then I
Speaker 87: was like, oh, moi, moi. I
did not
Speaker 87: know that was an
Speaker 1: Australian thing.
Speaker 1: Maybe Detective Hull needs a little closer eyeball.
Is that the car
Speaker 1: that stopped
in the
Speaker 1: middle of the road? Sorry
if you
Speaker 1: already covered it, saying this as I'm watching.
Speaker 465: Christ is king indeed. I did not cover it because it is not the same car. That was a Kia Soul.
But good
Speaker 465: catch. Good memory. Good memory. That was months ago.
Judge Graff,
Speaker 147: is there any footage, pause, of the awkward
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): stutter? Alleged shooting. Is that normal to refer to it as alleged by the judge? No. No.
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): No, it's
Speaker 90: not. Blake Snaff and his ex live conversation said we stayed until the 11th. Who is we? I wonder. Thank
you for all
Speaker 90: the work you put in, Baron. Bring joy to our day. Ave
Speaker 15 (lower-pitched voice): Maria. I strongly suspect Danny Phillip was one of the we. And it might have just been Danny and Blake. Or
there could have been a
Speaker 466: third person staying with them.
Don't know who that could
Speaker 467: have been.
Apologies
Speaker 467: if you've already covered this, but LT was given immunity.
Speaker 89: Immunity from what? That's a good question.
Because there
Speaker 89: was no admission that I could tell in there to any crime. Now, it could be that the judge, I mean, the lawyer just wanted to be extra cautious and didn't know what all
Speaker 374 (lower-pitched voice): would come up or what his client would blurt out. So
he just
Speaker 374 (lower-pitched voice): asked for transactional immunity on that statement just to be careful. But I didn't hear
him
Speaker 55 (lower-pitched voice): admit to a crime, I don't think.
Speaker 55 (lower-pitched voice): busy Montana weekend, Air Force Two in Butte, Bill Clinton, former
Speaker 90: Secretary of State, Anthony Blinken, and U.S. Senator Adam Schiff in Big
Speaker 333 (lower-pitched voice): Timba, all within one and a half hours of Bozeman. Wow, busy
Montana
Speaker 442: weekend. Where's Butte? Butte, Montana.
All right, I see
Speaker 442: Butte
Speaker 343: there. Uh-huh, Butte. Oh.
just
Speaker 396: about 20, 30 miles away from Dillon and Bozeman. Was
the Veep nearby
Speaker 469: for a particular
Speaker 470: reason?
Good
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): question. And
when Tyler
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): is dressed in black about to go on up the stairs, he steps to the left as if someone made
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): contact with him.
When he
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): continues up, he looks back, and the great car can be seen behind him. They were watching him. I agree. They were watching. That's fine. I think those cars were related, at least one of them.
The whole
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): thing looks highly
Speaker 164: suspicious. Then we look at things, the more we look at things, the more it don't make sense. Our humble principal knew this
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): months ago. Yo, Blakey Neff, where were you? This whole thing is a pile of poo.
Well, that rhymed. That's a
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): good
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): point.
So
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): fake and gay, they should have cut their losses. First one
Speaker 89: to the lawyer gets the best deal. I'm sure Trump will give y'all pardons. Give up. Trump cannot pardon people from a Utah state crime. Keep that in mind.
Everything else you
Speaker 89: said is true. I've tried everything to match the letters on the burnt
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): paper to note.
Not
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): happening. I'll drop it on your X to see if anyone else can get it. In my opinion, fake.
Match it to
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): what? I don't know what you're asking.
Oh, to the note. Oh.
match the
Speaker 453 (lower-pitched voice): letters on the burnt paper to the note. I see what you're saying. The paper's not the same as the note. Yeah,
let me know. Let me know how that
Speaker 453 (lower-pitched voice): turns out.
I'm
Speaker 359: waiting on the edge of
Speaker 90: my seat. I've got bated breath.
I super
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): chat you on Friday. The Ben S is involved. After CO show tonight, the more, are you more open-minded to that theory? Just started watching you and you do good work. I'm...
i'm
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): fair daisy's not
on right
Speaker 343: now i was gonna have
Speaker 471: her correct me
Speaker 343: if i'm wrong i'm fairly confident we covered that ben shapiro video monday
or tuesday uh
Speaker 343: i don't
Speaker 100: remember honestly i think we did and i think i said it was suspicious as hell and that i'm rethinking his involvement but i'd have to go back and watch the show i say so much
Speaker 472: stuff i
was
Speaker 243: thinking that
but i didn't say it
Speaker 243: i thought it
uh good
Speaker 243: catch and welcome to the program thank you
What
Speaker 243: 20-year-old has a monitor and keyboard? Don't they have laptops? A
lot of the
Speaker 361 (lower-pitched voice): gamers like the traditional setup.
Like I have a
Speaker 361 (lower-pitched voice): racing simulator that won't run on a laptop. You have
to have a
Speaker 361 (lower-pitched voice): tower. I
don't know if
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): this is universal for tower or not, but it is now.
It is
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): now. 5% of the world is truly evil. 5% actively fights the evil. 90% are just sheep. Appreciate you being part of the 5% on the right side
of
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): right.
Can
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): I adjust your percentages ever so slightly? Because I think it's more like 25% is evil.
I think it's
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): more like 2% or 3% are fighting that 25%. And everybody else is complicit in the evil because they're not fighting
it. Regarding stairs
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): video. Students, hi, Charlie. Love you, Charlie. Then Charlie Kirk, thank you. Thank you. Just using the restroom. I'll be right back. Okay. I didn't listen to the audio.
I should
Speaker 45 (lower-pitched voice): have.
why
Speaker 45 (lower-pitched voice): does he take nine people up with him to the bathroom? What are they doing in there?
What are
Speaker 45 (lower-pitched voice): they, women?
Powdering
Speaker 287: their noses? You
guys still
Speaker 287: powder noses?
That was always a trope in
Speaker 328 (lower-pitched voice): the movies in the 80s and 90s. I got to go powder my nose. I've never
heard a woman
Speaker 328 (lower-pitched voice): say that.
Nor do I
Speaker 328 (lower-pitched voice): know if
Speaker 177 (lower-pitched voice): they do powder their noses, I guess. I don't know.
Speaker 177 (lower-pitched voice): uh
Speaker 43: oh sorry have you compared the note to the lettering on the bullets whenever shows any resemblance um i didn't even try because
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): writing with a dremel now
it's not
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): going to be like handwriting it's
Speaker 318 (lower-pitched voice): like it's grinding
bumping
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): and grinding uh lance said tyler asked for the dremel about a month before but didn't show in text
how long
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): he was planning it
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): and tyler said a
week
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): could they be graving bullets a month before if they planned a week before?
Speaker 473: Well,
not entirely
Speaker 473: accurate. He
Speaker 323 (lower-pitched voice): said it was in the last month, and I did stop and make the point that the whole show, the whole shebang was only announced like a week and a half before it happened. So I'll give you
a little
Speaker 328 (lower-pitched voice): credit there and just
a gentle correction
Speaker 328 (lower-pitched voice): on it.
uh got
Speaker 299 (lower-pitched voice): my rbp merch today
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): christ is king indeed long sleeve t black high iq outfit women's t and the stunning intellectually
honest
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): philosophically consistent t where the proudly keep going max thank
you it
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): is stunning if i do say so myself hey b where
is the
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): fur they want us to believe the charade at least
Speaker 345: make him wear the costume that's a good point
that's what he
Speaker 345: should have Ask them now.
Mr. Twigs, we
Speaker 386: appreciate all your testimony at this point. One last question.
Speaker 474: Tiger. Lion. Chihuahua.
Speaker 102: What are you, sir? I got to know. I'm insanely curious. No, it has nothing to do with the case. I just, man to
Speaker 326: man, or whatever you are.
Man to
Speaker 326: creature.
Speaker 91: Oh, sorry.
Speaker 91: regarding trammel don't let it go off in the house not be careful
Speaker 345: with your precious life yeah don't mess up
the couch
Speaker 345: you know what's a couch cost uh
man you're
Speaker 345: the feds worst nightmare i
would like to not land on
Speaker 298: the radar
lance said i don't know when
Speaker 298: he specifically asked me
Speaker 153: to engrave the bullets yes that's correct uh
what's that philly
Speaker 153: software called toka lance's testimony Thank you.
I don't
Speaker 476: even think they need that. They just need some
Speaker 19 (lower-pitched voice): sort of like the AI software or something, you know, where they can make you sound and say whatever.
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): We did the whole analysis, or Candace did a great job with the analysis of the different companies that do it when she did the
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): Charlie announcement of Erica.
Super easy
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): stuff, man.
Speaker 47: And his lips did not move. And I'm telling you right now,
Speaker 47: There's a whole cottage industry of depositions and videotaped depositions. These are professionals. You don't
Speaker 266: have to put a camera on your Zoom.
Baron, at this point, what
Speaker 187 (lower-pitched voice): does support the Fed slot? Is there anything that does support TR with a 30-06 on the low C center, pulling the trigger, unaliving CK, Christ is king,
Speaker 47: and Giyawa.
Give it a
Speaker 47: whirl.
Is
Speaker 47: that what that means?
Give it a whirl? I
Speaker 477: don't know how I got that. That might not even be what it means.
You sink or
Speaker 478: swim, you got to give it a whirl. Do, do, do. Life's a dance. You learn as you go. John Michael Montgomery.
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): 1995. Well, I don't
know if
Speaker 479: that's right. We're just going with it.
Speaker 460: Is there
anything that
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): does support it?
So if
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): I'm the prosecutor, I've got Lance Twig saying he thinks that's him.
Yeah.
I've got a
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): 30-06
Speaker 95: near the scene. I have Tyler Robinson's DNA on the 30-06. I have bullet fragments that the medical examiner says came from Charlie. I've got text confessions
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): to at least being involved, if not pulling the trigger.
Speaker 480: Voluntary surrender
Speaker 481: The
Speaker 482: screwdriver on the roof I mean, you
know
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): That's their case We keep hearing the same thing That's what they've shown so far in court
If that's
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): enough, I don't know I don't know
I
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): think it's all, every
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): single piece of evidence I just said, you could introduce reasonable doubt on it. This is why I don't debate people, because all they're going to do is give me that,
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): and all I'm going to say is, yeah, but there's other people's DNA on the roof, on the screwdriver, and the officer's body cam footage died right before he found the screwdriver.
So we disagree on
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): the screwdriver. What else did you say? Oh, the DNA on the gun, highly degraded
DNA, you know, the
Speaker 189: dog's...
Speaker 189: Didn't find the gun if they were looking for it. Oh, we can't prove the dog's in there. Okay, well, we disagree on that.
They
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): pulled bullet fragments from the neck. Yeah, but they pulled seven, and they only provided four, and they're not the right size. The.30-06 is
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): .308 inches, and actually, I look. They do expand, actually, not shrink. They expand to fill the full barrel
Speaker 292 (lower-pitched voice): size, but actually should be
Speaker 292 (lower-pitched voice): 0.308 or even above i looked at testing of this they can be as low as 0.307 inches and as high as 0.311 inches i think and in testing this particular type around and the one they found was under uh it was 0.286 to 0.301 which is not
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): in the range so it looks like so i mean all we would do is like
they
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): would give one piece of fed slop evidence and I would give one piece of reasonable doubt. And then they would give a piece and I would give reasonable doubt. And that's it. That's not a
Speaker 43: debate. That's like
what we do
Speaker 43: every night here, you know?
Hey, I'll move your
Speaker 43: mouth as little as possible so
we can
Speaker 43: edit whatever we want over it. Thanks for all your work, Papa Baron. Go Max. You don't even need to tell him to not move his mouth.
You
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): can, they can AI that.
They can AI
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): his mouth out of it so you can't read his lip to what he actually said.
The
Speaker 90: 30-06 at Charlie's neck must have sounded like when you hit a gong. B.S. Neck
Speaker 483: of steel. Yeah, that wouldn't be.
That wouldn't be. Baron, on your
Speaker 205 (lower-pitched voice): podcast.
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): Oh, thank you.
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): Uh, you're great. So the person asking twigs says that he saw the note at 11 PM on September 10th.
I thought Taylor
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): texted him earlier about the note.
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): No, the official story is that he texted him right at precisely at 11.
He also
Speaker 164: don't really blink. I thought I saw the mouth when first came out. I thought I was seeing things. No, it's like they
Speaker 485: froze his face.
It's like they froze
Speaker 485: his face. And I, um,
I
Speaker 485: just think they should have jumped up and down and said this is ludicrous. I mean, this doesn't even look like a person's talking. Judge, you can't accept this. They
should have,
Speaker 485: like, moved to strike the whole thing and said this is nonsense. His mouth isn't
Speaker 486: even moving. Baron, your ventriloquist skills are unmatched. Laughing good tonight. Christ is king indeed. Yes.
Speaker 487: Yes. Who said that?
Speaker 340 (lower-pitched voice): maybe erica wanted to personally take the evidence to quantico lab to test it um yeah
that's not what
Speaker 182: i had in mind there
uh but
Speaker 182: bear on the vice principal oh i'm now the vice principal no that's
a lot of power and
Speaker 90: check out anna escobar's work about google trends image searches at fort
Speaker 45 (lower-pitched voice): huachuca concerning naval surface warfare center crane I'm going
to get to it.
Speaker 45 (lower-pitched voice): she's on my list of things to watch as well. I just haven't had
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): time to do it this week with all that's been going on.
But I
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): have that bookmarked as well. I
have a
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): feeling
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): all I'm going to be doing tomorrow is meetings and watching podcasts.
Not a bad day. Not a
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): bad day.
Speaker 337 (lower-pitched voice): Thank you. FYI,
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): TR's usage of the word yet in his alleged text message, he's using the word at the end of a sentence
as an
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): adverb. I'll be stuck in Orem for a little while longer yet. This is...
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): uncommon usage outside of pa ohio and virginia
you know what's funny i lived in
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): central pennsylvania for a year and they did it like crazy they said it like that i always thought it was just a midwestern thing i didn't realize it was even further east than that mid-atlantic maybe you're saying ohio's midwest i heard
it in
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): indiana a lot people would add yet to the end so maybe it's in indiana as well um i didn't
Speaker 45 (lower-pitched voice): realize it was quite that restricted in the regionality but yeah
Speaker 488: when i was in pennsylvania everybody said yet at the end of everything.
I was
Speaker 45 (lower-pitched voice): like,
Why are
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): we adding yet to everything? What's
going on
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): here? I haven't had time to get over to get a Hatchi dog yet. We
don't need the
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): yet there. Hey, Baron,
Speaker 453 (lower-pitched voice): do you think she may be traveling with her children? I'd like to
hope so
Speaker 453 (lower-pitched voice): and would love to know.
It's an
Speaker 453 (lower-pitched voice): option. I mean,
do
Speaker 341: you take your kids to their dad's preliminary hearing? I don't know.
I don't think I would want them
Speaker 453 (lower-pitched voice): in that environment.
So
Speaker 453 (lower-pitched voice): Lance and Tyler and Love lived together. He
Speaker 302: didn't turn him in or call the cops. Now we're expected to believe Lance is testifying in
such a
Speaker 302: way that would incriminate Tyler and is being vague.
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): Yep.
You nailed
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): it. My B, is there a connection between the white Toyota and the rented Toyotas by the Egyptian plane guys? I hope you saw that discussion. I'm not making short of it, but we did discuss that
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): just a little bit ago.
sir
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): baron my son has a world war one mauser it is not chambered for 30 at six we even know if tr mauser is chambered
for 30
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): at six sorry if i missed in previous shows love you for
Speaker 91: oh thank you excuse me for all
you do um i
Speaker 91: think it is because
they test
Speaker 91: fired it
i think
Speaker 91: uh can't yeah they had to have in order to get the rounds to test for the um they're going to go
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): through the through the um
barrel
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): in order to test the striations so i'm almost positive they test fired it
uh can't help but
Speaker 43: feel heavy about the fate of tr scares me to think someone could so easily be made a patsy thank
you and
Speaker 43: candace
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): for all you do god bless we don't know how easy it is to make a patsy we don't know what his involvement
was if any lt says
Speaker 95: hunting slash fishing trip an interview and then a note it said something slash something another coincidence
Speaker 489: no i don't know maybe can
we talk
Speaker 489: about how lt and t are on camera so awkwardly stiff uh
not how people
Speaker 462 (lower-pitched voice): normally appear on camera they do not move at all
yeah i mean tyler the only
Speaker 490: time we
saw him
Speaker 490: being stiff was when he was in a
black jacket or something
Speaker 491: whatever he was wearing
wondering
Speaker 286 (lower-pitched voice): if the uve location was chosen specifically for the strange right to speedy trial for the victim's family they could push it through and simultaneously
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): of erica another stage to cry on uh maybe i don't know how did
lance feel
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): about charlie trump politics the left uh
we'll get into
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): that this week um we have
Speaker 20 (lower-pitched voice): evidence of how he felt about it and we'll get
into it this
Speaker 20 (lower-pitched voice): week uh no gaylytics
have they
Speaker 190: asked lance i don't even know what that means have they asked lance if he knows what a fury a furry is and does he identify as a furry uh they
didn't ask on
Speaker 89: camera i don't know that's why i'd have been like come on buddy elephant
Speaker 492: what are you mastodon saber-toothed tiger
Speaker 89: like an aggressive furry
why does it feel
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): like the state of utah is a third world
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): country embedded inside the united states of america it's starting to isn't it starting to
Speaker 312: Where the defense team's names in Google Trends,
Speaker 493: Christ is King, love you. They were indeed.
They were indeed. Catherine
Speaker 494: Nestor, in particular, in July, and our greatest ally,
Speaker 495: in quotes.
I do
Speaker 463: do.
Speaker 340 (lower-pitched voice): Yes, yes, I said it. Safe and effective vibes from the 7K Club.
Yeah,
Speaker 496: safe and effective, wear the mask, six feet of social distancing, 9-11 was terrorist, we landed on the moon, Oswald killed
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): Kennedy, Sirhan killed Kennedy, RFK, James Earl Ray killed MLK, I mean, these are all
Speaker 192 (lower-pitched voice): just not true things. You
might believe one or more of
Speaker 112: them, but I don't know anyone who believes all of them.
Speaker 168: woman in room with Lance Twiggs was attorney at hearing. Same suit. Got
one of the
Speaker 315: prosecutors. Makes sense. I
think it's
Speaker 315: hilarious that the state made the case for the defense. Thank you, Utah prosecutors. I think
Speaker 497: Hull did when he said that the ring doorbell camera lady said there were
a
Speaker 498: bald man and three passengers driving. I mean,
Speaker 316: I think that helped.
And it's
Speaker 316: what Max today, like Kanye did on Tim Pool 2022.
Didn't see
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): that. Imagine how different things would be if CK did host Shapiro on his 9-9 show. He did.
He did host him on his
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): 9-9 show. How easy the transition would have been for them. Ben is the angel of death for conservative media companies. That is all. Mr. Calm, he did. He was on that 9-9.
what is
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): your favorite teddy roosevelt biography it's for myself
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): and my teen son we homeschool so my homeschooled uh was eighth grader last
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): year asked me the same question and
the one i
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): recommended for a homeschooler was river of doubt river
of
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): doubt it's about his post-presidency though there is some discussion of his presidency and you know laced throughout the book
but
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): it is it reads like a novel it is such an easy read it is exciting there's there's a native americans there's
Speaker 192 (lower-pitched voice): people dying there's a like not in a gruesome way but you know like there's there's a life and
death
Speaker 305: there's willy or won't he there's danger i mean it reads like a novel but
it's a
Speaker 305: biography it's a true story river of doubt
a river of doubt you
Speaker 323 (lower-pitched voice): will love it your kid will just be fascinated uh
what if he
Speaker 323 (lower-pitched voice): doesn't talk
Speaker 43: about ck who
Speaker 500: did he say he was engraving
Speaker 43: bullets for oh wait if he doesn't talk about ck doesn't sound like he said he was doing it for any particular he just wanted to send some messages on the hunt
all of
Speaker 43: it bull butter truth will
prevail
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): thank you be christ is king indeed i hope truth prevails regardless of what the truth is i hope it prevails they never ask what's your relationship to mr robinson ever
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): um well
they did discuss that
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): they were
Speaker 437: dating they started dating uh but they didn't ask what the relationship was on that date no they
didn't
Speaker 55 (lower-pitched voice): building three four five six seven also damaged unusually seen in space view it's due dustified buildings 9 11 revisions gotcha thank you i will check
it out congratulations
Speaker 360: on the spotify charts trending on x about this too really about what
I
Speaker 502: don't see a trend. I'll
have
Speaker 494: to check that out. Thank you.
The
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): motive is the least believable part. Kirk seldom brought up gay stuff, and he supported Trump, who's
openly
Speaker 286 (lower-pitched voice): pro-gay. YMCA is his favorite song.
Speaker 503: That might
make him
Speaker 286 (lower-pitched voice): gay.
Speaker 503: Um...
Not only
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): that, Charlie was actually pro-gay publicly. He did not make any bones about it. He was not into gay marriage, but he was like, love
who you
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): want. I don't care. When
LT was asked if
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): the text was
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): on 910 or 911, did he say that Tyler didn't text anyone else on 910? How would LT know who Tyler texted throughout any particular day? I don't
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): remember hearing that. I'd have to go back and look.
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): Lance Twiggs, owning an Infiniti FX35
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): SUV. No, it wasn't white. It was silver. It looks just like that, but silver.
It was
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): mentioned in news stories being left at the apartment when LT vanished. Yeah, and I have a picture of it.
That's how I
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): know it's silver.
TR never
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): talked about CK. When you found out he shot him, you never asked why? I'd be like, WTF, why you never mentioned them
Speaker 460: ever? Well,
I think
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): the explanation from the prosecution would be it was explained in the notes.
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): Actually, maybe it wasn't
Speaker 504 (lower-pitched voice): explained in the note. Hold on. Tyler Robinson Boot. Will that get it? Hold, please. If you are reading this from my text, so sorry, I left the house this
Speaker 297: morning on a mission and set an auto text. Likely
dead or
Speaker 297: facing a lengthy prison sentence. I had the opportunity to take out Charlie Kirk, and I took it. I don't know if he will have succeeded.
uh
Speaker 439: yeah he said he does talk about i wish we'd lived in a whatever but yeah um yeah
i never never asked
Speaker 505: him why it's a good question that's a great catch
great catch
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): the tpsa employees who interacted with tyler would have been better day of id witnesses than lance why are they not depositioned and presented that's a good
question what card is lance twig drive
Speaker 55 (lower-pitched voice): we just answered that that's a good good call we just answered
that
Speaker 55 (lower-pitched voice): that bee was in Dillon and Bozeman. We don't
want her
Speaker 55 (lower-pitched voice): here. I'm
assuming the bee means
Speaker 183: blonde. That blonde was in Dillon and Bozeman. I believe so. I mean, the planes came
Speaker 346 (lower-pitched voice): from Washington and it's a plane she uses and I didn't see another plane that took her out there. So I think that's where she went.
If the mic got
Speaker 459: an electrical current, would it still shatter? Thanks, Baron and Daisy, for your hard work. Jesus is Lord and King. I don't know the answer to that. I
wish I
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): did, but I don't.
At
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): 4.13, Lance says they didn't share a bedroom. That is an accurate
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): representation of what he said. I was giving talks at my college, no three, about these squibs and other evidence of
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): controlled demo.
Commercial planes
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): can't go that fast in atmosphere.
I don't
Speaker 338 (lower-pitched voice): know. Are those two sentences related? Because I'm not following it.
And I don't know
Speaker 338 (lower-pitched voice): what plane you're talking about.
I'm a total loss
Speaker 374 (lower-pitched voice): with that one.
uh
Speaker 374 (lower-pitched voice): et oh that's that looks like uh latin which is not my forte i'll sit
Speaker 506: through a latin mass but i got a book
and it
Speaker 506: translates to english can't remember candace giving license
plates
Speaker 187 (lower-pitched voice): of specific rental cars early on or any of the cars you're speaking on could they be any
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): of those i can't remember if you guys gave models of cars along with the plate numbers is why i asked yes they were toyota rav4s a toyota forerunner forerunner and
Speaker 338 (lower-pitched voice): toyota camrys
Speaker 338 (lower-pitched voice): and those cars we were just looking at could have been RAV4s. I don't know. I'm not an expert at cars.
Maybe the guy in black
Speaker 95: was supposed to wear maroon. I don't think so. I
think he was
Speaker 95: the black Tyler. In black Tyler. Have
these been
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): compared to the potential operators, rental cars? Yeah, we did that tonight. We
did
Speaker 508: that.
Speaker 187 (lower-pitched voice): Uh, my phone knows where I am every minute of every day while the speculation about when, where Tyler was, did he have location tracking turned off?
I don't
Speaker 509: know. I mean, I'm, I'm flying in the same plane you guys are in. I'm just observing maybe different stuff, but we're, we're
Speaker 13: all getting the same info. Finally caught alive. Thank you so much for all you do be Christ is King indeed. Thank you for that. Just a hit
Speaker 182: and run compliment. That's
Speaker 510: polite. Thank
you.
Speaker 182: Barron, how do you find out who's
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): on government planes? We had a plane land in my hometown, Butte, Montana. And
not
Speaker 45 (lower-pitched voice): surprisingly, no one knows who it is. Also, Bill Clinton spotted in Big Timber, Montana this week. You can
do a
Speaker 45 (lower-pitched voice): FOIA. Do
a FOIA request. Find out
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): what plane it was or what time it landed or what day it was there.
Then ask who
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): was on it.
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): A lot
of
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): times they'll tell you.
Unless there's
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): some reason they can't. And they'll tell you why they can't.
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): But, but, but, but, but,
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): but, but Baron, I can assure you plenty of gay men enjoy hunting and fishing. I have an ex-husband to prove it. Your ex, I didn't mean
Speaker 295: to laugh about that. Your expertise is otherwise spot on. Keep on trucking. I did not mean to laugh at your ex-husband. I apologize.
I just wasn't expecting
Speaker 271: that, you know, it was like.
Speaker 271: dry humor if you meant it that way i took it what are your thoughts on tyler's behavior and mannerisms in court if you're innocent and facing the same charges wouldn't you show more emotion
nah not
Speaker 376: necessarily i mean that's just empty the individual
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): white suv stopped middle street earlier video of yours oh no that's a different one that was
a
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): key of soul can
a criminal
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): negligence case be brought against charlie's professional security country company
Their
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): behavior is either incompetence or suspect from the
Speaker 338 (lower-pitched voice): planning to the transport.
That would
Speaker 338 (lower-pitched voice): be up to what the Utah law is. And I'm not, I'm not a expert in criminal law in Utah.
I doubt
Speaker 338 (lower-pitched voice): it.
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): Lived and dated for two years, yet had separate bedrooms. I know married people that have separate bedrooms. I don't think that's that unusual. I mean, we don't, but I know people who do. I
think if LT
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): says TR didn't text him because TR didn't send the levy message, they sent it for the narrative to show they were a couple.
That
Speaker 302: could be a good point. He doesn't remember it because
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): that's why it says moi-moi because it's Australian. Hey, I wasn't sure if you were
an agent
Speaker 102: or not.
Then I
Speaker 102: saw you on Liberty Lockdown with Buckley.
Now I
Speaker 102: can sleep easy. You weren't sure if I was an agent?
What did I say on Liberty
Speaker 511: Lockdown with Buckley?
Whatever it
Speaker 52: was, it was great. It was fantastic. I can assure you.
Well,
Speaker 512: thank you. I'm glad to have eased your mind.
uh
Speaker 512: suck it daily oh yeah oh yeah yeah
Speaker 448: yeah sorry i shouldn't have said that uh no worries if you don't get this on
Speaker 47: air i just want to say i appreciate all you do to get this message out thanks to daisy too much love to you all well thank you it's very kind i be lt face and mouth movements
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): even look like it could be one of those masks doesn't move head
neck etc weird
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): that's a good point i didn't think about that but how do you get the voice i don't know
I think
Speaker 316: the narrative is that the screenshots were taken on the 11th of Lance Twig's phone, but iMessage timestamps would say yesterday at.
Not
Speaker 513: necessarily.
Speaker 514: I don't
think they
Speaker 515: say. I
Speaker 514: think
it depends on when they
Speaker 516: captured them.
I think after like a
Speaker 517: week, they'd say the day name, don't they?
I don't
Speaker 512: know. I'm working about 20 minutes from the courthouse, not trying to be mean, but they all look like this here in Utah, bro. That's not mean. Not mean. CK on stairs going inside
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): UVU in original video. CK says, I'm just using the restroom. I'll be right back on TT, Hannah Frost, Hannah Emory 25. Thank you. Thank you. First
time super
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): chat.
Speaker 90: Want to start off with go Hoosiers? Thank you.
Never
Speaker 90: thought when I graduated from IU in 2010, we would be national champions.
Speaker 518: Thank you for all you do every week. I was
there
Speaker 19 (lower-pitched voice): 0-4, 0-5, 0-6, and they
Speaker 346 (lower-pitched voice): were not national championship caliber football team.
That was the Jerry
Speaker 519: DiNardo era and Terry Heppner. They weren't very good
at all, but
Speaker 519: they've
Speaker 39: gotten
Speaker 520: better.
They've
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): gotten better.
uh why did
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): tyler tell lance they grabbed some crazy guy in similar clothes did he even know that at plain clothes
what to look for uh
Speaker 373: i don't know
that's a
Speaker 373: good question how would they have known
that maybe he's
Speaker 373: following news closely i don't know
hard to
Speaker 374 (lower-pitched voice): believe in the justice
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): system sometimes yes did you
know there are snipers
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): on the roof during these court proceedings i heard that i didn't see
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): him but i heard that
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): Happy to see the dogs being covered by the big broadcasters. I covered them months ago and thought it deserved more attention. Thank you. We even cut some of the footage. We have a
lot of
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): footage of the dogs, but there's only so much you can cover.
Sometimes God
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): takes the ones we love from
Speaker 341: Earth, but not our heart and memories takes them out of pain by calling them home sooner than we want.
Oh, that's kind of a
Speaker 522: beautiful way to put it.
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): I think it's safe to say this had nothing to do with the LGBTQPS5HDMILMNOP crew.
I
Speaker 95: tend to agree.
She
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): also did small events and small groups on the days before she spoke Sunday. Could be the reason went Friday. Sister was there.
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): Yeah, could be. Could be. I just don't understand why you
Speaker 346 (lower-pitched voice): wouldn't fly into IAD and then be right there. Why would you fly into Manassas, which is down by Quantico? Like, that doesn't make sense to me. And she flew in at midnight on Friday night.
So why
Speaker 338 (lower-pitched voice): not just...
flying to Washington. I believe
Speaker 343: the family and judge have put the fear of God in the jail to keep TR safe. He
would have been gone
Speaker 343: by now. Pray, pray, pray. Actually, is she flying
at
Speaker 523: midnight? I
might have
Speaker 318 (lower-pitched voice): that time wrong. I'd
double check
Speaker 318 (lower-pitched voice): that. Actually, I think she flew in
at 7 p.m. Yeah, it was 7 p.m., I think. But
Speaker 318 (lower-pitched voice): thank you. Thank you. Yeah, pray.
hmm no wonder
Speaker 387 (lower-pitched voice): the price of silver is so high way too many people being paid 30 pieces at a time thank you for
the show no biblical reference
Speaker 387 (lower-pitched voice): am i crazy for wanting to
Speaker 460: order a steak at this penguin steakhouse
not at
Speaker 460: all um it's it's actually phenomenal i had a friend eat there recently and he said
it was phenomenal
Speaker 460: he said it was a great steakhouse great
Speaker 524: service great food um friendly people great
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): atmosphere beautifully decorated
You know, but
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): what it's worth, if I'm ever in Panguitch, that's where I'm eating. Neff's job description with military and where they take place.
Speaker 525: I don't know what that means. Check. Oh, check Neff's job description. He
Speaker 350: hadn't worked there since 2020. I don't
know that
Speaker 526: that's particularly relevant, but I mean,
Speaker 527: I'm
aware of
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): what he did. It was like wargaming for
people.
Are
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): they two cars in the parking lot when Tyler jumps off the roof? Same two cars when
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): Tyler is standing at the top of the stairs, white and dark. The white one could be. I think we've ruled the other one out because it was red.
Words of
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): the strange text exchange sound more and
Speaker 147: more like the bloke that was testifying. J.S. I agree. I
just flat
Speaker 147: out agree.
Today's mass
Speaker 147: reading was Isaiah 1, 10 through 7. Defend
Speaker 528 (lower-pitched voice): the widow. Was it
Speaker 529: really?
Oh, I
Speaker 528 (lower-pitched voice): don't have the English, the Novus Ordo missile. I only
have the Latin
Speaker 530: missile back there,
the
Speaker 78 (lower-pitched voice): Latin missile. Oh,
I can
Speaker 78 (lower-pitched voice): look it up here. Oh,
I
Speaker 530: got it on my phone.
Was it really? Law date. Law date's a
Speaker 317 (lower-pitched voice): great app, by the way. You
guys ever
Speaker 317 (lower-pitched voice): want to know the daily readings? Daily readings.
Hold please. Daily
Speaker 78 (lower-pitched voice): readings.
Yeah, Isaiah 1, 10
Speaker 90: through 17. You nailed it. Good call, Ed Franks. Daily Mass attender, though you are.
Hear the word of the
Speaker 531: Lord,
Speaker 25 (higher-pitched voice): princes of Sodom. That's how it started. That's how the daily reading started? Listen
to the
Speaker 221 (higher-pitched voice): instruction of our God, people of Gomorrah. God was angry that
Speaker 90: day, my friends. Wow.
You can go back
Speaker 89: and read Isaiah. I don't remember him being so lit. Former 911 dispatcher here. SOP in our department when an officer's body cam battery died was for them to acknowledge it over the radio. The dispatcher would log it, wondering what the SOP is for Orem PD. I
Speaker 164: would be surprised if it's not the same. AB,
so many
Speaker 164: Tylers running around, and the one they happened to film in the stairwell, that
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): spike with TPSA, is screaming sus to me.
I think it's all
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): bogus and easy to see. Christ is king indeed.
Oh, spoke. I
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): agree.
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): I agree. Why
are these
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): Zionists so heavy on calling people retards all the time now? When did this become acceptable? It
feels so
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): vulgar to me. It's kind of the shine has been taken off of the word. And by that, I mean
it's not
Speaker 192 (lower-pitched voice): as –
I think
Speaker 192 (lower-pitched voice): people realize people weren't using it to degrade mentally –
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): different people like they you know they you know we weren't calling someone slow
Speaker 158: retarded that no one's rude like that
no one
Speaker 158: says that anymore
um but
Speaker 158: the uh the zionists are overusing
it
Speaker 532: to the point it's like they think they have a cool word now and so they use it all
the time
Speaker 532: like it only has effect if you use it sparingly
went to utah on a
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): work trip a few months ago went to a bar and asked a few locals about kirk they shut the conversation down immediately and left the bar
B.
I wonder what
Speaker 243: kind of bar you were in.
I call it Sodom
Speaker 243: and Orem.
Speaker 533: Oh! You
must have
Speaker 243: read the daily
Speaker 396: reading today. Wasn't the white RAV4, the car the fed guy got pulled over and let go? Christ is king indeed. That's the rumor. Did
you notice that
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): when they found the rifle, they said they cleared it and made it safe, but no one asked if the safety was on or not. When they found
it or
Speaker 90: how easy hard it was put safety on. I was a little disappointed with that because to me, you would take pictures before you touched it.
right you
Speaker 90: would want it in the condition it was found
pull it out i
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): mean you're with professionals you're with cops don't shoot anyone pull it out picture wrap with the towel picture turn it over
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): picture okay now everyone step back we're gonna clear it and then you clear it towards the you know down range where no one's that way towards the
ground or something i was
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): disappointed
Was it
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): a white vehicle in the middle of the road? That was a, yes, Jillian. That was a Kia Soul. That was a different car.
Hope you read
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): this after, if not on
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): the show. Now the BS said his security was on the call. Then Tim Pool said his too. And now Frank Turek said Seth Dillon was on the phone too while in the car. Strategic confusion. Did Frank Turek
Speaker 534: say Seth Dillon was also on the
phone with
Speaker 534: security? Okay.
i don't i
Speaker 535: don't see that
i'll have to i'll have to check
Speaker 453 (lower-pitched voice): that i i don't know that i can accept that as fact i've not heard that i'll say
that i live eight
Speaker 453 (lower-pitched voice): miles away from
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): quantico that's a big base you could be anywhere i'm
having karen read
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): flashbacks not saying tyler's innocent
Speaker 45 (lower-pitched voice): but the case is fed slop that i
think
Speaker 45 (lower-pitched voice): I think that's becoming increasingly evident. That's why they're freaking out and attacking everybody. Candace, episode 266 talks about Egyptian cars, white 2023, RAV4, black rim, black mirrors, looks similar.
Yeah,
Speaker 370 (lower-pitched voice): we'll have to go back and look. But yeah, I know that that
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): was the rental car they were talking about.
Hey, big
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): question. I heard the plane was
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): donated to Charlie before he passed. Is that true? Also,
Anna
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): Escobar found, like, 17
Speaker 45 (lower-pitched voice): big players being photo searched near Fort Huachuca right before the Big Bang.
I don't know that the plane was
Speaker 303: donated. I haven't heard that.
I haven't
Speaker 537: heard that.
a
Speaker 303: rare wake baby boomer.
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): God bless all. I didn't mean to bang on the boomers. It was not on purpose. Had
a thought
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): tonight watching Candace when AK said it was supposed to be
Speaker 12: you. What if CK knew and sacrificed himself to protect
Speaker 110: her? Number one in Sahuarita. Sahuarita, Arizona.
Speaker 385: You guys have fun city names there. I
don't think he
Speaker 345: could have arranged to sacrifice himself unless I don't know.
How
Speaker 200 (lower-pitched voice): would Lance know that Tyler did not text anyone else for 11 on the 10th?
I don't
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): know. Counsel, your Google Trends discovery for the
win
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): tonight on Escobar. Just dropped bombs on the case, live streamed on Stu Peters. Thank you. I'll check that out. I
Speaker 370 (lower-pitched voice): know that one thing they were reporting was wrong, but I'm not going
Speaker 528 (lower-pitched voice): to bang on Stu or Anna because I think they're trying to get it right. But
I know that
Speaker 528 (lower-pitched voice): there was one picture being floated around and there was a name under it and it was not that guy's name.
Speaker 528 (lower-pitched voice): it was not his job title. But
that doesn't mean
Speaker 538 (lower-pitched voice): they're like way off. It just means there's one error. And I don't
want to
Speaker 538 (lower-pitched voice): be like the Fed sloppers are like,
Speaker 539: oh, you made one mistake. Everything
you said
Speaker 539: is invalid. That's not logical. But
I do know there
Speaker 370 (lower-pitched voice): was one mistake in what was being reported today on Twitter about it.
So I'd have
Speaker 370 (lower-pitched voice): to watch carefully and double check everything.
Speaker 540: And I plan to.
Please
Speaker 343: check IG message, sending email, subject urgent. I don't
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): even have access to Instagram. I
couldn't check the IG
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): message if I wanted to. That's Nurse Casey does Instagram. The wood line is
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): connected to the National Security Study. It's
several houses
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): down. It's
not
Speaker 45 (lower-pitched voice): right there.
tyler's
Speaker 45 (lower-pitched voice): shadow bounces off the building wall to his left before he hits the main sidewalk how is that possible uh i don't
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): know i spent a long time looking i spent like four hours one day looking at the shadows so i don't recall that exactly but i know that i looked at the shadows and i and i
Speaker 541: walked away feeling like they were all in the up and up but i i could double check
baren
Speaker 52: please waiting ask you for two days if a client passes on during their own trial does privilege still exist
or can
Speaker 90: defense lawyer or others release collected evidence? Oh, man, that's
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): a million-dollar question. We had this arise
in a
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): case I
Speaker 337 (lower-pitched voice): was working on. The client died, and the state instantly
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): tried to get access to everything. Died
like a
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): week before the trial,
and we
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): didn't turn it over.
And they
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): insisted
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): that we had to, and it was a big fight.
Speaker 346 (lower-pitched voice): And I honestly stopped working on that case like two years into the fight and don't know how they resulted. But
I know
Speaker 542: it's a contested issue. I don't know if Utah has some specific rule. I mean, ultimately, privilege is a state
Speaker 543: rule. It's
not a
Speaker 543: federal rule. So what's
true in
Speaker 543: whatever state I was, I think it was a New York case, but I don't remember, honestly, New
York or New
Speaker 543: Jersey. It was up in the Northeast somewhere. I don't
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): remember.
I don't
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): remember how it was resolved, and I know that it was really contingent on the state statute about privilege or the rule about privilege. So I think you'd have
Speaker 338 (lower-pitched voice): to look carefully at Utah
to find out. Anyone else get
Speaker 338 (lower-pitched voice): an Apple News alert? The
Mitch
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): McConnell passed yesterday. I saw it as I was getting offering at church and went to grab my phone, but first afterwards
said the
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): story was gone, and the story was gone. I did not get that Apple News alert, but I don't get Apple News alerts.
What do
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): you think ate brunch with eyebrows? AK, other TP rep, Christ is King. Much love, granddaddy, from
Cross
Speaker 361 (lower-pitched voice): Planes. Check out Thomas Drug's Soda Fountain. Okay. I don't want
to say my
Speaker 453 (lower-pitched voice): suspicion yet.
Because I'm running down a
Speaker 453 (lower-pitched voice): hot lead on a plane.
how can
Speaker 167: this many people be involved and not crack? It blows my mind, especially all the maroon decoy
Speaker 285 (lower-pitched voice): boys just starting the show, so you may have already discussed. No, I've not discussed that. I'll just say there's lots of large operations involve many people that never say a word. Think of JFK, think of RFK.
The
Speaker 544: moon
Speaker 176 (lower-pitched voice): landing. You get a lot of 9-11. You get a lot of big operations where people never say a word. But that's not unusual to me.
I'm
Speaker 176 (lower-pitched voice): behind on the live. I am at the white SUV. Could that be the same SUV that was at the
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): road when he's supposedly walking? Yes,
it could be, I
Speaker 341: think. I think it's the one that turned out in the parking lot, right? Did
you watch
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): this? I don't watch psychics. No. No. I don't want to know about anything they said. I don't watch them. Don't mention them to me. I am way not into psychics.
I know
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): you didn't know that, so I'm not getting on to you, but I don't
Speaker 346 (lower-pitched voice): even want to know what they think. I
don't want
Speaker 346 (lower-pitched voice): to be tainted in any way. I think that
is not my
Speaker 346 (lower-pitched voice): cup of tea.
Just sending my
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): support. St. Michael, pray for us. We have Jesus in our hearts forever. Christ is king indeed.
Yeah,
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): thank you. And again, I'm not getting on to that person for sending the psychic thing, but that is not my cup of tea. Like, I don't deal with psychics.
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): uh when i
Speaker 345: hear those texts it seems like schizo chicken scratch lance is obsessed with tyler and has multiple personalities and acting out like
he is tyler
Speaker 156: maybe he thinks he maybe truly thinks he's tyler i
don't know i'm not i don't i don't read
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): them that way uh be barone honest question from irish born and bred catholic did
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): cik cik statement phrase when it was common before principal tweeted
it.
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): Also, hopefully, Chucky Arla?
I don't know
Speaker 514: when that phrase
came into
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): vogue. I'll have to go back and look and see if anyone was saying
it before
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): then. You
could do
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): a Google Trend search on it.
Speaker 91: That'd be a good use of it. Parking garage receipt.
That's a good question. Good
Speaker 91: question.
I
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): think the text was written to have an LGBTQ effect with the plan being Tyler taken out without the need to testify the perfect fluffy LGBTQ story. Correct.
I agree
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): with you.
Maybe use
Speaker 43: the screwdriver to remove his license plate holder. Well, that's a good one. And then left and it fell out of his pocket. I
saw a video
Speaker 43: today. Credible source stating that it has
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): been discovered that TPSA is trying to get rid of as
much money
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): as possible and paying chapters a thousand dollars per month, even using abandoned schools for them.
I
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): don't
Speaker 338 (lower-pitched voice): know what the credible source is. I mean, I'd have to know the credible source. And how would they know they're trying to get rid of
as much
Speaker 338 (lower-pitched voice): money as possible? That's totally distinct. That's motive. That's intent.
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): That's different from they're paying people.
Someone might
Speaker 538 (lower-pitched voice): see the paying people and say, oh, they're trying to get rid of as much money as possible. Let me go report that, and we don't know that to be true. I mean,
I
Speaker 346 (lower-pitched voice): think you'd have to talk
to someone
Speaker 346 (lower-pitched voice): at TPSA that said, this is what we're
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): doing.
second
Speaker 95: super chat last one didn't get read last night number one fan clio michigan there's a
Speaker 100: city in alabama i think it's called
clio uh do you
Speaker 100: think the jury can
be
Speaker 45 (lower-pitched voice): rigged or bought what about the judge this was worded much better last night i'm tired now sorry
kayla do i
Speaker 21: think the jury can be
bought uh i
Speaker 21: think that everyone could be bought at a certain price not
not one say
Speaker 473: everyone
Speaker 285 (lower-pitched voice): a lot A lot of people can be.
i think the judge
Speaker 285 (lower-pitched voice): is all right but i don't know
thank you
Speaker 285 (lower-pitched voice): for continuing great shows and information
Speaker 545: i'm doing my best out here thank
you i
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): forgot the dairy queen versus steakhouse dairy queen 6 38 p.m steakhouse exactly
a
Speaker 285 (lower-pitched voice): three-hour drive earliest arrival 9 38 p.m if he eats and runs his car to 9 47 it's too fast owner said they
were busy um i
Speaker 546: think i don't know where the
Speaker 47: 6 38 p.m came from i think that was
just told
Speaker 47: verbally to candace
I've
Speaker 47: never seen a screen grab of a security
Speaker 95: film that says 6.30, 8 p.m. I've never seen anyone
from
Speaker 43: there testify in writing or
in video
Speaker 43: or anything. So I don't know. I think that might just be a mistranslation of what time it was.
Moi, kiss,
Speaker 43: common flirty, used as
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): a gamer. Oh, it's gamer and Australian. That makes sense. Video
on X sounds like
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): CK's security team says rally in the bathroom.
And
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): don't
Speaker 343: talk to
Speaker 493: P.D., Charlie's Angels?
Did they say don't talk
Speaker 493: to P.D.?
Speaker 504 (lower-pitched voice): I'm going to play it again.
I'll play it with sound
Speaker 504 (lower-pitched voice): this time. We'll all listen together.
Hold, please. All right, I'll keep
Speaker 548: on.
Speaker 549: love you charlie i
Speaker 550: didn't hear
Speaker 551: it
Speaker 338 (lower-pitched voice): if they said it
if they said
Speaker 338 (lower-pitched voice): something about rallying and don't talk to pd i didn't catch it but if
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): you guys heard it i'm not going to challenge
you tr could
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): have exited the garage on level one without going up the stairs after the tunnel i believe cars go in and out of there no need for waddling up steps
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): We'll
Speaker 45 (lower-pitched voice): be right
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): back.
Zero
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): searches in Google Trends for PETN in Israel the last year. Odd with their constant explosives flexing. Can't
ID the
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): law enforcement
Speaker 45 (lower-pitched voice): officer who left extra bullet. So here's the thing about the last,
Speaker 43: yes, no, they can't, or they haven't. You wouldn't Google Trend something that you already know
about,
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): right? Like you wouldn't be like, hey, guys, I need you to build a PETN bomb. They go, okay, hold on, I got to Google,
Speaker 552: what is PETN?
So you wouldn't
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): Google that.
if
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): you're like a scientist working on
it that doesn't make
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): it makes sense to me that it wouldn't be there
if
Speaker 47: they're even using
it uh my b
Speaker 47: go to sleep by the way yes the girlies
still powder our
Speaker 47: noses i'm almost done daisy i'm
Speaker 102: trying here 1992 john michael montgomery life's a dance i
was off
Speaker 68: by three
years here's why i said
Speaker 43: 1995 when i
was in high school
Speaker 43: there was a guy at
our high school
Speaker 43: named
Speaker 32: Bubba.
He's
Speaker 32: now a county commissioner up here, so we don't talk about his Bubba days. But his name
Speaker 31: was Bubba, and he had a giant truck. I don't know what it was. It was all lifted up, big wheels and all that.
And on the
Speaker 35: front, it said, life's a dance. So I
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): figured that had to be like a hot new song, and
that would
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): have been about 1995. That's the only
Speaker 462 (lower-pitched voice): reason I picked 95. Now,
if Bubba's
Speaker 462 (lower-pitched voice): watching, it was a beautiful truck,
kind of a
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): greenish truck, if I recall.
uh is
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): it possible to do a test on the dremel and say it was actually used to write on those bullets match it under a microscope i'm
Speaker 89: not gonna do that test i'm not writing on bullets they might go bang
baron i drive
Speaker 89: through dylan montana all the time to get to my cabin
nice you got a
Speaker 89: cabin look at her flex in her cabin you know who else had a cabin near
there
Speaker 109 (lower-pitched voice): ted kaczynski
i
Speaker 321: kid i kid
Speaker 10: think
Speaker 109 (lower-pitched voice): it was actually up more towards calispo
Speaker 90: 236.47, today's show, top row, left
Speaker 100: between red and blue cars. There's a person standing that moves towards the stop right car at 8X Zoom. You can see they're walking almost as if they have a limp.
Well, that's easy to
Speaker 553: check. I
don't have to go back to
Speaker 416 (lower-pitched voice): 236.47 or whatever. I can just pull the footage back up. Here we go.
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): you said there's a person standing that moves towards the stopped white car. So I'm going to play it
Speaker 363: right before it stops.
There we go. So we're
Speaker 555: talking about that person por ahí. I
think that's who you're
Speaker 555: talking about.
All right, let's
Speaker 556: play it, see what happens. Oh,
I got
Speaker 557: to hit mute.
Speaker 383: Hang on, there we go.
Speaker 390 (lower-pitched voice): That guy might have a limp, actually, now that you mention it. Let's go back a little more, see if we can find a little more of him walking. That
kind of guy looks like he has a limp,
Speaker 558: doesn't he? Where did he come from? Oh, it was too far back. Sorry. Oh,
he did
Speaker 558: touch his earbud there.
Speaker 560: oh he signaled to that car i missed that
i totally
Speaker 560: missed that
watch he's
Speaker 561: walking up the steps he turns looks at the
car touch his ear oh
Speaker 297: i missed that mr costello nice catch zach costello's a stud and a ginger he doesn't
Speaker 562: know it
yet.
He
Speaker 562: doesn't know. All right, now back to Limpy.
All
Speaker 563: right. Is
my man limping? By George? We saw it in
Speaker 565: ultra-high-def 4K. Isn't that right, Officer Tatum?
What a
Speaker 39: great catch. This is why they don't like this show. Bull Butter B.
Speaker 299 (lower-pitched voice): Guys talk shop to other dudes regarding their workplace. Lance should
Speaker 177 (lower-pitched voice): know even more considering they were lovers. Lance should know the process
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): for Tyler to be a master electrician. I-M-O. I-M-O.
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): I, you would think,
I
Speaker 268: mean, they, even if they just roommates, you would think they would know why does
Speaker 566: FBI elite FBI investigator with the pinstripe suit have a British accent. That's a great question. We've been dying to know. I
don't know the
Speaker 95: answer just now joining. May have missed this is there was an interview with someone stating Charlie had gone
Speaker 45 (lower-pitched voice): inside first. I'll look for it. Christ is King. Indeed. I would love to see it because I am just taking their word that it exists. Limping guy before he jumps
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): off roof, get in car. Actually.
Now
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): that you mention it, we'll pull it back up and look and see if limping guy disappeared. But he was walking like off the screen.
Like that way. Or that way
Speaker 567: to me. I think it might be that way to you.
Let's see. All right. Car stopped. Got some
Speaker 368: activity going on on the roof.
Guy's running. Guy's
Speaker 390 (lower-pitched voice): running. He's approaching the white triangle. He's now on the white triangle. Okay.
and
Speaker 568: then
Speaker 569: he is
Speaker 570: spider-manning down the building. This guy's waiting, waiting, waiting. And
then he tears out. And then
Speaker 36 (lower-pitched voice): when the guy jumps off, he turns here. No, we
Speaker 297: never see Gimpy again. He
slows down
Speaker 297: just long enough to see
if this
Speaker 297: guy's hurt or not, and then he takes off. I'm telling you what, guys, that is stellar, stellar.
For
Speaker 571: more
Speaker 381 (lower-pitched voice): information
visit www.fema.org
Speaker 297: Yeah, this side-by-side right here is
Speaker 571: kind of interesting too, this thing. Who's running around in that thing?
You
Speaker 381 (lower-pitched voice): think he
was going
Speaker 381 (lower-pitched voice): to be the gun stash? They were going to put the gun in one vehicle and the person in the other? Or
the
Speaker 572: weapon, whatever it was?
Speaker 298: Interesting. That's
why they hate
Speaker 68: this show because you guys are smarter than I am and
they
Speaker 45 (lower-pitched voice): can't stand it.
You should shorten your
Speaker 45 (lower-pitched voice): streams, take away stickers. Just kidding, just kidding. Bring on the haters. We high IQ. I was about to come unglued. I
was
Speaker 73: like this close. I'm glad I kept reading. I
Speaker 463: thought,
I'll show you a
Speaker 573: short stream. I may stay up all night. I'll
be
Speaker 50: streaming at 4 a.m. These must be video footage of the mystery fed with the badge and gun. Oh,
there
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): must be video footage of the mystery fed with badge and gun who went on roof with UVU officer. Why is it this person
Speaker 90: stepped forward to reveal himself?
That's a
Speaker 90: good question.
Kobe
Speaker 164: Holland, Dylan MT, professional sports shooter, Fort Benning, Georgia.
You have no idea what that
Speaker 539: comment just did.
No idea what that
Speaker 290 (lower-pitched voice): comment did.
I'm taking a
Speaker 290 (lower-pitched voice): picture.
you
Speaker 323 (lower-pitched voice): have no idea how relevant what you just said was.
Rifle had
Speaker 217 (lower-pitched voice): low ID number. Do modern bullets fit older? I think it had
a
Speaker 323 (lower-pitched voice): pre-1944 serial number. We went back and looked at that. I don't know. Kalispell
is known for
Speaker 55 (lower-pitched voice): semiconductor manufacturing, often used in explosive detonations. Oh, is that so?
fraternal order
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): the eagles shares parking lot with the fbi in kalispell just sharing a parking lot with a cult light organization no biggie i don't know what the fraternal or i've
Speaker 290 (lower-pitched voice): never heard of the fraternal order of the
eagles uh tuning
Speaker 290 (lower-pitched voice): into comment portion to save video for work oh welcome
Speaker 187 (lower-pitched voice): okay it's
an sbi guy
Speaker 187 (lower-pitched voice): with a new zealand accent either way he blows at his job who leaves a bullet wouldn't you be in trouble
Speaker 43: for leaving it i would hope so
Speaker 43: Don't want to leave bullets just all over town,
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): just clearing your rifle all over the place. FYI, Blake N. in X-Space right now with Paramount Tactical. Fence flop.
Wasn't part of LT's
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): testimony
Speaker 97 (lower-pitched voice): without video footage because they didn't want to see face expressions or because it showed someone coaching. Christ is king, vice principal. Thank you, indeed. Christ is king, indeed, not
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): vice principal, indeed. Don't want to do that.
I
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): think the defense requested those redactions. So I don't think they would
Speaker 386: have done that.
Wake
Speaker 574: in, crashing out, talking about Candace and you.
Love, R.B.P. Bad slob, like
Speaker 575: Alpo, eat it up, Baldy.
Speaker 333 (lower-pitched voice): Barron, G-I-A-W, stands for God is a Woman.
Our father who art in
Speaker 91: heaven.
uh
Speaker 91: padre uh blake in
Speaker 51 (lower-pitched voice): talking about you on x right now saying you stalked erica kirk i didn't stalker it's a public record what are you
Speaker 305: talking about stalking me like you went there i've been home i promise how come you don't think this is a religious war sending love from your biggest fan in sweden
uh
Speaker 56 (lower-pitched voice): love c is oh christ is king i would love a member show some bible talk
Speaker 89: why did I not say it was a religious war? I think it is. I talk about the demonic element all the time.
This Tyler
Speaker 52: Robinson thing is just a distraction to keep people focused on the real killers.
Keep people focused on the
Speaker 53 (lower-pitched voice): real killers. I don't follow that. Baron, just thought you, I know you guys just told me, saying you went to Arizona to stalk Erica at a church she attends. Also that you and Karen just
Speaker 90: encourage people to stalk her.
I
Speaker 576: didn't go to
Speaker 90: church she attends. I didn't
think she
Speaker 90: was Catholic. I
went to a
Speaker 90: Catholic church. I went to St. Bernadette.
I did not
Speaker 90: go to stalk
Speaker 345: her. I was at a friend's hospice
Speaker 52: bedside. I was flying out on Sunday morning early and was not going to be able to make mass on Sunday. And that church
Speaker 577: was the closest church. There's no stalking there, you psycho.
It was
Speaker 483: beautiful.
Speaker 188: absolutely beautiful. That is so defamatory. I mean, that's accusing
me of a crime. That is
Speaker 57: so defamatory. I
mean, I went
Speaker 305: to a mass with three other men or four other men.
Five other
Speaker 305: men. I can't remember how many men there were. That's ludicrous.
Speaker 298: B-B-B-Baron Mama. BJ.
Poor
Speaker 476: Benny. Thanks for hearing
Speaker 578: that.
poor
Speaker 476: unfortunate initials
Speaker 76 (higher-pitched voice): indeed i did not know where we were going with the rest of that comment i was like hey who's the mod come on somebody get
busy uh how
Speaker 531: did the empty bullet case get back to the apartment when the rifle was confiscated
when did
Speaker 531: he unload the rifle prints on the
cases uh
Speaker 531: the empty bullet case they claim is a test shot it even
Speaker 50: dremeled
Speaker 579: the word test on it just in case we were confused fat slop
uh
Speaker 579: thank you baron for your hard work and sacrifice i do
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): my best here i do my best since they love 33 jeremiah
Speaker 95: 33 three call to
me and i
Speaker 95: will answer you and tell you great and unsearchable things you do not know lord is using you to share the truth thanks
yeah
Speaker 581: apparently going
to
Speaker 67: mass is
Speaker 84: a crime that's what i'm learning uh does the maybe cow on the roof reach into bringing weapon
Speaker 13: out of the pants no way you can tell that
no
Speaker 99: way you can tell that what you have is exactly what happened with the feds and the situation, the Curtis Caldwell center
Speaker 90: in Garland.
Look it
Speaker 90: up. Feds
go
Speaker 21: to those guys to commit it and could have stopped it.
I did a
Speaker 21: whole opening on it. I don't
need to
Speaker 21: look it up. You guys need to look it up. Go read my openings. I
Speaker 305: kid, I kid, but I did do a whole opening on the Curtis Caldwell Garland thing in Texas. Not
Speaker 177 (lower-pitched voice): a whole opening, but it
was a
Speaker 177 (lower-pitched voice): big part. It was a big part of it.
When
Speaker 177 (lower-pitched voice): the lawyer asked Tyler for his chewing gum, they were sitting across from each other. They were in the same room because the lawyer is about to hand him something.
Oh, why wouldn't they
Speaker 343: have just done that before the camera started?
Plot twist,
Speaker 343: Twiggs offs himself, leaves Letter apologizing for framing
Speaker 344 (lower-pitched voice): him now, and they don't have to worry about the truth coming out or being obvious.
That's pretty
Speaker 582 (lower-pitched voice): terrifying.
that's
Speaker 582 (lower-pitched voice): actually more believable than Tyler Robinson did it. Please consider offline backup
of
Speaker 343: your streams. This is all important historic record document worthy material. Thank you for pursuing truth. We, I mean, I have backups of all the recordings, if that's what you're asking. I guess
I could put them
Speaker 153: up somewhere else. You'd land in Kalispell to go to Whitefish, areas packed with retired CIA spooks and sheriffs. I've heard that.
I've
Speaker 153: heard
Speaker 370 (lower-pitched voice): there's a big CIA
Speaker 343: presence up there. Continue. TR used yet like someone from PA, Ohio, VA,
but he
Speaker 343: is not. This along with other abnormal text content
Speaker 303: seems manufactured off in some way. I agree. Sounds British. Charlie's Angels, 47, has a vid from one day ago. Beginning of it is black car says someone don't
Speaker 585: talk to PD. Pfft.
Speaker 585: is black car or someone says I'll have to check it out
and
Speaker 586: I've not seen that
what
Speaker 270: kind of trouble would the prosecutors get into if he caught altering testimony video shenanigans apparently none Utah seems pretty lawless if I'm being honest
uh could
Speaker 270: LR be wearing
a
Speaker 21: mask kind of like the general it could be but I don't think
so
Speaker 387 (lower-pitched voice): lead FBI investigator looks like Maxine the villain from despicable me four I've
never seen it but
Speaker 587: I'll take your word for it
Speaker 587: shame on him for looking like that
Speaker 297: I swear I swear the radio uh cad doesn't match with having a suspect within the quick time frame testified to at the preliminary hearing I'm double checking that thanks for your grind love it p.s. Lance lied uh if you find the answer
Speaker 343: email me let me know don't you don't spend money to send it back but just email what if Tyler is forced to forced pressure
Speaker 585: to confess to protect his parents assured no death penalty not sure how though great So thank you.
I
Speaker 585: mean,
Speaker 416 (lower-pitched voice): we could come up with all reasons, all manner of ways in which Tyler could be forced to do this or forced
to do
Speaker 416 (lower-pitched voice): that. But I mean, we just have to wait and see how it plays out.
But I do
Speaker 416 (lower-pitched voice): know
Speaker 18: this. I appreciate you guys joining me. You'll notice the on-air sign is especially bright because I forgot to put my backlight on tonight. So
I just
Speaker 588: noticed that when I pulled the comments down. I
was
Speaker 582 (lower-pitched voice): like, why is it so offensively bright right there? I apologize, ladies and gentlemen. This is supposed to be a professional outfit. It won't happen again. Well, it probably will.
So it's
Speaker 582 (lower-pitched voice): happened before.
Speaker 589: It'll probably happen again, but I don't mean for it to happen.
If you
Speaker 343: like the show, give it a like. Appreciate the likes. If you want to subscribe, go to the main page, hit subscribe. While you're there, there's a join option next to it. If you hit the join option, you'll become a monthly member. Get access
to all
Speaker 343: the members' content. There's a lot of really good interviews, a lot of just me rambling for
hours at
Speaker 18: a time. It's fun. It's fun. We'll do a member show this Friday, and you'll get an idea of just how fun
it can
Speaker 18: be. And...
Speaker 193 (lower-pitched voice): yeah that's it click the notifications turn those on um i will not be back tomorrow i my schedule is just jam-packed tomorrow we'll not be able to make it
Speaker 289 (lower-pitched voice): uh but i will be back wednesday night and thursday night with a member show friday before taking off saturday as we take off every saturday uh check out the clips channel baron coleman clips you get little condensed versions
Speaker 292 (lower-pitched voice): of some of our segments not whole shows condensed but whole segments sometimes are condensed down into eight to 15 minute digestible bites they're easy to share uh introduce people to the program and the content.
Speaker 292 (lower-pitched voice): um
Speaker 347 (lower-pitched voice): our editor over there is phenomenal he does a great job they're superbly edited like i could never do what he does
ever and
Speaker 347 (lower-pitched voice): he does a great job he deserves
a lot of kudos so um
Speaker 590: i
Speaker 300 (lower-pitched voice): appreciate you
Speaker 591: joining me
oh oh oh oh don't forget jesus loves you
Speaker 592: every
Speaker 593: single day of the week even on sunday saturday tuesday thursday
miércoles he
Speaker 594: loves you
Speaker 47: he loves you ladies and gentlemen
um so
Speaker 47: thank you for
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): joining me and uh i will be back
like i said
Speaker 96 (lower-pitched voice): wednesday i'll be back wednesday have a wonderful
Speaker 595: night everybody and we'll talk soon